<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/christopherlam888/workday-scraper</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Major Claim Adjuster , General Liability]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://travelers.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/ON---Oakville/Major-Case-Specialist--General-Liability_R-43424?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>remote type<br />Hybrid<br />locations<br />ON - Oakville<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R-43424<br />Who Are We?<br />Solid reputation, passionate people and endless opportunities. That’s Travelers. Our superior financial strength and consistent record of strong operating returns mean security for our customers – and opportunities for our employees. You will find Travelers to be full of energy and a workplace in which you truly can make a difference.<br />Job Category<br />Claim<br />Target Openings<br />1<br />What Is the Opportunity?<br />Investigate, evaluate, reserve, negotiate and resolve assigned serious and complex claims in   accordance with Best Practices. Provide quality claim handling and superior customer   service on assigned claims, while engaging in indemnity & expense management. Promptly   manage claims by completing essential functions including contacts, investigation, damages development, evaluation, reserving, litigation management, and disposition. Provides   consulting and training and serves as an expert technical resource to other claim   professionals, business partners, customers, and other stakeholders as appropriate or   required.<br />What Will You Do?<br />Business Processes:<br />Directly handle assigned severe and/or complex claims.<br />Provide quality customer service and ensure file quality timely coverage analysis and communication with insured based on application of policy information to facts or allegations of each case.<br />Consult with Manager on use of Claim Coverage Counsel as needed.<br />Directly investigate each claim through prompt and strategically-appropriate contact with appropriate parties such as policyholders, accounts, claimants, law enforcement agencies, witnesses, agents, medical providers and technical experts to determine the extent of liability, damages, and contribution potential.<br />Claim Strategy:<br />Interview witnesses and stakeholders, take necessary statements, as strategically appropriate.<br />Complete outside investigation as needed per case specifics.<br />Actively engage in the identification, selection and direction of appropriate internal and/or external resources for specific activities required to effectively evaluate claims, such as Subro, Risk Control, nurse consultants nurse consultants, and fire or fraud investigators, and other experts.<br />Verify the nature and extent of injury or property damage by obtaining and reviewing appropriate records and damages documentation.<br />Maintain claim files and document claim file activities in accordance with established procedures.<br />Utilize evaluation documentation tools in accordance with department guidelines.<br />Proactively review CFAs for adherence to quality standards and trend analysis.<br />Utilize diary management system to ensure that all claims are handled timely.<br />At required time intervals, evaluate liability & damages exposure.<br />Establish and maintain proper indemnity & expense reserves.<br />Business Partnership Duties:<br />Provide guidance to underwriting business partners with respect to accuracy and adequacy of, and potential future changes to, loss reserves on assigned claims.<br />Recommend appropriate cases for discussion at roundtable.<br />Attend and or present at roundtables/ authority discussions for collaboration of technical expertise resulting in improved payout on indemnity and expense.<br />Actively and enthusiastically share experience and deep knowledge of creative resolution techniques to improve the claim results of others.<br />Apply the Company's claim quality management protocols, Best Practices and metrics to all claims; document the rationale for any departure from applicable protocols and metrics.<br />Attend depositions, mediations, arbitrations, pre-trials, trials and all other legal proceedings, as needed.<br />Update appropriate parties as needed, providing new facts as they become available, and their impact upon the liability analysis and settlement options.<br />Recognize cases, based on severity/complexity protocols, that should be transferred to another level of claim professional and refer on a timely basis.<br />Appropriately deal with information that is considered personal and confidential.<br />Customer Service:<br />Develop and employ creative resolution strategies.<br />Responsible for prompt and proper disposition of all claims within delegated authority.<br />Negotiate disposition of claims with insureds and claimants or their legal representatives.<br />Recognize and implement alternate means of resolution.<br />Manages litigated claims.<br />Develop litigation plan with staff or panel counsel, including discovery and legal expenses, to assure effective resolution and to satisfy our customers.<br />Apply expert litigation management through the selection of counsel, evaluation and direction of claim and litigation strategy.<br />Track and control legal expenses to assure cost-effective resolution.<br />Effectively and efficiently manage both allocated and unallocated loss adjustment expenses.<br />Develop and employ innovative techniques to manage expense and outcome when independent counsel is engaged.<br />Fulfill specific service commitments made to certain accounts, as outlined in Special.<br />Account Communication (SAC) instructions, and inquiries from agents and brokers.<br />Represent the company as a technical resource, attend legal proceedings as needed, act within established professional guidelines as well as applicable state laws.<br />Actively provide mentoring and coaching to less experienced claim professionals to increase the technical expertise and improve bench strength.<br />Share accountability with business partners to achieve and sustain quality results.<br />Evaluate all claims for recovery potential; directly handle recovery efforts and/or engage and direct Company resources for recovery efforts.<br />May be responsible to research and evaluate current information regarding trends in the law; digest and communicate this information to other Company departments and divisions to assist in underwriting and management decisions.<br />May assist underwriting business partners in marketing and account-contact efforts.<br />May participate in periodic file quality reviews.<br />Perform other duties as assigned.<br />What Will Our Ideal Candidate Have?<br />College degree or equivalent business experience.<br />10+ years claim handling experience with 5 -7 years experience handling serious injury and complex liability claims.<br />Extensive working level knowledge and skill in various business line products.<br />Excellent negotiation and customer service skills.<br />Advanced skills in coverage, liability and damages analysis with expert understanding of the litigation process in all Canadian jurisdictions, including<br />relevant case and statutory law and procedure; expert litigation management skills.<br />Extensive claim and/or legal experience and thus the technical expertise to evaluate severe and complex claims.<br />Able to make independent decisions on most assigned cases without involvement of supervisor.<br />Openness to the ideas and expertise of others actively solicits input and shares ideas.<br />Thorough understanding of commercial lines products, policy language, exclusions, ISO forms, and effective claims handling practices.<br />Demonstrated strong coaching, influence and persuasion skills.<br />Advanced written and verbal communication skills are required so as to understand, synthesize, interpret and convey, in a simplified manner, complex data and information to audiences with varying levels of expertise.<br />Can adapt to and support cultural change.<br />Strong technology aptitude; ability to use business technology tools to effect State insurance adjusting license (where applicable) and ongoing satisfaction of any necessary continuing education requirements.<br />In order to perform the essential job functions of this job, acquisition and maintenance of Insurance License(s) may be required to comply with provincial and Travelers requirements. Generally, License(s) are required to be obtained within three months of starting the job.<br />What is a Must Have?<br />High School Degree or GED required with a minimum of 4 years claim handling experience.<br />Experience utilizing computer technology; such as Microsoft Office, e-mail, Web-enabled applications, and database software.<br />Ability to accurately compute a variety of numerical calculations.<br />Licensing Required: In order to perform the essential job functions of this job, acquisition and maintenance of Insurance License(s) may be required to comply with provincial and Travelers requirements.<br />Must secure and maintain company credit card if required.<br />What Is in It for You?<br />Health Insurance: Employees and their eligible family members – including spouses, partners, and children – are eligible for coverage from the first day of employment.<br />Retirement: Travelers provides a core contribution of 3% of your total eligible earnings to your Deferred Profit Sharing Plan (“DPSP”). Travelers also matches your savings plan contribution dollar-for-dollar up to 5% of base pay.<br />Paid Time Off: Start your career at Travelers with a minimum of 20 days Paid Time Off (“PTO”) annually, plus the opportunity to purchase additional days to allow for up to a total of 36 PTO days per year. You will also receive twelve paid company Holidays.<br />Wellness Program: The Travelers wellness program is comprised of tools, discounts and resources that empower you to achieve your wellness goals and caregiving needs. In addition, our mental health program provides access to free professional counseling services, health coaching and other resources to support your daily life needs.<br />Volunteer Encouragement: We have a deep commitment to the communities we serve and encourage our employees to get involved. Travelers has a Matching Gift and Volunteer Rewards program that enables you to give back to the charity of your choice.<br />Employment Practices<br />Travelers is an equal opportunity employer. We value the unique abilities and talents each individual brings to our organization and recognize that we benefit in numerous ways from our differences. <br />We are committed to providing accommodation to persons with disabilities. If you require accommodation during the recruitment or interview process we will work with you to accommodate your needs.<br />If you are a candidate and have specific questions regarding the physical requirements of this role, please send us an email so we may assist you.<br />Travelers reserves the right to fill this position at a level above or below the level included in this posting.<br />To learn more about our comprehensive benefit programs please visit http://careers.travelers.com/life-at-travelers/benefits/.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Hybrid]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Travelers]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patient Care Associate- The Birthplace-Postpartum /Term Nursery (per-diem)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://albanymed.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Albany_Med/job/43-New-Scotland-Avenue-Albany-NY-12208/Patient-Care-Associate--The-Birthplace-Postpartum--Term-Nursery--per-diem-_65202?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />43 New Scotland Avenue Albany, NY 12208<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />65202<br />Department/Unit:<br />The Birth Place - Gyn<br />Work Shift:<br />Staffing Options Program (United States of America)<br />Salary Range:<br />The Patient Care Assistant (PCA) will work under the direction of the Registered Nurse. During the assigned work period, PCAs will collect patient data, complete personal care of the patient, perform point of care testing such as whole blood glucose, turn & position and/or mobilize patients, and assist with caring for the needs of assigned patients with a focus on progress toward discharge, including during transitions within the acute care stay. The PCA is trained to perform technical procedures such as blood draw and electrocardiography. The Patient Care Assistant promotes the availability of resources for patient care through collaboration with Material's Coordinators for use, stocking, and storage of supplies.<br />The Patient Care Assistant participates in the creation and maintenance of a clean, orderly, and safe environment of care. PCAs may also be asked to provide the service of activity companion for patients requiring 11 observation.</p><p>The Patient Care Assistant is responsible for assisting in the delivery of patient care provided by the caregiving team. They assures that competent, compassionate patient care is uniformly provided to customers.</p><p>Essential Duties and Responsibilities<br />Collects pertinent data and information relative to the patient’s health or situation, including vital signs, height and weight, and food and fluid intake and output.<br />Reports abnormal findings to the RN and patient care team.<br />Participates in care planning and the nursing report process.<br />Incorporates patient/family rights to participate in decision making about their care<br />Utilizes standardized techniques for keeping patients and families informed.<br />Provides personal care to patients including bathing, oral care, and skin care<br />Assists the patient with eating and hydration, grooming, dressing, and toileting.<br />Incorporates safe patient handling into basic restorative care such as ambulation, range of motion and use of assistive and prosthetic devices.<br />Employs strategies to promote a clean, orderly, and safe environment.<br />Demonstrates standard and transmission, based precautions and infection control techniques.<br />Provides details related to patient progress toward the achievement of goals and outcomes to the RN.<br />Documents all care in the patient record.</p><p>Qualifications<br />High School Diploma/G.E.D. or equivalent  - required <br />less than 1 year experience in a health care setting or completion of certified nurse assistant course  - preferred <br /> experience as a paramedic, emergency technician   - preferred <br />Basic knowledge of medical terminology (Medium proficiency)<br />Honest, punctual, and performs the job in adherence to the highest standards of ethical conduct as defined by Albany Medical Center and the tenets of the profession. <br />Ability to communicate cooperatively and effectively with patients, family members, employees and others.</p><p>Physical Demands<br />Standing - Constantly <br />Walking - Constantly <br />Sitting - Rarely <br />Lifting - Frequently <br />Carrying - Frequently <br />Pushing - Occasionally <br />Pulling - Occasionally <br />Climbing - Occasionally <br />Balancing - Occasionally <br />Stooping - Frequently <br />Kneeling - Frequently <br />Crouching - Frequently <br />Crawling - Occasionally <br />Reaching - Frequently <br />Handling - Frequently <br />Grasping - Frequently <br />Feeling - Constantly <br />Talking - Constantly <br />Hearing - Constantly <br />Repetitive Motions - Constantly <br />Eye/Hand/Foot Coordination - Constantly</p><p>Thank you for your interest in Albany Medical Center!</p><p>Albany Medical Center is an equal opportunity employer.</p><p>This role may require access to information considered sensitive to Albany Medical Center, its patients, affiliates, and partners, including but not limited to HIPAA Protected Health Information and other information regulated by Federal and New York State statutes. Workforce members are expected to ensure that:<br />Access to information is based on a “need to know” and is the minimum necessary to properly perform assigned duties. Use or disclosure shall not exceed the minimum amount of information needed to accomplish an intended purpose. Reasonable efforts, consistent with Albany Medical Center policies and standards, shall be made to ensure that information is adequately protected from unauthorized access and modification.<br />Thank you for your interest in Albany Medical Center!<br />Albany Medical is an equal opportunity employer.<br />This role may require access to information considered sensitive to Albany Medical Center, its patients, affiliates, and partners, including but not limited to HIPAA Protected Health Information and other information regulated by Federal and New York State statutes. Workforce members are expected to ensure that:<br />Access to information is based on a “need to know” and is the minimum necessary to properly perform assigned duties. Use or disclosure shall not exceed the minimum amount of information needed to accomplish an intended purpose. Reasonable efforts, consistent with Albany Med Center policies and standards, shall be made to ensure that information is adequately protected from unauthorized access and modification.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[43 New Scotland Avenue Albany, NY 12208]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Albany Medical Center]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Inpatient Pharmacy Technician - St. Lukes - 3rd Shift]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-St-Lukes-Medical-Center---2900-W-Oklahoma-Ave/Inpatient-Pharmacy-Technician---St-Lukes---3rd-Shift_R145754?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora St Lukes Medical Center - 2900 W Oklahoma Ave<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R145754<br />Department:<br />38410 Aurora St. Lukes Medical Center - Pharmacy<br />Status: <br />Part time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />20<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />3rd shift, part time (40 hours per 2 week pay period). Position works every other Thursday, Friday, Saturday, and Sunday. 8pm-6:30am<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Develops competence in dispensing and delivery of medications. This includes developing competence in the department’s use of information systems, technology, and automation used for dispensing and storage of medications.<br />Develops competence in preparing non-sterile products following USP, state, and federal recommendations, as required.<br />Develops competence in entering medication orders in the computer system and/or processing medication requests via the computer system.<br />Develops competence in managing phone calls from customers and team members such as nurses, physicians or patients. This includes accurately understanding and interpreting the issue, timely resolution, or timely hand-off to another team member as appropriate.<br />Develops competence in pharmacy procedures and documentation as required, satisfying legal, regulatory, and department requirements of pharmacy practice.<br />Complies with legal, regulatory, accreditation standards. This includes (but is not limited to) controlled substance procedures, USP procedures and DNV requirements.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Licensure (IL only): State of Wisconsin (registration):<br />Pharmacy Technician or Pharmacy Technician Student; Certification (CPhT) issued by PTCB or ExCPT within two years of hire, or sooner if required by law. Must sit for the certification exam at least one time within the first year of employment.<br />Patient facing teammates may be required to have three certifications: Immunization, BLS through an entity approved by Advocate Health and non-vaccine injectable to be granted from the state of WI or if from out of state, the program is approved by the accreditation council for pharmacy education (ACPE) or by the WI pharmacy examining board.</p><p>Education Required:<br />High School Graduate.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />No experience required.</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Good mathematics skills.<br />Attention to details.<br />Good communication (written and verbal) and interpersonal skills.<br />Basic computer skills.</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job <br />Frequent fine motor motion of hands and wrists to operate keyboard and manipulate syringes <br />Lifts, carries, and/or pushes/pulls various items (bags, boxes, carts, etc.) while utilizing proper technique <br />Will be frequently required to lift to 35 lbs., lift and carry up to 35 lbs. at waist height a reasonable distance, push/pull with 30 lbs. of force <br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, bend, kneel, climb, twist, crawl and reach above shoulders <br />Must have functional speech, vision, touch, and hearing <br />May be exposed to chemical hazards <br />May be exposed to chemical and hazardous waste as well as blood and body fluids and communicable disease. Therefore, protective clothing and equipment must be worn as necessary.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$21.45 - $32.20<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora St Lukes Medical Center - 2900 W Oklahoma Ave]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - Nicu 0.0 Registry]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Advocate-Good-Samaritan-Hospital---3815-Highland-Ave/Registered-Nurse---Nicu-00-Registry_R154153-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Advocate Good Samaritan Hospital - 3815 Highland Ave<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date: May 29, 2025 (2 days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R154153<br />Department:<br />35125 Advocate Good Samaritan Hospital - NICU<br />Status: <br />Part time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />No<br />Hours Per Week:<br />0<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Day shift 7A-7P, minimum 4 shifts in a 6 week schedule. 2 weekend shifts in 6 week schedule. One winter/One summer holiday track.<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Uses the nursing process to assess the needs of the patient, plan and implement individualized interventions and evaluate the effectiveness of the plan of care. Includes the patient and family in planning and implementing care and develops and maintains a therapeutic relationship throughout the healthcare continuum.<br />Anticipates and recognizes significant changes in the patient’s condition, status, and need for care. Provides ongoing assessment of the patient and takes appropriate actions when changes occur. Anticipates and alters the plan of care as needed, mobilizes appropriate resources, and collaborates with other health care team members to coordinate patient centered care.<br />Implements strategies to reduce patient risk and increase patient safety. Assesses patient and family readiness to learn and individualizes the approach as necessary. Works collaboratively to develop strategies to meet the learning needs of the patient and family.<br />Actively coordinates the discharge plan utilizing an interdisciplinary approach. Applies evidence-based practice to deliver patient care. Consistently incorporates nursing and regulatory standards of care into practice.<br />Provides ongoing evaluation of patient, team, and unit outcomes and is empowered to take appropriate action when changes are needed. Supports shared governance activities and initiatives to improve processes and patient outcomes.<br />Demonstrates effective communication, feedback, and conflict resolution skills. Promotes collaboration among healthcare team members. Assumes a leadership role in the care team and delegates appropriately to unlicensed personnel.<br />Promotes a culture of safety through identifying threats to patient safety and intervening to prevent patient harm. Reports patient safety events and near misses in a timely manner. Seeks to identify potential safety issues and assists in the implementation of corrective actions.<br />Applies ethical decision making, demonstrates respect and understanding for peers, and other clinical disciplines. Participates as an effective member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated, unbiased, individualized approach to care.<br />Participates in quality/process improvement initiatives to improve the functions of the department and the patient care experience.<br />Participates in professional activities which contribute to personal professional development and the development of others. Seeks opportunities to be taught, coached, and mentored. Attends required meetings/educational programs and completes annual competencies in a timely manner.<br />Must be able to demonstrate knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patients served. Must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient's status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to his/her age-specific needs, and to provide the care needed as described in the department's policies and procedures. Age-specific information is developed further in the departmental job standards.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Registered Nurse license issued by the state in which the team member practices, and<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Providers certification issued by the American Heart Association (AHA).</p><p>Education Required:<br />Completion of an accredited or approved program in Nursing.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />Typically requires 1 year of experience in clinical nursing.</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Demonstrates progression to provide holistic patient care and the ability to view clinical situations from a patient and family focus.<br />Demonstrates progression to recognize situational changes that require unplanned or unanticipated interventions, and responds to situations with confidence, timeliness and flexibility.<br />Proficient computer skills, use of electronic mail and electronic medical records systems.<br />Excellent communication (written and verbal), listening and interpersonal skills.<br />Demonstrates human relation skills with the ability to develop rapport and maintain positive, professional relationships with a variety of patients, team members and physicians. Ability to take initiative and work collaboratively with others.<br />Demonstrated ability to effectively make critical, independent decisions.<br />Excellent organization, prioritization and problem-solving skills.<br />Demonstrates time management skills with an ability to multi-task and prioritize in an environment with frequent interruptions.<br />Demonstrates coordination, collaboration, delegation and team building skills.<br />Certification Addendum:<br />Team members will maintain annual educational requirements for hospital based certifications (e.g. DNV, CARF or others)</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, reach above shoulders, and twist frequently throughout the workday.<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 50 lbs. from floor to waist.<br />lift up to 20 lbs. over the head.<br />carry up to 40 lbs. a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 30 lbs. of force.<br />perform a sliding transfer of 150 lbs. with a second person present.<br />Position requires use of foot pedals on carts or machines.<br />May be exposed to chemical and hazardous waste as well as blood and body fluids and communicable disease. Therefore, protective clothing and equipment must be worn as necessary.<br />Must have functional speech, vision, hearing, and touch with ability to use fine hand manipulation skills for IV insertion and other procedures/functions.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$37.50 - $56.25<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Advocate Good Samaritan Hospital - 3815 Highland Ave]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>