<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/christopherlam888/workday-scraper</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nursing Unit Secretary PT, Evenings]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://huntingtonhospital.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/HuntingtonHospitalCareers/job/Huntington-Hospital---Pasadena/Nursing-Unit-Secretary-PT--Evenings_R-29584?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>locations</li><li>Huntington Hospital - Pasadena</li><li>time type</li><li>Part time</li><li>posted on</li><li>Posted Today</li><li>job requisition id</li><li>R-29584</li><li>Internal Workers – Please log into your Workday account to apply **</li><li>Huntington Hospital Employee Login</li><li>Compensation Range:</li><li>Anticipated compensation range of $24.00 - $25.80 / Hour depending on qualifications and experience.</li><li>Department:</li><li>Emergency Services</li><li>Expectations:</li><li>Responsible for performing clerical and non-clinical patient duties on inpatient and outpatient units.</li><li>This position may require flexibility of hours.</li></ul><p>EDUCATION:<br />High School Diploma or GED. Equivalency or one year of work related experience.</p><p>EXPERIENCE/TRAINING:<br />Preferred - Two years experience as a unit secretary in applicable patient care area.<br />Preferred - Evidence of having participated in Performance Improvement Models i.e. conferences,  meetings, seminars, councils. <br />Basic computer skills/experience with computerized documentation systems preferred.<br />Knowledge/experience with use of medical terminology.<br />Microsoft Office skills or equivalent.</p><p>SKILLS:<br />Must be willing and able to work in a face paced, frequently changing environment. <br />Must be willing and able to multi-task effectively to accomplish work assignments. <br />Must be able and willing to take direction from a variety of staff members – sometimes with conflicting directions and deadlines.<br />Worker Type:<br />Regular<br />Part time<br />Shift:<br />Evenings</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Huntington Hospital - Pasadena]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Huntington Hospital]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Nursing Director]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Intermountain-Health-Intermountain-Medical-Center/Cardiovascular-Nursing-Director_R144898?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Intermountain Health Intermountain Medical Center<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date: July 14, 2025 (8 days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R144898<br />Job Description:<br />This position provides leadership and operational direction to a designated service line or group of departments at a facility. It involves working with the Chief Nursing Officer and other management to ensure optimal patient care, financial goals, and leadership development. The role has regional accountability or responsibility for multiple departments and typically reports to the Chief Nursing Officer. Job duties are distributed as follows: 20% Tactical (staffing, equipment, employee relations), 50% Operational (budget management, supply acquisition, process improvement, performance evaluations), and 30% Strategic (developing goals, holding employees accountable).<br />Essential Functions<br />Champions the use of available resources to ensure nursing care is efficient, effective, safe, and delivered with compassion, in line with current practice standards.<br />Facilitates collaborative decision-making and upholds professional independence by contributing departmental perspectives to executive decisions and ensuring staff are updated on activities at the executive level.<br />Assists with development, implementation and management of annual capital/operating and personnel (FTE) budget for unit. Provides resources effectively for department managers to meet financial goals of department.<br />Models and fosters an environment of professionalism and employee engagement on the unit.<br />Ensures competent and sufficient number of staff to meet patient care needs, which includes hiring, orientation, retention, and employee satisfaction.<br />Accountable for the implementation of clinical program protocols, and that ongoing monitoring and process improvement occurs to assure goals are achieved.<br />Collaborates with medical director and system colleagues in the development and implementation of clinical program goals.<br />Evaluates staff competency through use of performance reviews and peer reviews.<br />Coordinates performance and compliance with patient safety initiatives, federal, state and other regulatory bodies such as Joint Commission, OSHA, CMS, DOPL, and other unit specific accrediting and certifying bodies.<br />Facilitates use of resources by nursing staff such as nurse practitioners, other expanded role RNs, and other specialty roles.<br />Serves as an exemplary figure for employees within all facets of providing patient care.<br />Monitors and improves patient satisfaction utilizing available service metrics and national benchmarks to develop and implement action plans to achieve desired outcomes.<br />Partners with physicians at the unit level to achieve clinical, operational, and service goals.<br />Supports staff participation in outside community organizations such as volunteer health clinics, health fairs and advisory boards for not-for-profit organizations.<br />Skills<br />Leadership<br />Communication<br />Problem-solving<br />Financial acumen<br />Clinical knowledge<br />Resource management<br />Patient safety<br />Mentorship<br />Community outreach<br />Minimum Qualifications<br />Bachelor’s degree in nursing (BSN) from an accredited institution (degree will be verified).  <br />Current Nursing License to practice as a Registered Nurse in state of practice.  Valid compact licenses must be transferred to the state of practice within 60 days of the start of employment.<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) certification for Healthcare Providers.<br />Leadership/supervisory experience.<br />3 years of management experience and 2 years of clinical experience.<br />Preferred Qualifications<br />Master's degree from an accredited institution (degree will be verified) must be obtained within 4 years of hire.<br />Experience in the area of oversight<br />Specialty Certification<br />Physical Requirements:<br />Physical Requirements<br />Ongoing need for employee to see and read information, documents, monitors, identify equipment and supplies, and be able to assess customer needs.<br />Frequent interactions with providers, colleagues, customers, patients/clients, and visitors that require employee to verbally communicate as well as hear and understand spoken information, needs, and issues quickly and accurately.<br />Manual dexterity of hands and fingers to manipulate complex and delicate equipment with precision and accuracy. This includes frequent computer use for typing, accessing needed information, etc.<br />May have the same physical requirements as those of clinical or patient care jobs, when the leader takes clinical shifts.<br />For roles requiring driving: Expected to drive a vehicle which requires sitting, seeing and reading signs, traffic signals, and other vehicles.<br />With this position, you are eligible to participate in the Annual Pay for Performance (AP4P) Plan. This plan enables Intermountain Health to provide leaders with an additional performance compensation opportunity. The AP4P award opportunities are calculated as a percentage of your base salary. Awards are paid out based on attainment of selected Board-approved goals.<br />Location:<br />Intermountain Health Intermountain Medical Center<br />Work City:<br />Murray<br />Work State:<br />Utah<br />Scheduled Weekly Hours:<br />40<br />The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience. <br />$58.62 - $90.48<br />We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged. <br />Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.<br />Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.<br />At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.<br />All positions subject to close without notice.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Intermountain Health Intermountain Medical Center]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Acute Care Nurse Practitioner or PA, - SW Cardiology]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://memorialhermann.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/external/job/Southwest-Medical-Plaza-2/Advanced-Practice-Provider--Specialty_100145370-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Southwest Medical Plaza 2<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />100145370<br />At Memorial Hermann, we pursue a common goal of delivering high quality, efficient care while creating exceptional experiences for every member of our community. When we say every member of our community, that includes our employees. We know that when our employees feel cared for, heard and valued, they are inspired to create moments that exceed expectations, while prioritizing safety, compassion, personalization and efficiency. If you want to advance your career and contribute to our vision of creating healthier communities, now and for generations to come, we want you to be a part of our team.<br />Job Summary<br />Responsible for providing comprehensive patient care congruent with role and approved population foci (Family/Individual across lifespan, Adult/Gerontology, Neonatal, Pediatrics, Women’s Health/Gender Related, Psychiatric Mental Health) through systemic assessment, diagnosis, treatment, management, and follow up affecting direct patient care.<br />Job Description<br />Minimum Qualifications<br />Nurse Practitioner / Advanced Practice Nurse<br />Education: Graduate of a Nurse Practitioner program approved by the State of Texas. Masters required. May encompass the following specialties:  CRNA, CNM, CNS, CNP. May encompass the following specialties:  CRNA, CNM, CNS, CNP<br />Licenses/Certifications:<br />Licensed to practice professional nursing by the State of Texas<br />Licensure by the State of Texas APRN and eligibility for full prescriptive authority by the State of Texas<br />Certified by a recognized national certification by the State Board of Texas in area of population foci and/or additional specialty recognition beyond the APRN<br />Eligibility for DEA licensure<br />Basic Cardiac Life Certification  or Advanced Cardiac Life Certification<br />Physician Assistant<br />Education: Graduate of a nationally accredited Physician Assistant program;  Masters strongly preferred<br />Licenses/Certifications:<br />Certified by the National Commission on Certification of Physician Assistants, Inc.<br />Licensed by the Texas State Board of Physician Assistant Examiners<br />Eligibility for DEA licensure<br />Basic Cardiac Life Certification  or Advanced Cardiac Life Certification)<br />Experience / Knowledge / Skills:<br />Two (2) years clinical experience preferred in area of intended practice<br />First Assist and/or EVD experience preferred<br />Principal Accountabilities<br />Provides health promotion and the assessment, diagnosis, and management of patient problems which includes the use and prescription of pharmacologic and non-pharmacologic intervention, assessment, triage, and therapeutic management of patient/family needs throughout the disease process and across the health wellness-illness continuum as an integral part of an interdisciplinary team, according to the age/needs of the patient population served.<br />For prescriptive authority, APRN or PA acts under the delegation of a supervising physician, maintaining an active Prescriptive Authority agreement in accordance with regulations and policy.<br />Practices within approved protocols, guidelines, and clinical pathways and evidence based medicine.<br />Transitions between inpatient/outpatient.<br />Directs and evaluates throughput; delegates or provides backup assistance including triage.<br />Ability to float, round to multiple facilities and/or take call (first call).<br />External Ventricular Drain (EVD) Insertion (Mischer Neurosciences only).<br />Provides accurate billing, coding and documentation.<br />Completes medical records and submit charges in a timely manner.<br />Responsible for overall unit performance in collaboration with physicians or other providers.<br />First Assist physicians in performing surgical procedures by providing support as needed.<br />Obtains medical histories; performs physical examinations/ reviews/orders/interprets diagnostic tests and radiographic results; formulates and manages patient treatment plan and outcomes; provides interventions and performs procedures within legal cope and authority that the APRN or PA is approved, delegated to and credentialed to perform including but not limited to incision and drainage, pelvic exams, lesion removal/destruction, suturing, and casting/splinting.<br />Collaborates in the development and evaluation of patient care. Updates clinical guidelines/protocols/pathways; works autonomously and accepts accountability for outcomes; signs orders in accordance with institution and state board requirements; collaborates in research and teaching projects and applies research to practice. <br />Uses interpersonal and verbal communication skills to educate patient/family on care resources; participates in process improvement and multidisciplinary clinical outcome improvement activities utilizing advanced nursing expertise.<br />Ensures safe care to patients, staff and visitors; adheres to all Memorial Hermann policies, procedures, and standards within budgetary specifications including time management, supply management, productivity and quality of service.<br />Promotes individual professional growth and development by meeting requirements for mandatory/continuing education and skills competency; supports department-based goals which contribute to the success of the organization; serves as preceptor, mentor and resource to less experienced staff.<br />Demonstrates commitment to caring for every member of our community by creating compassionate and personalized experiences. Models Memorial Hermann’s service standards by providing safe, caring, personalized and efficient experiences to patients and colleagues.<br />Other duties as assigned.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Southwest Medical Plaza 2]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Memorial Hermann Health System]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Utilization Review Clinician - Behavioral Health]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://centene.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/centene_external/job/Remote-TX/Utilization-Review-Clinician---Behavioral-Health_1576127-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Remote-TX<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />1576127<br />You could be the one who changes everything for our 28 million members as a clinical professional on our Medical Management/Health Services team. Centene is a diversified, national organization offering competitive benefits including a fresh perspective on workplace flexibility.<br /> Required Work Schedule: Wednesday - Saturday (Set Schedule)<br />NOTE: Position requires working EVERY Saturday and rotating holidays<br />Full-time Flexible Hours: 4 days, 10 hours shifts (40 hrs per week)<br />Must be able to work Central Time Zone hours<br />NOTE: Must be fully licensed for the state of Texas via the Texas BHEC if you hold a LPC, LCSW, or LMFT. Registered Nurse can hold Texas State Licensure and/or Compact State Licensure.<br />Position Purpose: Performs a clinical review and assesses care related to mental health and substance abuse. Monitors and determines if level of care and services related to mental health and substance abuse are medically appropriate.<br />Evaluates member’s treatment for mental health and substance abuse before, during, and after services to ensure level of care and services are medically appropriate<br />Performs prior authorization reviews related to mental health and substance abuse to determine medical appropriateness in accordance with regulatory guidelines and criteria<br />Performs concurrent review of behavioral health (BH) inpatient to determine overall health of member, treatment needs, and discharge planning<br />Analyzes BH member data to improve quality and appropriate utilization of services<br />Provides education to providers members and their families regrading BH utilization process<br />Interacts with BH healthcare providers as appropriate to discuss level of care and/or services<br />Engages with medical directors and leadership to improve the quality and efficiency of care<br />Formulates and presents cases in staffing and integrated rounds<br />Performs other duties as assigned<br />Complies with all policies and standards<br />Education/Experience: Requires Graduate of an Accredited School Nursing or Bachelor's degree and 2 – 4 years of related experience.<br /> Requires Graduate of an Accredited School Nursing or Bachelor's degree and 2 – 4 years of related behavioral health or substance abuse or ASAM experience. OR<br />Master’s degree for behavioral health clinicians is required<br />Master's degree AND 2 - 4 years of related behavioral health and/or substance abuse addiction disorders experience is preferred.<br />Clinical knowledge and ability to review and/or assess treatment plans related to mental health and substance abuse is preferred.<br />Knowledge of mental health and substance abuse utilization review process is preferred.<br />Experience working with providers and healthcare teams to review care services related to mental health and substance abuse is preferred.<br />Utilization Review/ Utilization management with behavioral health cases<br />Precertification, Concurrent Review, Discharge reviews for behavioral health<br />Direct in patient Behavioral Health and SUD inpatient hospital experience<br />Managed care knowledge is preferred<br />Working knowledge and experience with the ASAM Criteria and levels of care for Addiction Treatment is preferred<br />Direct BH/SUD inpatient intake assessments experience is preferred<br />Direct work experience in In-Patient Behavioral Health Units, Partial Hospitalization, or Residential Treatment is required<br />License to practice independently, and/or have obtained the state required licensure as outlined by the applicable state required.</p><p>License/Certification:<br />LCSW- License Clinical Social Worker required or<br />LMHC-Licensed Mental Health Counselor required or<br />LPC-Licensed Professional Counselor required or<br />Licensed Marital and Family Therapist (LMFT) required or<br />Licensed Mental Health Professional (LMHP) required or<br />RN - Registered Nurse - State Licensure and/or Compact State Licensure required<br />Pay Range: $26.50 - $47.59 per hour<br />Centene offers a comprehensive benefits package including: competitive pay, health insurance, 401K and stock purchase plans, tuition reimbursement, paid time off plus holidays, and a flexible approach to work with remote, hybrid, field or office work schedules.  Actual pay will be adjusted based on an individual's skills, experience, education, and other job-related factors permitted by law, including full-time or part-time status.  Total compensation may also include additional forms of incentives.  Benefits may be subject to program eligibility.<br />Centene is an equal opportunity employer that is committed to diversity, and values the ways in which we are different. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability, veteran status, or other characteristic protected by applicable law.</p><p>Qualified applicants with arrest or conviction records will be considered in accordance with the LA County Ordinance and the California Fair Chance Act</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote-TX]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Centene Corporation]]></company>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>