<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/christopherlam888/workday-scraper</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse, Cath Lab, PT, 8HR, Days]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://huntingtonhospital.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/HuntingtonHospitalCareers/job/Huntington-Hospital---Pasadena/Registered-Nurse-8-10HR-13_R-28466?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations</p><p>Huntington Hospital - Pasadena</p><p>time type</p><p>Part time</p><p>posted on</p><p>Posted Today</p><p>job requisition id</p><p>R-28466</p><p>Internal Workers – Please log into your Workday account to apply **</p><p>Huntington Hospital Employee Login</p><p><strong>Compensation Range</strong>:</p><p>Anticipated Base compensation rate is in the range of $54.10 - $68.99 / Hour depending on qualifications and experience.</p><p><strong>Department</strong>:</p><p>Cardiac Cath Lab</p><p><strong>Expectations</strong>:</p><p>Responsible for coordination of care to meet identified needs of the patient/family. Supervises the management of patient care utilizing critical thinking and nursing process, discharge planning, resource identification, linking and scheduling patients with required services, monitoring care delivery, advocating for the patient, care planning and evaluating outcomes. Coordinates patient care across the health care continuum, and assists other team members with meeting individual patient needs.</p><p>This position may require flexibility of hours.</p><p>This position requires the ability to take on-call for patients requiring emergency cardiovascular procedures.</p><p><strong>EDUCATION</strong>:<br />Bachelor’s degree (BSN) required.   Associate Degree in Nursing (ADN) will be considered if enrolled in a BSN program with degree completion within 2 years of date of hire or date of transfer to an RN position. Diploma or transcripts on highest degree earned required.</p><p><strong>EXPERIENCE/TRAINING</strong>:<br />Minimum 1 year of current experience in acute care area of expertise/equivalent service area, 2 years preferred. <br />Previous experience in a Cardiac Cath Lab setting preferred.<br />Must challenge and successfully pass the Basic Dysrhythmia course curriculum within 21 days of hire. Basic computer skills/experience with computerized documentation systems required.</p><p><strong>LICENSES/CERTIFICATIONS</strong>:<br />Required:<br />Current unrestricted Registered Nurse (RN) license issued by California Board of Registered Nursing (BRN)<br />Current Basic Life Support Provider (BLS), Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support Provider (ACLS) issued by American Heart Association</p><p><strong>Preferred</strong>:<br />Current Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN) Certification<br />Current Cardiovascular Registered Nurse (CVRN) Certification</p><p><strong>SKILLS</strong>:<br />Knowledge of Basic Dysrhythmia course curriculum <br />Care of the patient receiving Sedation/Analgesia<br />Care of the patient with Hemodynamic monitoring and/or support including IABP<br />Must be willing and able to work in a face paced, frequently changing environment. <br />Must be willing and able to multi-task effectively to accomplish work assignments. <br />Must be able and willing to take direction from a variety of staff members – sometimes with conflicting directions and deadlines.<br />Worker Type:<br />Regular<br />Part time<br />Shift:<br />Days</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Huntington Hospital - Pasadena]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Huntington Hospital]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse, Cardiac Rehab, 8HR, PT, Days]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://huntingtonhospital.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/HuntingtonHospitalCareers/job/Huntington-Hospital---Pasadena/Registered-Nurse-8HR-10-Cardiac-Rehab-Program_R-29187?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations</p><p>Huntington Hospital - Pasadena</p><p>time type</p><p>Part time</p><p>posted on</p><p>Posted Today</p><p>job requisition id</p><p>R-29187</p><p>Internal Workers – Please log into your Workday account to apply **</p><p>Huntington Hospital Employee Login</p><p><strong>Compensation Range</strong>:</p><p>Anticipated Base compensation rate is in the range of $52.67 - $67.16 / Hour depending on qualifications and experience.</p><p><strong>Department</strong>:</p><p>Cardiac Rehab Program</p><p><strong>Expectations</strong>:</p><p>Responsible for coordination of care to meet identified needs of the patient/family. Supervises the management of patient care utilizing critical thinking and nursing process, discharge planning, resource identification, linking and scheduling patients with required services, monitoring care delivery, advocating for the patient, care planning and evaluating outcomes. Coordinates patient care across the health care continuum, and assists other team members with meeting individual patient needs. This position may require flexibility of hours.</p><p><strong>EDUCATION</strong>:<br />Bachelor’s degree (BSN) required.   Associate Degree in Nursing (ADN) will be considered if enrolled in a BSN program with degree completion within 2 years of date of hire or date of transfer to an RN position. Diploma or transcripts on highest degree earned required.</p><p><strong>EXPERIENCE/TRAINING</strong>:<br />Minimum 1 year of current experience in acute care area of expertise/equivalent service area, 2 years preferred. Experience in a cardiac rehab setting, preferred. <br />Must challenge and successfully pass the Basic Dysrhythmia course curriculum within 21 days of hire. Basic computer skills/experience with computerized documentation systems required.</p><p><strong>LICENSES/CERTIFICATIONS</strong>:<br />Required:<br />Current unrestricted Registered Nurse (RN) license issued by  California Board of Registered Nursing (BRN)<br />Current Basic Life Support Provider (BLS), Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support Provider (ACLS) issued by American Heart Association</p><p><strong>Preferred</strong>:<br />Current unrestricted Registered Nurse-Board Certified (RN-BC) or related certification</p><p><strong>SKILLS</strong>:</p><p>Demonstrates competent knowledge base in pathophysiology of the cardio vascular patient through appropriate</p><p>Assessment</p><p>Critical thinking skills</p><p>Rehab Plan of Care</p><p>Competent in Dysrhythmia recognition and treatment.</p><p><strong>Worker Type</strong>:</p><p>Regular</p><p>Part time</p><p><strong>Shift</strong>:</p><p>Days</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Huntington Hospital - Pasadena]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Huntington Hospital]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse Clinical Specialist - Operating Room - Berkeley Hospital]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://easyservice.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/RoperStFrancisHealthcare/job/Summerville-SC/Registered-Nurse-Clinical-Specialist---Operating-Room---Berkeley-Hospital_R239596?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations</p><p>Summerville, SC</p><p>time type</p><p>Full time</p><p>posted on</p><p>Posted Today</p><p>job requisition id</p><p>R239596</p><p>Thank you for considering a career at Roper St. Francis Healthcare!</p><p><strong>Scheduled Weekly Hours</strong>:</p><p></p><p><strong>Work Shift</strong>:</p><p>Days (United States of America)</p><p><strong>Roper St. Francis Berkeley Hospital</strong>: Expanding to Serve More</p><p>Our community is growing and so are we! Roper St. Francis Berkeley Hospital is doubling its bed capacity as part of a major expansion, set for completion in early 2026.</p><p>This growth will bring expanded services to emergency, cardiology, orthopedics, obstetrics, neurology, inpatient dialysis and additional specialties in our Medical Office Building.</p><p>We are proud to be a trusted place of hope, healing and support for our neighbors, families and friends. Ready to make a difference? Let’s build something together.</p><p><strong>Position Details</strong>: Must have Operating Room Experience / Scrub Nurse / Circulator.</p><p><strong>Monday through Friday 8 am to 4</strong>:30 pm</p><p>Position starts June 2025</p><p>Job Description</p><p>Primary Function/General Purpose of Position</p><p>The Clinical Nurse Specialist (CNS) is a registered nurse with clinical expertise within a selected area of nursing. The CNS functions as an educator, clinical expert, consultant, and researcher for the nursing staff.  Collaborates with nursing leaders and other interdisciplinary staff to achieve patient outcomes. Leads, facilitates, and manages day-to-day clinical improvement activities related to nursing practice and process.  Work function is targeted toward achieving quality, cost-effective evidenced based outcomes.  Goals for targeted populations are attained through the synthesis of comparative clinical and aggregate data, development and application of standard indicators, and design and development of innovative programs.</p><p>Essential Job Functions</p><p>Demonstrates advanced, specialized knowledge of nursing practice issues related to clinical specialty</p><p>Leverages data to identify trends; shares measures of success and areas of opportunity with the interprofessional team</p><p>Collaborate with the interprofessional team and clinical unit leadership to identify areas of opportunity and construct improvement plans</p><p>Facilitates change and collaborates with the healthcare team to identify gaps, barriers, and practice improvement</p><p>Support orientation, competency, and continuing education of staff in the clinical environment</p><p>Acts as a patient safety advocate by participating in ongoing quality improvement in the hospital.  Incorporates the professional practice model into care delivery.</p><p>Analyzes the practice setting in a continuous improvement framework</p><p>Establishes and maintains standards of practice at the client, unit, hospital, corporate, community and national levels</p><p>Provides innovative and collaborative leadership in professional and clinical practice by role modeling, mentoring, and serving as a clinical consultant</p><p>Initiates and participates in strategic planning at all levels of the health care system</p><p>Facilitates and interprets research, incorporating appropriate findings into practice</p><p>Coordinates, facilitates, provides and evaluates patient, staff and community education programs</p><p>The integration of ethical/legal concepts into the practice of self and others.</p><p>This document is not an exhaustive list of all responsibilities, skills, duties, requirements, or working conditions associated with the job. Employees may be required to perform other job-related duties as required by their supervisor, subject to reasonable accommodation.</p><p>Licensing/Certification</p><p>Must be currently licensed as an Advanced Practice Nurse/Clinical Nurse Specialist in the state of practice or is eligible to initiate the application process (required)</p><p>Must maintain current Basic Life Support (BLS) – American Heart Association (required)</p><p>Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support (ACLS) – American Heart Association (preferred)</p><p>Education</p><p>Master’s prepared Registered Nurse from an accredited school of nursing (required)</p><p>Continuing Education (CE), Continuing Education Units (CEU), Credit Hours (CH) (required)</p><p>Work Experience</p><p>Minimum of 5 years clinical experience (required)</p><p>Clinical experience in health care research, data acquisition and statistical analysis (preferred)</p><p>years of experience in application of performance improvement methods (preferred)</p><p>Oral/written skills and previous work experience communicating complex theoretical and technical concepts to healthcare members, developing, and presenting formal educational programs, and effective collaboration with other healthcare members (required)</p><p>Demonstrated group facilitation, problem solving, and analytical skills (required)</p><p>Training</p><p>Training in LEAN/Six Sigma process (preferred)</p><p>Word processing, spreadsheet, and presentation program abilities (preferred)</p><p>EPIC Electronic Health Record (preferred)</p><p>Language</p><p>None</p><p>Patient Population</p><p>Demonstrates the knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patients served on his or her assigned unit.</p><p>Demonstrates knowledge of the principles of growth and development of the life span and possesses the ability to assess data reflective of the patient's status and interprets the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to his or her age, specific needs and to provide the care needed as described in departmental policies and procedures.</p><p>Adolescents (13-17 years)</p><p>Adults (18-64 years)</p><p>Geriatrics (65 years and older)</p><p>Working Conditions</p><p>Periods of high stress and fluctuating workloads may occur.</p><p>Long-distance or air travel as needed- not to exceed 10% travel.</p><p>General office environment.</p><p>May be exposed to high noise levels and bright lights.</p><p>May be exposed to physical altercations and verbal abuse.</p><p>May be exposed to limited hazardous substances or body fluids.*</p><p>May be required to use physical restraints.</p><p>May be exposed to human blood and other potentially infectious materials.*</p><p>May be exposed to adverse weather conditions; cold, hot, dust, wind, etc.</p><p>May have periods of constant interruptions.</p><p>Required to car travel to off-site locations, occasionally in adverse weather conditions.</p><p>Prolonged periods of working alone.</p><p>Physical Requirements</p><p>Physical Demands</p><p>Frequency                                             0%                  1-33%                 34-66%                 67-100%</p><p>Lifting/ Carrying (0-50 lbs.)                                             x</p><p>Lifting/ Carrying (50-100 lbs.)                                         x</p><p>Push/ Pull (0-50 lbs.)                                                        x</p><p>Push/ Pull (50-100 lbs.)                                                    x</p><p>Stoop, Kneel                                                                                                        x</p><p>Crawling                                                                              x</p><p>Climbing                                                                               x</p><p>Balance                                                                                                                x</p><p>Bending                                                                               x</p><p>Work Position</p><p>Frequency                                               0%                    1-33                     34-66%                 67-100%</p><p>Sitting                                                                                     x</p><p>Walking                                                                                                                 x</p><p>Standing                                                                                                                x</p><p>Additional Physical Requirements/Hazards</p><p>Physical Requirements</p><p>Manual dexterity (eye/hand coordination)</p><p>Perform shift work</p><p>Maneuver weight of patients</p><p>Hear alarms/telephone/audio recordings</p><p>Reach above shoulder</p><p>Repetitive arm/hand movements</p><p>Finger Dexterity</p><p>Color Vision</p><p>Acuity – far</p><p>Acuity – near</p><p>Hazards</p><p>Depth perception</p><p>Use of Latex products</p><p>Exposure to toxic/caustic/chemicals/detergents</p><p>Exposure to moving mechanical parts</p><p>Exposure to dust/fumes</p><p>Exposure to potential electrical shock</p><p>Exposure to x ray/electromagnetic energy</p><p>Exposure to high pitched noises</p><p>Gaseous risk exposure</p><p>Skills</p><p>Participate in BLS and/or ACLS events occurring within the acute care setting</p><p>Monitor patient conditions during treatment and document</p><p>Administer medications if needed and document</p><p>Inform medical professionals regarding patient conditions and care</p><p>Record patient medical histories</p><p>Budgeting & Financial Acumen</p><p>Evaluate employee performance during evaluation of competencies</p><p>Analyzing data or information</p><p>Prepare and deliver presentations for executive level/mid-level leaders/frontline associate audiences</p><p>Attention to detail</p><p>Acceptance of authority</p><p>Critical thinking</p><p>Communication with family members</p><p>Communication with patients</p><p>Teamwork</p><p>Conflict resolution</p><p>Active listening</p><p>Relationship building</p><p>Self-motivated to function autonomously in work</p><p>Roper St. Francis Healthcare is an equal opportunity employer.</p><p><strong>Many of our opportunities reward* your hard work with</strong>:</p><p>Comprehensive, affordable medical, dental and vision plans</p><p>Prescription drug coverage</p><p>Flexible spending accounts</p><p>Life insurance w/AD&D</p><p>Employer contributions to retirement savings plan when eligible</p><p>Paid time off</p><p>Educational Assistance</p><p>And much more</p><p>Benefits offerings vary according to employment status.</p><p><strong>Department</strong>:</p><p>Admin - Perioperative Service - Roper St Francis Healthcare</p><p>It is our policy to abide by all Federal and State laws, as well as, the requirements of 41 CFR 60-1.4(a), 60-300.5(a) and 60-741.5(a). Accordingly, all applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, national origin, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, genetic information, or protected veteran status, and will not be discriminated against on the basis of disability. If you are an individual with a disability and would like to request a reasonable accommodation as part of the employment selection process, please contact The Talent Acquisition Team at recruitment@RSFH.com.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Summerville, SC]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Roper St. Francis Healthcare (EasyService)]]></company>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>