<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/christopherlam888/workday-scraper</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) - Mental Health Emergency Department (Full Time - Nights)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://choc.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Careers/job/Main-Campus---Orange/Registered-Nurse--RN----Mental-Health-Emergency-Department--Full-Time---Nights-_R-29292?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Main Campus - Orange<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R-29292<br />Work Location<br />Orange, California</p><ul><li>Work Shift</li><li>Night – 12hrs (United States of America)</li><li>Why CHOC?</li><li>At CHOC, we strive to be the leading destination of children’s health by providing exceptional and innovative care. We are responsible for the overall health of our community’s pediatric population in our hospitals, clinics, and practices. And because of our breadth of care, your career at CHOC can be as diverse and fulfilling as you determine. CHOC’s compensation structure, benefits offerings, and career development programs are geared to helping you achieve your professional and personal goals. Apply now to see where your career at CHOC can take you.</li><li>Job Summary</li><li>The Clinical Nurse II MHU is responsible for the planning and delivery of family-centered patient care utilizing the nursing process: assessment, diagnosis, planning, implementation, and evaluation. Is responsible for directing and coordinating nursing care for patients based on established clinical and behavioral health nursing and practice standards. Will collaborate with patient/ family and other professional disciplines. This role creates a partnership to ensure effective and efficient patient care delivery for the achievement of mutually desired patient outcomes. Additionally, the Clinical Nurse II supports the organization’s vision and mission while promoting and providing excellence in nursing care.</li><li>Pay Range</li><li>Minimum $54.77 Midpoint $71.20 Maximum $87.63</li><li>Rate of pay is determined by various factors, including but not limited to knowledge, skills, competencies, experience, education, as well as position requirements.</li><li>Experience</li><li>Required: Minimum of one (1) year of acute care nursing experience OR nine (9) months of acute care nursing experience in a pediatric setting.</li><li>Preferred: One (1) year acute care nursing in a pediatric inpatient hospital.</li></ul><ul><li>Education</li><li>Required: Graduation from an accredited school of Registered Nursing; Bachelor of Science degree in Nursing (BSN) required within two (2) years of hire..</li></ul><ul><li>Training</li><li>Required: None required.</li></ul><ul><li>Specialized Skills</li><li>Required: Knowledge of and ability to provide appropriate family-centered patient care based upon age appropriateness and cultural and spiritual needs; excellent customer satisfaction skills; effective communication skills; ability to prioritize and complete duties in a timely and organized manner. Ability to work collaboratively and in a positive manner with others. Ability to prepare timely and accurate documentation and reports. Ability to perform work according to CHOC policies and procedures, professional standards of care, and applicable laws. Demonstrate flexibility and creativity in response to unexpected changes in work load/staffing. Ability to set goals and judge results in accordance with the highest standards; care with sensitivity and respect; advance care through development of new ideas and technology; promote teamwork to achieve CHOC’s mission; and understand and exceed customer expectations.</li><li>Preferred: Bilingual</li></ul><ul><li>Licensure</li><li>Required: Comprehensive Crisis Management (CCM) – Must be obtained before starting patient care and must be completed annually through CHOC Children's; Basic Life Support (BLS); Registered Nurse (RN) - CA; Effective 10/04/2020, Lanterman-Petris-Short (LPS) designation is required within 6 months of hire/transfer.</li><li>Preferred: Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS); Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN).</li><li>Work Environments - Functional Demand:</li><li>Light -  Moderate energy level Lift and carry 25-35 lbs. Push/pull 50-100 lbs. (ie. empty bed, stretcher).</li><li>Physical Activity Requirements:</li><li>Bending, Carry Objects, Climbing, Keyboard use/repetitive motion, Pinching/fine motor activities, Push/Pull, Reaching forward, Reaching overhead, Sitting, Squat/kneel/crawl (Squad & Knee), Standing, Talk or hear, Taste or smell, Twisting, Walking, Wrist position deviation</li><li>Physical Activity Lifting</li><li>Lifting (Floor to waist level) - Constant 67 or more%, Lifting (Floor to waist level) - Frequent  36-66%, Lifting (Floor to waist level) - Occasional 0-35%, Lifting (Waist level and above) - Constant 67 or more%, Lifting (Waist level and above) - Frequent 36-66%, Lifting (Waist level and above) - Occasional 0-35%</li><li>Sensory Requirements:</li><li>Color Discrimination, Depth Perception, Far Vision, Hearing, Near Vision</li><li>Environment Requirements:</li><li>Airborn Communicable Disease, Bloodborne Pathogens, Chemical, Dust Particular Matter, Extreme Noise Levels, Extreme Temperatures, Radiation, Uneven Surfaces or Elevations</li><li>Non-Discrimination Statement:</li><li>CHOC does not discriminate on the basis of age, race, color, religion, national origin, ancestry, marital status, genetic information, disability, sex, gender (including pregnancy, breastfeeding, childbirth, lactation or related medical conditions), gender identity or expression, medical condition, sexual orientation, veteran status, military or uniformed service member status, or other protected characteristics in accordance with state and federal laws. CHOC will consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories, in accordance with the Fair Chance Initiative for Hiring.</li><li>We encourage individuals from all backgrounds to apply for positions at CHOC, even if your experience doesn’t align perfectly with the listed qualifications for a particular role, as your unique experience may be a great addition to our culture for another one of our opportunities.</li><li>If you desire support or accommodations throughout the Talent Acquisition process, please inform your Talent Acquisition Partner.</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Main Campus - Orange]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Children’s Hospital of Orange County (CHOC)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Trauma Nurse Coordinator]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Intermountain-Health-LDS-Hospital/Trauma-Nurse-Coordinator_R140405?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Intermountain Health LDS Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date: June 1, 2025 (13 days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R140405<br />Job Description:<br />The Specialty Care Coordinator II position exists to ensure compliance to state, national and other regulatory agency requirements for disease specific programs and disease specific centers of excellence. The Specialty Care Coordinator II in collaboration with the Medical Director ensures optimal patient care using evidence based, clinical best practice models, appropriate staffing and technologies and continuous process improvement measures. The Specialty Care Coordinator II is typically based at a facility, but may have oversight for relevant processes at referring facilities.<br />Position Details<br />·       Benefits Eligible: Yes<br />·       Shift Details: Full time, 40 hours/week, Monday - Friday, occasional evening or weekend shift as business needs<br />·       Department: Trauma<br />·       Primary Location: LDS Hospital<br />·       Additional Details: Previous trauma or stroke experience preferred. Prior education and/or leadership experience preferred. 5 years of applicable nursing experience required. <br />Scope</p><p>The Specialty Care Coordinator II oversees a program and may have direct supervision of staff.</p><p>Job Essentials</p><ul><li>Clinical Activities: Coordinates care across the continuum, including planning and implementing of clinical protocols and practice management guidelines, monitoring care, and serving as an expert resource for clinical practice. Oversees the development and review of care protocols, policies and procedures that promote an organized and effective program.</li><li>Physician Engagement: Engages with providers at the service line level to achieve clinical, operational, and service goals as appropriate. Acts as a resource and primary contact for providers in the department. Enhances physician productivity by proactively identifying and removing operations barriers and responds to providers' operational needs.</li><li>Education Responsibilities: Facilitates the development and implementation of educational programs including pre-hospital care provider agencies, hospital nursing and physician continuing education programs. Facilitates case review, standardizing practice guidelines, and directs community education and prevention programs. Participates in patient education and community activities to promote prevention of disease and early treatment as applicable.</li><li>Performance Improvement: Provides ongoing evaluation of the effectiveness and efficiency of the program. Responsible for the development and maintenance of the process improvement program. Monitors clinical outcomes and system issues related to quality of care. Develops quality filters and audits, and helps to outline corrective actions as applicable. Is involved in patient experience efforts and monitors patient perception of the quality of care delivered.</li><li>In conjunction with the Medical Director, plans, coordinates and conducts program meetings such as Executive Leadership, Mortality and Morbidity, Grand Rounds and Multi-disciplinary Committees. Sees that agendas, attendance, records/minutes and follow up are prompt and accurate.</li><li>Provides local oversight of the disease specific registry and data management process. Facilitates sharing of registry data with care teams.</li><li>Supports clinical program, facility and system goals and initiatives. Attends and actively participates in system level meetings representing the facility. Presents/reports on progress of the program to directors, administrators and leadership boards as assigned.</li><li>Ensures compliance to regulatory agency guidelines, credentialing bodies and all applicable state and federal regulations related to the applicable disease specific care.</li><li>Depending on facility may provide managerial oversight for program personnel including data registrars, advanced practice clinicians, research associates, program billing staff and secretarial support. Supervisory duties may include hiring, orientation, staffing, payroll, annual performance evaluation and wage adjust.</li><li>Budgetary Responsibilities: Assists in annual strategic planning, operational and capital budgetary planning. Partners with billing and revenue departments in monitoring billing compliance and revenue production. Adheres to staffing and operational budgets as applicable. Completes and submits budget reports as required by facility.</li><li>Consultant/Liaison: Stabilizes the complex network of many disciplines that work in concert to provide high quality care, serving as an internal resource for staff in all departments, and acting as an extended liaison for Emergency Medical Services agencies, the community and the nation. Is involved in the development and improvement of care at the community, state and national levels.</li><li>Minimum Qualifications</li></ul><ul><li>RN license in state of practice.</li><li>and -</li><li>RNs hired or promoted into this role need to have or obtain their BSN within three years of hire or promotion.</li><li>and -</li><li>BLS certification for healthcare providers.</li></ul><ul><li>Five years of applicable nursing experience.</li><li>and -</li><li>Demonstration of expertise in disease specific care.</li><li>and -</li><li>Demonstrated experience with quality management programs including registry data collection. Computer skills including the creation of graphs, tables, and trend reports.</li><li>and -</li><li>Demonstrated critical thinking skills, data organization, management, and analysis skills.</li><li>and -</li><li>Experience in educational program development.</li><li>and -</li><li>Experience in process development including detailed corrective action plans which demonstrate comprehensive follow up and loop closure.</li><li>and -</li><li>Excellent verbal and written communication skills.</li><li>and -</li><li>Well-developed interpersonal skills with the ability to develop excellent working relationships with physicians and ancillary departments.</li><li>Preferred Qualifications</li></ul><ul><li>Bachelor's degree in Nursing (BSN). Education must be obtained from an accredited institution. Degree will be verified.</li><li>Master's degree.</li><li>Physical Requirements:</li><li>Ongoing need for employee to see and read information, labels, monitors, identify equipment and supplies, and be able to assess patient needs.</li><li>and -</li><li>Frequent interactions with patient care providers, patients, and visitors that require employee to verbally communicate as well as hear and understand spoken information, alarms, needs, and issues quickly and accurately, particularly during emergency situations.</li><li>and -</li><li>Manual dexterity of hands and fingers to manipulate complex and delicate equipment with precision and accuracy. This includes frequent computer use and typing for documenting patient care, accessing needed information, etc.</li><li>Location:</li><li>Intermountain Health LDS Hospital</li><li>Work City:</li><li>Salt Lake City</li><li>Work State:</li><li>Utah</li><li>Scheduled Weekly Hours:</li><li></li><li>The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience.</li><li>$43.98 - $63.79</li><li>We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged.</li><li>Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.</li><li>Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.</li><li>At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.</li><li>All positions subject to close without notice.</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Intermountain Health LDS Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse Ambulatory (FT-Day, 40hrs/week) - Vascular Practice - Abington, PA]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://jeffersonhealth.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/ThomasJeffersonExternal/job/Montgomery-County-PA/Registered-Nurse-Ambulatory--FT-Day--40hrs-week----Vascular-Practice---Abington--PA_REQ-0009481-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>locations</li><li>Montgomery County, PA</li><li>time type</li><li>Full time</li><li>posted on</li><li>Posted Today</li><li>job requisition id</li><li>REQ-0009481</li><li>Job Details</li><li>With a commitment to patient- and family-centered care, the professional nurse uses the nursing process in ways that values the uniqueness of each individual and addresses the physical, psychological, emotional, and social needs of the diversity of patients served by Jefferson Health Primary Care.  As an integral member of the of the primary care clinical team, the primary care nurse effectively collaborates with providers and support staff and provides clinical nursing interventions. S/he communicates effectively and respectfully with patients to address individualized needs and priorities of patients that are consistent with their cultural beliefs and values.  Must maintain a current nursing license in the state of practice.</li><li>Integrates Evidence-Based Practice, clinical expertise, patients, their family/designated care partner(s) preferences and cultural beliefs and values for delivery of optimal healthcare</li><li>Collaborates and communicates with primary care providers regarding patient care and management; supports efficient and timely communication between primary care providers and specialists.</li><li>Supports implementation of clinical care pathways for common primary care conditions and participates actively in quality improvement opportunities</li><li>Utilizes evidence-based ambulatory care nursing interventions during clinical visits, telephone encounters, and electronic communication</li><li>Provides patient, their family/designated care partner(s) education for preventive care, chronic disease management, and medication management, and management of common illnesses treated in the primary care setting</li><li>Documents all patient and their family/designated care partner(s) interactions and clinical care in electronic medical record (EMR) and nursing care given according to organizational standards and in compliance with applicable regulations.</li><li>Performs care coordination for patients i.e. abnormal results, triage, RN verification of vaccinations and other injections, management of in-baskets. (prior authorizations and forms)</li><li>Oversees clinical care essential to the assessment, promotion, maintenance and restoration of patients’ health and wellness.</li><li>Minimizes risk of harm to patient, their family/designated care partner(s) by following established nursing practices and protocols</li><li>Uses information technology to communicate, manage knowledge, and mitigate errors</li><li>Uses data to monitor the outcomes of care processes and support ethical decision making; uses improvement methods to design and test changes to continuously improve the quality and safety of patient care</li><li>Functions effectively within primary care inter-professional teams, fostering open communication, mutual respect, and shared decision-making to achieve quality patient care.</li><li>Recognizes patient and their family/designated care partner(s) in providing safe, compassionate and coordinated care based on respect for patient's preferences, priorities, needs, and cultural beliefs and values.</li><li>Creates an environment of belonging and inclusion and demonstrates skills in problem solving and conflict resolution.</li><li>Demonstrates a commitment to learning and seeks opportunities for continued professional growth and development.</li><li>Actively participates in team huddles/assemblies to provide announcements and clinical operations updates</li><li>Demonstrates willingness to give and receive feedback and integrates appropriate changes into practice.</li><li>Job Description</li><li>Minimum Education and Experience Requirements:</li><li>EDUCATION:</li><li>Graduate of an accredited school of nursing required; BSN or completion of BSN or appropriate advanced degree within 3 years of hire strongly preferred.</li><li>AND</li><li>EXPERIENCE:</li><li>+ years’ experience as a Nurse, in an ambulatory setting preferred</li><li>Minimum Certifications, Registration or License Requirements:</li><li>Current RN licensure in state of practice; BLS required based on organizational guidelines/policies</li><li>Additional Information:</li><li>Encouraged to obtain ambulatory care nursing certification</li><li>Expected to participate in or support quality, evidence-based practice and research of nursing governance initiatives</li><li>Work Shift</li><li>Workday Day (United States of America)</li><li>Worker Sub Type</li><li>Regular</li><li>Primary Location Address</li><li>Old York Road, Abington, Pennsylvania, United States of America</li><li>Nationally ranked, Jefferson, which is principally located in the greater Philadelphia region, Lehigh Valley and Northeastern Pennsylvania and southern New Jersey, is reimagining health care and higher education to create unparalleled value. Jefferson is more than 65,000 people strong, dedicated to providing the highest-quality, compassionate clinical care for patients; making our communities healthier and stronger; preparing tomorrow's professional leaders for 21st-century careers; and creating new knowledge through basic/programmatic, clinical and applied research. Thomas Jefferson University, home of Sidney Kimmel Medical College, Jefferson College of Nursing, and the Kanbar College of Design, Engineering and Commerce, dates back to 1824 and today comprises 10 colleges and three schools offering 200+ undergraduate and graduate programs to more than 8,300 students. Jefferson Health, nationally ranked as one of the top 15 not-for-profit health care systems in the country and the largest provider in the Philadelphia and Lehigh Valley areas, serves patients through millions of encounters each year at 32 hospitals campuses and more than 700 outpatient and urgent care locations throughout the region. Jefferson Health Plans is a not-for-profit managed health care organization providing a broad range of health coverage options in Pennsylvania and New Jersey for more than 35 years.</li><li>Jefferson is committed to providing equal educa­tional and employment opportunities for all persons without regard to age, race, color, religion, creed, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, marital status, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, military status, veteran status, handicap or disability or any other protected group or status.</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Montgomery County, PA]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Jefferson Health]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patient Care Associate- Neonatal ICU (full time 36 hrs/week NIGHTS)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://albanymed.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Albany_Med/job/43-New-Scotland-Avenue-Albany-NY-12208/Patient-Care-Associate--Neonatal-ICU--full-time-36-hrs-week-NIGHTS-_64950?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />43 New Scotland Avenue Albany, NY 12208<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />64950<br />Department/Unit:<br />Neonatal ICU-B4<br />Work Shift:<br />Night (United States of America)<br />Salary Range:<br />The Patient Care Assistant (PCA) will work under the direction of the Registered Nurse. During the assigned work period, PCAs will collect patient data, complete personal care of the patient, perform point of care testing such as whole blood glucose, turn & position and/or mobilize patients, and assist with caring for the needs of assigned patients with a focus on progress toward discharge, including during transitions within the acute care stay. The PCA is trained to perform technical procedures such as blood draw and electrocardiography. The Patient Care Assistant promotes the availability of resources for patient care through collaboration with Material's Coordinators for use, stocking, and storage of supplies.<br />The Patient Care Assistant participates in the creation and maintenance of a clean, orderly, and safe environment of care. PCAs may also be asked to provide the service of activity companion for patients requiring 11 observation.</p><p>The Patient Care Assistant is responsible for assisting in the delivery of patient care provided by the caregiving team. They assures that competent, compassionate patient care is uniformly provided to customers.</p><p>Essential Duties and Responsibilities<br />Collects pertinent data and information relative to the patient’s health or situation, including vital signs, height and weight, and food and fluid intake and output.<br />Reports abnormal findings to the RN and patient care team.<br />Participates in care planning and the nursing report process.<br />Incorporates patient/family rights to participate in decision making about their care<br />Utilizes standardized techniques for keeping patients and families informed.<br />Provides personal care to patients including bathing, oral care, and skin care<br />Assists the patient with eating and hydration, grooming, dressing, and toileting.<br />Incorporates safe patient handling into basic restorative care such as ambulation, range of motion and use of assistive and prosthetic devices.<br />Employs strategies to promote a clean, orderly, and safe environment.<br />Demonstrates standard and transmission, based precautions and infection control techniques.<br />Provides details related to patient progress toward the achievement of goals and outcomes to the RN.<br />Documents all care in the patient record.</p><p>Qualifications<br />High School Diploma/G.E.D. or equivalent  - required <br />less than 1 year experience in a health care setting or completion of certified nurse assistant course  - preferred <br /> experience as a paramedic, emergency technician   - preferred <br />Basic knowledge of medical terminology (Medium proficiency)<br />Honest, punctual, and performs the job in adherence to the highest standards of ethical conduct as defined by Albany Medical Center and the tenets of the profession. <br />Ability to communicate cooperatively and effectively with patients, family members, employees and others.</p><p>Physical Demands<br />Standing - Constantly <br />Walking - Constantly <br />Sitting - Rarely <br />Lifting - Frequently <br />Carrying - Frequently <br />Pushing - Occasionally <br />Pulling - Occasionally <br />Climbing - Occasionally <br />Balancing - Occasionally <br />Stooping - Frequently <br />Kneeling - Frequently <br />Crouching - Frequently <br />Crawling - Occasionally <br />Reaching - Frequently <br />Handling - Frequently <br />Grasping - Frequently <br />Feeling - Constantly <br />Talking - Constantly <br />Hearing - Constantly <br />Repetitive Motions - Constantly <br />Eye/Hand/Foot Coordination - Constantly</p><p>Thank you for your interest in Albany Medical Center!</p><p>Albany Medical Center is an equal opportunity employer.</p><p>This role may require access to information considered sensitive to Albany Medical Center, its patients, affiliates, and partners, including but not limited to HIPAA Protected Health Information and other information regulated by Federal and New York State statutes. Workforce members are expected to ensure that:<br />Access to information is based on a “need to know” and is the minimum necessary to properly perform assigned duties. Use or disclosure shall not exceed the minimum amount of information needed to accomplish an intended purpose. Reasonable efforts, consistent with Albany Medical Center policies and standards, shall be made to ensure that information is adequately protected from unauthorized access and modification.<br />Thank you for your interest in Albany Medical Center!<br />Albany Medical is an equal opportunity employer.<br />This role may require access to information considered sensitive to Albany Medical Center, its patients, affiliates, and partners, including but not limited to HIPAA Protected Health Information and other information regulated by Federal and New York State statutes. Workforce members are expected to ensure that:<br />Access to information is based on a “need to know” and is the minimum necessary to properly perform assigned duties. Use or disclosure shall not exceed the minimum amount of information needed to accomplish an intended purpose. Reasonable efforts, consistent with Albany Med Center policies and standards, shall be made to ensure that information is adequately protected from unauthorized access and modification.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[43 New Scotland Avenue Albany, NY 12208]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Albany Medical Center]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[HOUSEKEEPING; PT, 1st shift]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-BayCare-Medical-Center---2845-Greenbrier-Rd/HOUSEKEEPING--PT--1st-shift_R150081?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora BayCare Medical Center - 2845 Greenbrier Rd<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R150081<br />Department:<br />11906 BayCare Leased Employees - Environmental Services<br />Status: <br />Part time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />20<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />HOURS: 7:00 am - 3:30 pm, including every other weekend and rotating holidays.<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Cleans patient care areas, surgical areas, public/private restrooms, conference rooms, lobbies, offices, elevators, and stairwells.<br />Cleans all environmental surfaces including ceilings and vents, walls, doors, furniture, beds, bathroom fixtures, and windows. Assists in cleaning emergency spills as requested.<br />Dusts and damp mops floors in patient and exam rooms, corridors, stairwells, restrooms, and other areas of the facility.<br />Replaces cubicle and window coverings.<br />Gathers and disposes recyclables, trash, and medical waste. Collects hazardous trash following established infection control guidelines.<br />Sorts, stocks and delivers linens. Gathers and prepares soiled linen for transportation.<br />Cleans and prepares dismissal and transfer units and certain equipment used in the care of patients and distributes non-medical supplies to specific areas.<br />Fills and cleans supply dispensers.<br />Inventories linens, cleaning supplies and paper supplies and orders additional in a timely and cost effective manner. Keeps housekeeping closet organized and clean.<br />Reports any mechanical failures or unsafe conditions to the supervisor.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />None Required.</p><p>Education Required:<br />No Formal Education.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />No experience required.</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Ability to follow and understand oral and written instructions and communicate with others.<br />Ability to work alone and to understand the physical arrangements of the facilities.<br />Performs tasks without disrupting operations of the doctors, nurses, patients, public, and other staff.<br />Ability to set priorities, be aware of and follow department policies and procedures in all situations.<br />Basic computer skills.<br />Excellent customer service skills.</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 35 lbs. from floor to a maximum 5 ft.<br />lift and carry up to 20 lbs. at waist height a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 50 lbs. of force.<br />Must be able to bend, stoop, kneel, reach above shoulders, and crawl to complete tasks. <br />Must also be able to push/pull/drag equipment such as hospital beds, and lift items weighing up to 50 lbs.<br />Must be able to be on feet the majority of the time with both walking/standing throughout the shift.<br />Must have ability to wear protective clothing as will be exposed to strong germicidal solutions, cleaning chemicals, temperature changes, soiled linen, infectious waste (blood and body fluids). Requires that incumbent be familiar with policies on handling infectious and hazardous waste.<br />Must have ability to operate vacuum cleaners, mopping equipment, buffer or burnisher, automatic scrubber, up to six-foot stepladder, and other cleaning tools.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job, including telephones, zone phones, and pagers.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$18.50 - $27.75<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora BayCare Medical Center - 2845 Greenbrier Rd]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[HOUSEKEEPING; PT, 1st shift]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-BayCare-Medical-Center---2845-Greenbrier-Rd/HOUSEKEEPING--PT--1st-shift_R152649?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora BayCare Medical Center - 2845 Greenbrier Rd<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R152649<br />Department:<br />11906 BayCare Leased Employees - Environmental Services<br />Status: <br />Part time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />20<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Hours: 7:00 am - 3:30 pm, including every other weekend, some holidays.<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Cleans patient care areas, surgical areas, public/private restrooms, conference rooms, lobbies, offices, elevators, and stairwells.<br />Cleans all environmental surfaces including ceilings and vents, walls, doors, furniture, beds, bathroom fixtures, and windows. Assists in cleaning emergency spills as requested.<br />Dusts and damp mops floors in patient and exam rooms, corridors, stairwells, restrooms, and other areas of the facility.<br />Replaces cubicle and window coverings.<br />Gathers and disposes recyclables, trash, and medical waste. Collects hazardous trash following established infection control guidelines.<br />Sorts, stocks and delivers linens. Gathers and prepares soiled linen for transportation.<br />Cleans and prepares dismissal and transfer units and certain equipment used in the care of patients and distributes non-medical supplies to specific areas.<br />Fills and cleans supply dispensers.<br />Inventories linens, cleaning supplies and paper supplies and orders additional in a timely and cost effective manner. Keeps housekeeping closet organized and clean.<br />Reports any mechanical failures or unsafe conditions to the supervisor.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />None Required.</p><p>Education Required:<br />No Formal Education.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />No experience required.</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Ability to follow and understand oral and written instructions and communicate with others.<br />Ability to work alone and to understand the physical arrangements of the facilities.<br />Performs tasks without disrupting operations of the doctors, nurses, patients, public, and other staff.<br />Ability to set priorities, be aware of and follow department policies and procedures in all situations.<br />Basic computer skills.<br />Excellent customer service skills.</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 35 lbs. from floor to a maximum 5 ft.<br />lift and carry up to 20 lbs. at waist height a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 50 lbs. of force.<br />Must be able to bend, stoop, kneel, reach above shoulders, and crawl to complete tasks. <br />Must also be able to push/pull/drag equipment such as hospital beds, and lift items weighing up to 50 lbs.<br />Must be able to be on feet the majority of the time with both walking/standing throughout the shift.<br />Must have ability to wear protective clothing as will be exposed to strong germicidal solutions, cleaning chemicals, temperature changes, soiled linen, infectious waste (blood and body fluids). Requires that incumbent be familiar with policies on handling infectious and hazardous waste.<br />Must have ability to operate vacuum cleaners, mopping equipment, buffer or burnisher, automatic scrubber, up to six-foot stepladder, and other cleaning tools.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job, including telephones, zone phones, and pagers.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$18.50 - $27.75<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora BayCare Medical Center - 2845 Greenbrier Rd]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[HOUSEKEEPING; PT, 1st shift]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-BayCare-Medical-Center---2845-Greenbrier-Rd/HOUSEKEEPING--PT--1st-shift_R152646?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora BayCare Medical Center - 2845 Greenbrier Rd<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R152646<br />Department:<br />11906 BayCare Leased Employees - Environmental Services<br />Status: <br />Part time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />20<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Hours: 7:00 am - 3:30 pm, including every other weekend, some holidays.<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Cleans patient care areas, surgical areas, public/private restrooms, conference rooms, lobbies, offices, elevators, and stairwells.<br />Cleans all environmental surfaces including ceilings and vents, walls, doors, furniture, beds, bathroom fixtures, and windows. Assists in cleaning emergency spills as requested.<br />Dusts and damp mops floors in patient and exam rooms, corridors, stairwells, restrooms, and other areas of the facility.<br />Replaces cubicle and window coverings.<br />Gathers and disposes recyclables, trash, and medical waste. Collects hazardous trash following established infection control guidelines.<br />Sorts, stocks and delivers linens. Gathers and prepares soiled linen for transportation.<br />Cleans and prepares dismissal and transfer units and certain equipment used in the care of patients and distributes non-medical supplies to specific areas.<br />Fills and cleans supply dispensers.<br />Inventories linens, cleaning supplies and paper supplies and orders additional in a timely and cost effective manner. Keeps housekeeping closet organized and clean.<br />Reports any mechanical failures or unsafe conditions to the supervisor.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />None Required.</p><p>Education Required:<br />No Formal Education.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />No experience required.</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Ability to follow and understand oral and written instructions and communicate with others.<br />Ability to work alone and to understand the physical arrangements of the facilities.<br />Performs tasks without disrupting operations of the doctors, nurses, patients, public, and other staff.<br />Ability to set priorities, be aware of and follow department policies and procedures in all situations.<br />Basic computer skills.<br />Excellent customer service skills.</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 35 lbs. from floor to a maximum 5 ft.<br />lift and carry up to 20 lbs. at waist height a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 50 lbs. of force.<br />Must be able to bend, stoop, kneel, reach above shoulders, and crawl to complete tasks. <br />Must also be able to push/pull/drag equipment such as hospital beds, and lift items weighing up to 50 lbs.<br />Must be able to be on feet the majority of the time with both walking/standing throughout the shift.<br />Must have ability to wear protective clothing as will be exposed to strong germicidal solutions, cleaning chemicals, temperature changes, soiled linen, infectious waste (blood and body fluids). Requires that incumbent be familiar with policies on handling infectious and hazardous waste.<br />Must have ability to operate vacuum cleaners, mopping equipment, buffer or burnisher, automatic scrubber, up to six-foot stepladder, and other cleaning tools.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job, including telephones, zone phones, and pagers.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$18.50 - $27.75<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora BayCare Medical Center - 2845 Greenbrier Rd]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[HOUSEKEEPING; PT, 1st shift]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-BayCare-Medical-Center---2845-Greenbrier-Rd/HOUSEKEEPING--PT--1st-shift_R152652?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora BayCare Medical Center - 2845 Greenbrier Rd<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R152652<br />Department:<br />11906 BayCare Leased Employees - Environmental Services<br />Status: <br />Part time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />28<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />HOURS: 7:00 am - 3:30 pm, including every other weekend and rotating holidays.<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Cleans patient care areas, surgical areas, public/private restrooms, conference rooms, lobbies, offices, elevators, and stairwells.<br />Cleans all environmental surfaces including ceilings and vents, walls, doors, furniture, beds, bathroom fixtures, and windows. Assists in cleaning emergency spills as requested.<br />Dusts and damp mops floors in patient and exam rooms, corridors, stairwells, restrooms, and other areas of the facility.<br />Replaces cubicle and window coverings.<br />Gathers and disposes recyclables, trash, and medical waste. Collects hazardous trash following established infection control guidelines.<br />Sorts, stocks and delivers linens. Gathers and prepares soiled linen for transportation.<br />Cleans and prepares dismissal and transfer units and certain equipment used in the care of patients and distributes non-medical supplies to specific areas.<br />Fills and cleans supply dispensers.<br />Inventories linens, cleaning supplies and paper supplies and orders additional in a timely and cost effective manner. Keeps housekeeping closet organized and clean.<br />Reports any mechanical failures or unsafe conditions to the supervisor.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />None Required.</p><p>Education Required:<br />No Formal Education.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />No experience required.</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Ability to follow and understand oral and written instructions and communicate with others.<br />Ability to work alone and to understand the physical arrangements of the facilities.<br />Performs tasks without disrupting operations of the doctors, nurses, patients, public, and other staff.<br />Ability to set priorities, be aware of and follow department policies and procedures in all situations.<br />Basic computer skills.<br />Excellent customer service skills.</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 35 lbs. from floor to a maximum 5 ft.<br />lift and carry up to 20 lbs. at waist height a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 50 lbs. of force.<br />Must be able to bend, stoop, kneel, reach above shoulders, and crawl to complete tasks. <br />Must also be able to push/pull/drag equipment such as hospital beds, and lift items weighing up to 50 lbs.<br />Must be able to be on feet the majority of the time with both walking/standing throughout the shift.<br />Must have ability to wear protective clothing as will be exposed to strong germicidal solutions, cleaning chemicals, temperature changes, soiled linen, infectious waste (blood and body fluids). Requires that incumbent be familiar with policies on handling infectious and hazardous waste.<br />Must have ability to operate vacuum cleaners, mopping equipment, buffer or burnisher, automatic scrubber, up to six-foot stepladder, and other cleaning tools.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job, including telephones, zone phones, and pagers.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$18.50 - $27.75<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora BayCare Medical Center - 2845 Greenbrier Rd]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>