<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/christopherlam888/workday-scraper</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Advanced Practice Provider Medical Oncology]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Lutheran-Medical-Center-Radiation-Oncology/Advanced-Practice-Provider-Medical-Oncology_R142895?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Lutheran Medical Center Radiation Oncology<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date: July 12, 2026 (30+ days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R142895<br />Job Description:<br />When you join us, you’ll become a part of a nationally recognized health system dedicated to our mission of “helping people live the healthiest lives possible<br />About this role:<br />As an Advanced Practice Provider- Medical Oncology, you will work with a team of healthcare professionals committed to providing quality care and excellent patient experience. In this role you will work with 3 Oncologists to provide top-notch care and patient experience. Here are some highlights you can expect.<br />You would practice at the Cancer Center at Lutheran Medical Center Campus in Wheat Ridge, CO<br />Your hours will be Mon-Fri 8am-5pm, or 4/10s<br />no call/no weekends<br />You would mostly see patients in the clinic for follow up and plans of care<br />You will round at the hospital as needed.<br />This position includes a $10,000 sign-on bonus, and up to $7,500.00 in relocation assistance if applicable.<br />Productivity Model is offered: $18.00 wRVU/ 487.50/calendar quarter<br />How we'll support you:<br />We care about your well-being, which is why we provide our caregivers with a generous benefits package. In addition, we offer paid time off, license reimbursement, malpractice insurance coverage, and an annual CME allowance to support your continuous growth and development. Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.<br />What you’ll bring:<br />APRN or PA-C degree from an accredited program<br /> Unrestricted license as an NP or PA in the state of Colorado or able to obtain<br />Current BLS, DEA, and full prescriptive authority<br />Minimum 1 year of NP or PA experience, preferably in oncology<br />Can consider a new graduate NP with recent RN oncology experience<br />We are not able to accept candidates requiring Visa sponsorship currently<br />About us:<br />Intermountain Health is a model health system by providing extraordinary care and superior service at an affordable cost. We are an integrated not-for-profit system of 33 hospitals, 385 clinics, and a medical group with more than 5,000 employed physicians and advanced practice providers across seven states in the mountain west. <br />Our value statements are core to our culture. They reflect the behavior and attitudes that are important to us, are an agreement for how we treat each other, help us make decisions on how to act, and are a promise of what people can expect from us. Learn more about our Mission, Vision, and Values at: About Intermountain!<br />Intermountain Health was recently recognized by the American Medical Association’s Joy in Medicine award for our commitment to physician wellbeing.<br />What does it mean to be a part of Intermountain Health?<br />It means joining the Power of We, building an environment where providers and caregivers can deliver the best in healthcare. Realizing each caregiver and volunteer is vital to providing care to our patients, because WE can only achieve the extraordinary together. Committed to the best in research and most advanced technology, the results are better clinical patient outcomes<br />Life in Denver, CO<br />Good Samaritan Hospital is a 234-bed Level II Trauma Center. Our mission is to bring health and hope to the poor, the vulnerable, our communities and each other. Opening in 2004, Good Samaritan Hospital is an Accredited Chest Pain Center, Primary Stroke Center, and a Cardiovascular Center of Excellence. We’re especially proud of our people, who helped win us the Outstanding Patience Experience Award  for 2021, 2022, and 2023 according to Healthgrades.<br />Lutheran Medical Center is a 338-bed Level II Trauma Center that provides comprehensive, specialty care to the poor, the vulnerable, our communities and each other. Dating back to 1905, we are proud of the rich history and inspiring mission our hospital has embodied for over 110 years.<br />Platte Valley Medical Center is a 98-bed Level III Trauma community hospital that is proud to offer comprehensive, integrated care focused on holistic health. We are proud to extend the mission of Intermountain Health by providing care for the poor, the vulnerable, our communities and each other.<br />Saint Joseph Hospital is a 365-bed facility and one of the top-ranked hospitals in Denver. We have been awarded the highest national recognition possible for nursing excellence – Magnet designation – by the ANCC. We are proud to extend the mission of Intermountain Health by providing care for the poor, the vulnerable, our communities and each other. Our deep community roots date back to 1873, making us one of the oldest hospitals in Colorado. We are proud to have received several awards including  America’s 250 Best Hospital Awards according to Healthgrades for 2022 and 2023.<br />Physical Requirements:<br />Location:<br />Lutheran Medical Center Radiation Oncology<br />Work City:<br />Golden<br />Work State:<br />Colorado<br />Scheduled Weekly Hours:<br />40<br />The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience. <br />$56.76 - $87.59<br />We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged. <br />Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.<br />Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.<br />At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.<br />All positions subject to close without notice.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Lutheran Medical Center Radiation Oncology]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patient Care Technician (First Shift/Full Time)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://roswellpark.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/ExternalCareers/job/Roswell/Patient-Care-Technician--First-Shift-Full-Time-_R-19701?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Roswell<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R-19701<br />Title: <br />Patient Care Technician (First Shift/Full Time)<br />Job Type:<br />Regular<br />Company:<br />Roswell Park Comprehensive Cancer Center<br />Department: <br />Nursing - 6 West<br />Time Type: <br />Full time<br />Weekly Hours: <br />40<br />FTE:<br />1<br />Shift: <br />First Shift (United States of America)<br />Summary: <br />Assists nurses and therapists with numerous duties involving direct and indirect patient care; transports patients within the organization; picks up and delivers x-rays, supplies, mail, scans and other items as needed in the clinic; assists with patient flow through; monitors and maintains quality assurance and quality improvement activities.<br />Qualifications:<br />Minimum Qualifications</p><ul><li>High School Diploma or High School Equivalency Diploma and the equivalent of one (1) year of full-time direct patient experience; or</li><li>High School Diploma or High School Equivalency Diploma and the equivalent of three (3) years of full-time experience in a healthcare setting; or</li><li>High School Diploma or High School Equivalency Diploma and the equivalent of three (3) years of full-time face-to-face customer service experience; or</li><li>Matriculation in a Nursing Program.</li></ul><p>NOTE: <br />Required degrees must have been granted by an accredited college or university or one recognized by Roswell Park Comprehensive Cancer Center as following acceptable educational practices.<br />Preferred Qualifications<br />The preferred candidate should have previous patient care experience in a hospital setting, including direct clinical experience. In addition, the preferred candidate should have prior experience working as a Patient Care Technician (PCT) and/or<br />currently enrolled in an accredited nursing program.<br />Equal Employment Opportunity Statement<br />Roswell Park Cancer Institute Corporation (RPCIC) and Health Research Inc. (HRI) Roswell Park Division believe that all persons are entitled to equal employment opportunities, and we do not discriminate against our employees, applicants or job seekers because of their race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, national origin, creed, age, disability, pregnancy-related condition, military or veteran status, marital or familial status, domestic violence victim status, citizenship status, genetic information, individual’s relationship or association with a member of a protected category or any other protected group status as defined by law.<br />Reasonable Accommodation Request<br />RPCIC and HRI are committed to working with and providing reasonable accommodation to individuals with disabilities. If, because of a medical condition or disability, you need a reasonable accommodation for any part of the employment process, please email HR-PayAndBenefits@RoswellPark.org and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.<br />Our Core Values<br />RPCIC and HRI are committed to providing an environment where patients, families, employees and community are treated with courtesy and respect. We support an inclusive environment that nurtures the talents, skills and abilities of each individual to embody and reflect our core values: Innovation, Integrity, Teamwork, Commitment, Compassion and Respect.<br />Historical Compensation Information Statement <br />Pursuant to Executive Order 161, no State entity, as defined by the Executive Order, is permitted to ask, or mandate, in any form, that an applicant for employment provide his or her current compensation, or any prior compensation history, until such time as the applicant is extended a conditional offer of employment with compensation. If such information has been requested from you before such time, please contact the Governor’s Office of Employee Relations at (518) 474-6988 or via email at info@goer.ny.gov.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Roswell]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Roswell Park Comprehensive Cancer Center]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[RN - Medical Surgical, Days (Pearland)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://memorialhermann.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/external/job/Pearland-Hospital/RN---Medical-Surgical--Days--Pearland-_100171419?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Pearland Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />100171419<br />At Memorial Hermann, we pursue a common goal of delivering high quality, efficient care while creating exceptional experiences for every member of our community. When we say every member of our community, that includes our employees. We know that when our employees feel cared for, heard and valued, they are inspired to create moments that exceed expectations, while prioritizing safety, compassion, personalization and efficiency. If you want to advance your career and contribute to our vision of creating healthier communities, now and for generations to come, we want you to be a part of our team.<br />Job Summary<br />Collaborates with interdisciplinary team in the delivery of patient care, utilizing the nursing process; provides professional nursing care to patients, including conducting nursing assessments, assisting with exams and treatment, patient education, and maintenance of medical records.</p><ul><li>Located in dynamic Pearland, one of the fastest-growing communities in the country, Memorial Hermann Pearland Hospital (ANCC Magnet designated) brings the expertise of the Memorial Hermann Health System close to home.  MH Pearland is currently seeking positive and engaged nurses that love working with a family oriented culture.</li><li>total beds Med/surg unit</li><li>Caring, Fun, and supportive environment with a strong focus on compassionate and quality patient care.</li><li>Non specialized units with a wide variety of patients to care for:  Cardiac (CHF, MI, Heart Cath patients), Neuro (stroke, seizures), Diabetes, Surgical (orthopedic, general) and more.</li><li>hour hospitalist coverage</li><li>Job Description</li><li>Minimum Qualifications</li><li>Education:  Graduate of an accredited School of Professional Nursing; Bachelors of Nursing preferred</li><li>Licenses/Certifications:</li><li>Current State of Texas license or temporary/compact license to practice professional nursing</li><li>Certified in Basic Life Support</li><li>Additional certifications may be required based on discipline and/or nursing unit requirements</li><li>Experience / Knowledge / Skills:</li><li>RN I <1 year</li><li>RN II = 1-3 years</li><li>RN III = 3-10 years</li><li>RN IV = 10+ years</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Pearland Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Memorial Hermann Health System]]></company>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>