<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/christopherlam888/workday-scraper</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse 12HR Nights, Psychiatric - ICU]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://huntingtonhospital.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/HuntingtonHospitalCareers/job/Huntington-Hospital---Pasadena/Registered-Nurse-12HR_R-29597?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>locations</li><li>Huntington Hospital - Pasadena</li><li>time type</li><li>Full time</li><li>posted on</li><li>Posted Today</li><li>job requisition id</li><li>R-29597</li><li>Internal Workers – Please log into your Workday account to apply **</li><li>Huntington Hospital Employee Login</li><li>Compensation Range:</li><li>Anticipated compensation range of $47.88 - $71.23 / Hour depending on qualifications and experience.</li><li>hour shifts at Huntington Health are overtime-based (not a straight time rate for all 12 hours). Therefore, employees who work a full 12-hour shift will be paid their base rate for 8 hours AND overtime (1.5) for hours up to 12.</li><li>Department:</li><li>Psychiatric - ICU</li><li>Expectations:</li><li>Responsible for coordination of care to meet identified needs of the patient/family. Supervises the management of patient care utilizing critical thinking and nursing process, discharge planning, resource identification, linking and scheduling patients with required services, monitoring care delivery, advocating for the patient, care planning and evaluating outcomes. Coordinates patient care across the health care continuum, and assists other team members with meeting individual patient needs.</li><li>This position may require flexibility of hours.</li></ul><p>EDUCATION:<br />Bachelor’s degree (BSN) required.   Associate Degree in Nursing (ADN) will be considered if enrolled in a BSN program with degree completion within 2 years of date of hire or date of transfer to an RN position. Diploma or transcripts on highest degree earned required.</p><p>EXPERIENCE/TRAINING:<br />Minimum 1 year of current experience in acute care area of expertise/equivalent service area, 2 years preferred.<br />Basic computer skills/experience with computerized documentation systems required.</p><p>LICENSES/CERTIFICATIONS:<br />Required:<br />Current unrestricted Registered Nurse (RN) license issued by California Board of Registered Nursing (BRN)<br />Current Basic Life Support Provider (BLS) issued by American Heart Association</p><p>Preferred:<br />Current unrestricted Registered Nurse-Board Certified (RN-BC)</p><ul><li>SKILLS:</li><li>Ensures all patients' rights are intact. Reports all violations and all patient complaints to Psychiatric Unit Shift Supervisor</li><li>Provides therapeutic structure and assist staff therapist in group settings.</li><li>Provides patient education.</li><li>Continually updates knowledge base in terms of the special needs of the various patient populations served.</li><li>Assists in planning and providing care to meet the developmental needs of the patient populations.</li><li>Provides supervision to every team member on the unit/shift (PCA, LVN, LPT, Sitter)</li><li>Enforces all safety policies and procedures carried out by team members.</li><li>Follows all applicable guidelines and policies during events such as Code Gray, Seclusion and Restraints, and other Codes.</li><li>Cross trained and competent to work on any DMC inpatient unit.</li><li>Worker Type:</li><li>Regular</li><li>Full time</li><li>Shift:</li><li>Nights</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Huntington Hospital - Pasadena]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Huntington Hospital]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Physical Therapist Wound Care - Full Time - Days]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://stanfordhealthcare.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/SHC_Tri-Valley_External_Careers/job/5555-W-Las-Positas-Blvd---PLEASANTON/Physical-Therapist-Wound-Care---Full-Time---Days_R2548804?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />5555 W. Las Positas Blvd. - PLEASANTON<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R2548804<br />If you're ready to be part of our legacy of hope and innovation, we encourage you to take the first step and explore our current job openings. Your best is waiting to be discovered. <br /> Day - 08 Hour (United States of America)<br />Job Summary:<br />The Wound Care Physical Therapist is responsible for providing MIST Therapy, patient care, and education to acute and chronic wounds, urinary incontinence and pressure injuries.<br />Essential Functions:<br />The essential functions listed below are general examples and not a description of comprehensive duties.<br />Specific duties and responsibilities may vary depending on department or program needs without changing the nature or scope of this position or level of responsibility. May be asked to perform other duties as assigned.<br />Assess patient s pertinent prior medical histories, skin integrity problems, acute and chronic wounds to develop an appropriate plan of care for each patient.<br />Provide Ultrasound MIST Therapy to patients identified to benefit from the treatment to enhance wound healing.<br />Educate patients and families on wound and problems with skin integrity etiology, systematic factors which they can impact, and self-care where practical.<br />Provides real-time education to all staff members to improve their wound care, early mobility and pressure injury prevention skills.<br />Consults with physicians, nurses, case managers, pharmacists and therapists to provide coordinated care specific to the patient.<br />Documents clearly the plan of care, education, specific steps in care, including products and how they are to be used.<br />Participate in 2 PI Surveys annually.<br />Willing to provide mentorship on future physical therapy students on wound care and pressure injury prevention management.<br />Employee must perform all duties and responsibilities in accordance with the C-I-CARE Standards of the hospital. C-I-CARE is the foundation of Stanford Healthcare – Tri-Valley’s patient-experience and represents a framework for patient-centered interactions.<br />Job Qualifications:<br />Education: <br />Graduate of an accredited Physical Therapy Program, Masters or Doctorate degree preferred.<br />Completion of Wound Care Education program or has successfully completed experiential program and certification through an accredited institution (e.g. NAWCO, APTA Specialist Certification Program) prior or within the first year of hire.<br />Experience:<br />Preferred minimum of 2 years full time or 4 years part time years of direct wound care bedside experience, experience with wound debridement preferred.<br />Proof of continuing education on wound care in the last license renewal or active participation in current facility’s wound care or pressure injury prevention program.<br />License/Certification:<br />Current permanent/unrestricted license to practice physical therapy in the United States or any of its possessions or territories.<br />Current CA PT license.<br />Current American Heart Association BLS Certification.<br />Knowledge, Skills, and Abilities:<br />Maintains high level of competence in wound care specialization.<br />Previous documentation experience within the EPIC electronic health record environment strongly preferred.<br />Strong communication skills – Ability to read, write and understand the English language.<br />Strong attention to detail.<br />Ability to problem solve and adapt to a changing environment.<br />Ability to use information and keep abreast of developments in technology to communicate, manage knowledge, mitigate error, and support decision-making in patient care.<br />Ability to work as a valued team member, but also autonomously.<br />Ability to positively influence others to meet patient needs and achieve shared goals.<br />Ability to effectively prioritize to provide quality and valued patient care.<br />Knowledge of principles, practices and current trends in health care and hospital system organization and administration sufficient to provide clinical judgement, leadership, coordination and operational direction for assigned areas of responsibilities.<br />Physical Demand and Working Conditions:<br />The physical requirements and working conditions in which the job is typically performed are available from Occupational Health Department. Reasonable accommodations will be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions of the job.<br />Equal Opportunity Employer:<br />Equal Opportunity Employer Stanford Health Care – Tri-Valley (SHC-TV) strongly values diversity and is committed to equal opportunity and non-discrimination in all of it’s policies and practices, including the area of employment. Accordingly, SHC does not discriminate against any person on the basis of race, color, sex, sexual orientation or gender identity and/or expression, religion, age, national or ethnic origin, political beliefs, marital status, medical condition, genetic information, veteran status, or disability, or the perception of any of the above. People of all genders, members of all racial and ethnic groups, people with disabilities, and veterans are encouraged to apply. Qualified applicants with criminal convictions will be considered after an individualized assessment of the conviction and the job requirements.<br />Equal Opportunity Employer Stanford Health Care (SHC) strongly values diversity and is committed to equal opportunity and non-discrimination in all of its policies and practices, including the area of employment. Accordingly, SHC does not discriminate against any person on the basis of race, color, sex, sexual orientation or gender identity and/or expression, religion, age, national or ethnic origin, political beliefs, marital status, medical condition, genetic information, veteran status, or disability, or the perception of any of the above. People of all genders, members of all racial and ethnic groups, people with disabilities, and veterans are encouraged to apply. Qualified applicants with criminal convictions will be considered after an individualized assessment of the conviction and the job requirements.<br />Base Pay Scale: Generally starting at $47.71 - $64.96 per hour<br />The salary of the finalist selected for this role will be set based on a variety of factors, including but not limited to, internal equity, experience, education, specialty and training. This pay scale is not a promise of a particular wage.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[5555 W. Las Positas Blvd. - PLEASANTON]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Stanford Health Care]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nurse II - Perioperative Care Unit]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://roswellpark.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/ExternalCareers/job/Hospital/Nurse-II---Perioperative-Care-Unit_R-19623?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R-19623<br />Title: <br />Nurse II - Perioperative Care Unit<br />Job Type:<br />Regular<br />Company:<br />Roswell Park Comprehensive Cancer Center<br />Department: <br />Perioperative Care Unit<br />Time Type: <br />Full time<br />Weekly Hours: <br />37.5<br />FTE:<br />0.9375<br />Shift: <br />Second Shift (United States of America)<br />Summary: <br />Plans, provides and supervises nursing interventions for individuals with cancer and cancer-related health care problems; diagnoses and treats human responses to actual or potential health problems through such services as patient care, health teaching, and health counseling; provides interventions supportive to or restorative of life and well-being; executes medical regimens prescribed by a physician, dentist or other licensed health care provider authorized by the State Education Commissioner’s regulations; supervises Nurse I’s, Licensed Practical Nurses, Hospital Clinical Assistants and Clinical Support Assistants; performs administrative tasks with assigned area of responsibility; enhances professional growth and development through participation in educational programs, current literature, inservice meetings and workshops.<br />Qualifications:<br />Required Education and Experience</p><p>License Requirement<br />License to practice as a Registered Nurse in the State of New York.</p><ul><li>Education and Experience</li><li>Graduation from an accredited school of nursing and the equivalent of one (1) year of full-time oncology nursing experience; or</li><li>Graduation from an accredited school of nursing and the equivalent of one (1) year of full-time critical care experience; or</li><li>Graduation from an accredited school of nursing and the equivalent of two (2) years of full-time medical-surgical experience in an acute care setting; or</li><li>Graduation from an accredited school of nursing, the equivalent of one (1) year of full-time medical-surgical experience in an acute care setting and completion of Roswell Park nursing orientation with the ability to function independently at a satisfactory level for three (3) months (full-time) as a Nurse I at Roswell Park.</li></ul><ul><li>NOTE:</li><li>Incumbents will serve a one (1) year full-time probationary period as a Nurse II.</li><li>Required degrees must have been granted by an accredited school, college or university or one recognized by Roswell Park Comprehensive Cancer Center as following acceptable educational practices.</li><li>Preferred Qualifications</li><li>Preferred qualifications include at least one year of critical care nursing experience, along with prior perioperative experience. Candidates should hold current Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS) and Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS) certifications, demonstrating the ability to respond effectively in high-acuity and emergency situations across patient populations.</li><li>Equal Employment Opportunity Statement</li><li>Roswell Park Cancer Institute Corporation (RPCIC) and Health Research Inc. (HRI) Roswell Park Division believe that all persons are entitled to equal employment opportunities, and we do not discriminate against our employees, applicants or job seekers because of their race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, national origin, creed, age, disability, pregnancy-related condition, military or veteran status, marital or familial status, domestic violence victim status, citizenship status, genetic information, individual’s relationship or association with a member of a protected category or any other protected group status as defined by law.</li><li>Reasonable Accommodation Request</li><li>RPCIC and HRI are committed to working with and providing reasonable accommodation to individuals with disabilities. If, because of a medical condition or disability, you need a reasonable accommodation for any part of the employment process, please email HR-PayAndBenefits@RoswellPark.org and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.</li><li>Our Core Values</li><li>RPCIC and HRI are committed to providing an environment where patients, families, employees and community are treated with courtesy and respect. We support an inclusive environment that nurtures the talents, skills and abilities of each individual to embody and reflect our core values: Innovation, Integrity, Teamwork, Commitment, Compassion and Respect.</li><li>Historical Compensation Information Statement</li><li>Pursuant to Executive Order 161, no State entity, as defined by the Executive Order, is permitted to ask, or mandate, in any form, that an applicant for employment provide his or her current compensation, or any prior compensation history, until such time as the applicant is extended a conditional offer of employment with compensation. If such information has been requested from you before such time, please contact the Governor’s Office of Employee Relations at (518) 474-6988 or via email at info@goer.ny.gov.</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Roswell Park Comprehensive Cancer Center]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nurse II [RP-N]]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://roswellpark.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/ExternalCareers/job/Hospital/Nurse-II--RP-N-_R-19021?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R-19021<br />Title: <br />Nurse II [RP-N]<br />Job Type:<br />Regular<br />Company:<br />Roswell Park Comprehensive Cancer Center<br />Department: <br />Operating Room<br />Time Type: <br />Full time<br />Weekly Hours: <br />37.5<br />FTE:<br />0.9375<br />Shift: <br />Second Shift (United States of America)<br />Summary: <br />Qualifications:<br />Required Education and Experience</p><p>License Requirement<br />License to practice as a Registered Nurse in the State of New York.</p><ul><li>Education and Experience</li><li>Graduation from an accredited school of nursing and the equivalent of one (1) year of full-time oncology nursing experience; or</li><li>Graduation from an accredited school of nursing and the equivalent of one (1) year of full-time critical care experience; or</li><li>Graduation from an accredited school of nursing and the equivalent of two (2) years of full-time medical-surgical experience in an acute care setting; or</li><li>Graduation from an accredited school of nursing, the equivalent of one (1) year of full-time medical-surgical experience in an acute care setting and completion of Roswell Park nursing orientation with the ability to function independently at a satisfactory level for three (3) months (full-time) as a Nurse I at Roswell Park.</li></ul><ul><li>NOTE:</li><li>Incumbents will serve a one (1) year full-time probationary period as a Nurse II.</li><li>Required degrees must have been granted by an accredited school, college or university or one recognized by Roswell Park Comprehensive Cancer Center as following acceptable educational practices.</li><li>Equal Employment Opportunity Statement</li><li>Roswell Park Cancer Institute Corporation (RPCIC) and Health Research Inc. (HRI) Roswell Park Division believe that all persons are entitled to equal employment opportunities, and we do not discriminate against our employees, applicants or job seekers because of their race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, national origin, creed, age, disability, pregnancy-related condition, military or veteran status, marital or familial status, domestic violence victim status, citizenship status, genetic information, individual’s relationship or association with a member of a protected category or any other protected group status as defined by law.</li><li>Reasonable Accommodation Request</li><li>RPCIC and HRI are committed to working with and providing reasonable accommodation to individuals with disabilities. If, because of a medical condition or disability, you need a reasonable accommodation for any part of the employment process, please email HR-PayAndBenefits@RoswellPark.org and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.</li><li>Our Core Values</li><li>RPCIC and HRI are committed to providing an environment where patients, families, employees and community are treated with courtesy and respect. We support an inclusive environment that nurtures the talents, skills and abilities of each individual to embody and reflect our core values: Innovation, Integrity, Teamwork, Commitment, Compassion and Respect.</li><li>Historical Compensation Information Statement</li><li>Pursuant to Executive Order 161, no State entity, as defined by the Executive Order, is permitted to ask, or mandate, in any form, that an applicant for employment provide his or her current compensation, or any prior compensation history, until such time as the applicant is extended a conditional offer of employment with compensation. If such information has been requested from you before such time, please contact the Governor’s Office of Employee Relations at (518) 474-6988 or via email at info@goer.ny.gov.</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Roswell Park Comprehensive Cancer Center]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) - Med/Surg/Ortho - 3rd Floor - FT - Nights (@)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://methodisthealth.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MLH/job/Methodist-North-Hospital/RN---Med-Surg---North---Full-Time---Nights_R-6132?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Methodist North Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R-6132<br />If you are looking to make an impact on a meaningful scale, come join us as we embrace the Power of One!<br /> We strive to be an employer of choice and establish a reputation for being a talent rich organization where Associates can grow their career caring for others. For over a century, we’ve served the health care needs of the people of Memphis and the Mid-South.<br /> Methodist North - Med Surg Registered Nurse (RN)<br />Address: 3960 New Covington Pike; Memphis, TN 38128<br />Full Time Nights : Three 12 Hour Night Shifts, 7pm - 7am</p><p>Working at MLH means carrying the mission forward of caring for our community and impacting the lives of patients in every way through compassion, a deliberate focus on service expectations and a consistent thriving for excellence.</p><p>A Brief Overview<br />Responsible for delivering and coordinating nursing care for patients within a multidisciplinary team, utilizing the nursing process to ensure comprehensive, high-quality care. Provides compassionate, patient-centered care while supporting patients and families through emotional challenges and crises. Prioritizes patient safety and strives for optimal care outcomes through evidence-based practice. Educates and advocates for both patients and their families, empowering them with the knowledge and resources needed for treatment and self-care. Demonstrates professionalism and upholds the MLH Mission, Vision, and Values, serving as a role model for excellence in nursing practice.</p><p>What you will do<br />Conducts comprehensive nursing assessments to determine appropriate interventions and develop individualized care plans.<br />Provides patient and family education on care plans, medications, and self-care strategies.<br />Develops, implements, and adjusts personalized patient care plans based on ongoing clinical assessments.<br />Administers medications safely, following best practices in medication management.<br />Collaborates with interdisciplinary teams to ensure coordinated, high-quality patient care.</p><p>Education Qualifications<br />Post-Graduate Certificate or Diploma Nursing - RN<br />Preferred: Bachelor's Degree Nursing - RN<br />Experience Qualifications<br />Minimum of 6 months RN experience<br />Preferred: Greater than 1 year experience in similar clinical setting<br />Skills and Abilities<br />Comprehensive understanding of patient care, including the ability to conduct thorough assessments using the nursing process.<br />Strong knowledge of the Nurse Practice Act and the scope of practice for a Registered Nurse.<br />Ability to process complex clinical information using critical thinking to develop, implement, and support individualized care plans.<br />Ability to effectively delegate tasks to team members, ensuring a collaborative, team-based approach to delivering high-quality patient care.<br />Familiarity with healthcare technology that enhances patient safety and care efficiency (e.g., bar code scanning, electronic health records).<br />Licenses and Certifications<br />BASIC LIFE SUPPORT - American Heart Association<br />Registered Nurse Tennessee - Tennessee Board of Nursing<br />Preferred: Certification in clinical specialty<br />Supervision Provided by this Position<br />The Registered Nurse directs and delegates all patient care activities on nursing units.<br />Physical Demands<br />The physical activities of this position may include climbing, pushing, standing, hearing, walking, reaching, grasping, kneeling, stooping, and repetitive motion.<br />Must have good balance and coordination.<br />The physical requirements of this position are: medium work - exerting up to 50 lbs. of force occasionally and/or up to 25 lbs. of force frequently.<br />The Associate is required to have close visual acuity including color, depth perception, and field of vision to perform an activity, such as assessing patients, preparing and analyzing data and figures; transcribing; viewing a computer terminal; or extensive reading.<br />Frequent invasive and non-invasive patient contact.<br />Exposure to patient body fluids as well as exposure to hazardous or poisonous materials.<br />Ability to react quickly to emergency situations.<br />Our Associates are passionate about what they do, the service they provide and the patients they serve. We value family, team and a Power of One culture that requires commitment to the highest standards of care and unity.</p><p>Boasting one of the South's largest medical centers, Memphis blends a friendly community, a thriving and growing downtown, and a low cost of living. We see each day as a new opportunity to make a difference in the lives of the people in our community.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Methodist North Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Methodist Le Bonheur Healthcare]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) - OR - FT - 9a - 930p - University (@)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://methodisthealth.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MLH/job/Methodist-University-Hospital/RN---University-CV-OR---10-hr-Days_R-6332?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Methodist University Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R-6332<br />If you are looking to make an impact on a meaningful scale, come join us as we embrace the Power of One!<br /> We strive to be an employer of choice and establish a reputation for being a talent rich organization where Associates can grow their career caring for others. For over a century, we’ve served the health care needs of the people of Memphis and the Mid-South.<br /> Responsible for the nursing care of patients requiring specialized judgment and skill. This judgment and skill is based on knowledge of the natural, behavioral and nursing sciences and humanities as the basis for application of the nursing process in wellness and illness care.<br />Models appropriate behavior as exemplified in MLH Mission, Vision and Values.</p><p>Working at MLH means carrying the mission forward of caring for our community and impacting the lives of patients in every way through compassion, a deliberate focus on service expectations and a consistent thriving for excellence.</p><p>A Brief Overview<br />Responsible for delivering and coordinating nursing care for patients within a multidisciplinary team, utilizing the nursing process to ensure comprehensive, high-quality care. Provides compassionate, patient-centered care while supporting patients and families through emotional challenges and crises. Prioritizes patient safety and strives for optimal care outcomes through evidence-based practice. Educates and advocates for both patients and their families, empowering them with the knowledge and resources needed for treatment and self-care. Demonstrates professionalism and upholds the MLH Mission, Vision, and Values, serving as a role model for excellence in nursing practice.</p><p>What you will do<br />Conducts comprehensive nursing assessments to determine appropriate interventions and develop individualized care plans.<br />Provides patient and family education on care plans, medications, and self-care strategies.<br />Develops, implements, and adjusts personalized patient care plans based on ongoing clinical assessments.<br />Administers medications safely, following best practices in medication management.<br />Collaborates with interdisciplinary teams to ensure coordinated, high-quality patient care.</p><p>Education Qualifications<br />Post-Graduate Certificate or Diploma Nursing - RN<br />Preferred: Bachelor's Degree Nursing - RN<br />Experience Qualifications<br />Minimum of 6 months RN experience<br />Preferred: Greater than 1 year experience in similar clinical setting<br />Skills and Abilities<br />Comprehensive understanding of patient care, including the ability to conduct thorough assessments using the nursing process.<br />Strong knowledge of the Nurse Practice Act and the scope of practice for a Registered Nurse.<br />Ability to process complex clinical information using critical thinking to develop, implement, and support individualized care plans.<br />Ability to effectively delegate tasks to team members, ensuring a collaborative, team-based approach to delivering high-quality patient care.<br />Familiarity with healthcare technology that enhances patient safety and care efficiency (e.g., bar code scanning, electronic health records).<br />Licenses and Certifications<br />BASIC LIFE SUPPORT - American Heart Association<br />Registered Nurse Tennessee - Tennessee Board of Nursing<br />Preferred: Certification in clinical specialty<br />Supervision Provided by this Position<br />The Registered Nurse directs and delegates all patient care activities on nursing units.<br />Physical Demands<br />The physical activities of this position may include climbing, pushing, standing, hearing, walking, reaching, grasping, kneeling, stooping, and repetitive motion.<br />Must have good balance and coordination.<br />The physical requirements of this position are: medium work - exerting up to 50 lbs. of force occasionally and/or up to 25 lbs. of force frequently.<br />The Associate is required to have close visual acuity including color, depth perception, and field of vision to perform an activity, such as assessing patients, preparing and analyzing data and figures; transcribing; viewing a computer terminal; or extensive reading.<br />Frequent invasive and non-invasive patient contact.<br />Exposure to patient body fluids as well as exposure to hazardous or poisonous materials.<br />Ability to react quickly to emergency situations.<br />Our Associates are passionate about what they do, the service they provide and the patients they serve. We value family, team and a Power of One culture that requires commitment to the highest standards of care and unity.</p><p>Boasting one of the South's largest medical centers, Memphis blends a friendly community, a thriving and growing downtown, and a low cost of living. We see each day as a new opportunity to make a difference in the lives of the people in our community.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Methodist University Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Methodist Le Bonheur Healthcare]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) - Dialysis - Nights (@)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://methodisthealth.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MLH/job/Methodist-University-Hospital/Registered-Nurse--RN----Dialysis---Nights_R-7421?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>remote type<br />On Campus<br />locations<br />Methodist University Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R-7421<br />If you are looking to make an impact on a meaningful scale, come join us as we embrace the Power of One!<br /> We strive to be an employer of choice and establish a reputation for being a talent rich organization where Associates can grow their career caring for others. For over a century, we’ve served the health care needs of the people of Memphis and the Mid-South.<br /> Responsible for the nursing care of dialysis patients requiring specialized judgment and skill. This judgment and skill is based on knowledge of the natural, behavioral and nursing sciences and humanities as the basis for application of the nursing process in diabetic care. Models appropriate behavior as exemplified in MLH Mission, Vision and Values.</p><p>Working at MLH means carrying the mission forward of caring for our community and impacting the lives of patients in every way through compassion, a deliberate focus on service expectations and a consistent thriving for excellence.</p><p>A Brief Overview<br />Responsible for the nursing care of dialysis patients requiring specialized judgment and skill. This judgment and skill is based on knowledge of the natural, behavioral and nursing sciences and humanities as the basis for application of the nursing process in diabetic care. Models appropriate behavior as exemplified in MLH Mission, Vision and Values.</p><p>What you will do<br />Provides Practice Excellence through specialized nursing assessment, care, evaluation and education to patients and families in accordance with established policies and procedures.<br />Promotes evidence based practice by using research to develop, implement and evaluate process standards, such as plans of care, protocols and guidelines.<br />Provides Leadership Excellence in clinical practice area.<br />Demonstrates a commitment to Learning Excellence through professional development and clinical expertise.<br />Demonstrates Role Clarity through professional competence, expertise, and knowledge, and supports the nursing profession through role modeling and fostering an environment of growth and learning.<br />Promotes Cultural Excellence with recognition and appreciation for cultural, ethnic, and generational diversity.</p><p>Education/Formal Training Requirements<br />Associate's Degree Nursing- RN <br />Bachelor's Degree Nursing- RN</p><p>Work Experience Requirements<br />1-3 years Registered Nurse</p><p>Licenses and Certifications Requirements<br />BASIC LIFE SUPPORT - American Heart Association  <br />Registered Nurse Arkansas - Arkansas State Board of Nursing  <br />Registered Nurse Tennessee - Tennessee Board of Nursing  <br />Registered Nurse Arkansas - Arkansas State Board of Nursing</p><p>Knowledge, Skills and Abilities<br />Analytical skills necessary to assess complex patient conditions effectively and to develop comprehensive plans of care.<br />Synthesizes multiple sources of information to assist in the resolution of human responses to complex problems.<br />Skill and proficiency in applying highly technical principles, concepts and techniques, which are central to the nursing profession.<br />Other certifications may be required depending on assigned nursing unit.</p><p>Supervision Provided by this Position<br />The Registered Nurse directs and delegates all patient care activities on nursing units.</p><p>Physical Demands<br />The physical activities of this position may include climbing, pushing, standing, hearing, walking, reaching, grasping, kneeling, stooping, and repetitive motion. <br />Must have good balance and coordination. <br />The physical requirements of this position are: medium work - exerting up to 50 lbs. of force occasionally and/or up to 25 lbs. of force frequently. <br />The Associate is required to have close visual acuity including color, depth perception, and field of vision to perform an activity, such as assessing patients, preparing and analyzing data and figures; transcribing; viewing a computer terminal; or extensive reading. <br />Frequent invasive and non-invasive patient contact. <br />Exposure to patient body fluids as well as exposure to hazardous or poisonous materials. <br />Ability to react quickly to emergency situations.</p><p>Our Associates are passionate about what they do, the service they provide and the patients they serve.  We value family, team and a Power of One culture that requires commitment to the highest standards of care and unity.</p><p>Boasting one of the South's largest medical centers, Memphis blends a friendly community, a thriving and growing downtown, and a low cost of living. We see each day as a new opportunity to make a difference in the lives of the people in our community.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Methodist University Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Methodist Le Bonheur Healthcare]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) - Cardiac - St. Luke's]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-St-Lukes-Medical-Center---2900-W-Oklahoma-Ave/Registered-Nurse--RN----Cardiac---St-Luke-s_R167452?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora St Lukes Medical Center - 2900 W Oklahoma Ave<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R167452<br />Department:<br />Status: <br />Full time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />36<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Nights, ,1900-0730 Every 3rd weekend rotation, 50% holidays/year<br />Our Cardiac Angioplasty unit is seeking a dynamic newly licensed or tenured nurse to join our team of nursing excellence. Join Aurora St. Luke's is a 6 TIMES Magnet designated Medical Center.</p><p>Perks of joining 10S Cardiac Angioplasty <br />$10,000 Sign-on Bonus!<br />Up to $20,000 Loan Support Program!<br />Up to $7,200 Education Assistance<br />Nurse Residency Program for Newly Licensed RNs<br />Nursing Certification fee paid through ANCC’s Success Pays Program<br />Comprehensive and progressive 12 weeks orientation<br />Mentor/Mentee Program available for all nurses<br />Continuing Education Credits<br />Robust Nursing Shared Governance<br />Generous Benefits package<br />10 S is a 24 bed a fast paced high acuity unit that specializes on pre and post interventional cardiology patients. 10S also serves a large volume of chest pain/STEMI patients, heart failure patients, and pre-op open heart surgery/TAVR patients.  If interested in the newest technology and breakthrough medical procedures in cardiac care this is a place for you. If you are a nurse who thrives in high paced environments this is a unit for you! <br />Advocate Aurora Health provides a leading-edge residency program with your future in mind. The New Graduate Nurse Residency Program is evidence-based and support the professional development, confidence, and overall well-being of the nurse resident as they transition from academia to the practice setting. <br />Night Shift Differential $5/hr<br />Weekend Differential $2/hr</p><p>Major Responsibilities:<br />Uses the nursing process to assess the needs of the patient, plan and implement individualized interventions and evaluate the effectiveness of the plan of care. Includes the patient and family in planning and implementing care and develops and maintains a therapeutic relationship throughout the healthcare continuum.<br />Anticipates and recognizes significant changes in the patient’s condition, status, and need for care. Provides ongoing assessment of the patient and takes appropriate actions when changes occur. Anticipates and alters the plan of care as needed, mobilizes appropriate resources, and collaborates with other health care team members to coordinate patient centered care.<br />Implements strategies to reduce patient risk and increase patient safety. Assesses patient and family readiness to learn and individualizes the approach as necessary. Works collaboratively to develop strategies to meet the learning needs of the patient and family.<br />Actively coordinates the discharge plan utilizing an interdisciplinary approach. Applies evidence-based practice to deliver patient care. Consistently incorporates nursing and regulatory standards of care into practice.<br />Provides ongoing evaluation of patient, team, and unit outcomes and is empowered to take appropriate action when changes are needed. Supports shared governance activities and initiatives to improve processes and patient outcomes.<br />Demonstrates effective communication, feedback, and conflict resolution skills. Promotes collaboration among healthcare team members. Assumes a leadership role in the care team and delegates appropriately to unlicensed personnel.<br />Promotes a culture of safety through identifying threats to patient safety and intervening to prevent patient harm. Reports patient safety events and near misses in a timely manner. Seeks to identify potential safety issues and assists in the implementation of corrective actions.<br />Applies ethical decision making, demonstrates respect and understanding for peers, and other clinical disciplines. Participates as an effective member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated, unbiased, individualized approach to care.<br />Participates in quality/process improvement initiatives to improve the functions of the department and the patient care experience.<br />Participates in professional activities which contribute to personal professional development and the development of others. Seeks opportunities to be taught, coached, and mentored. Attends required meetings/educational programs and completes annual competencies in a timely manner.<br />Must be able to demonstrate knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patients served. Must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient's status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to his/her age-specific needs, and to provide the care needed as described in the department's policies and procedures. Age-specific information is developed further in the departmental job standards.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Registered Nurse license issued by the state in which the team member practices, and<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Providers certification issued by the American Heart Association (AHA).</p><p>Education Required:<br />Completion of an accredited or approved program in Nursing.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />New Grads Welcome</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Demonstrates progression to provide holistic patient care and the ability to view clinical situations from a patient and family focus.<br />Demonstrates progression to recognize situational changes that require unplanned or unanticipated interventions, and responds to situations with confidence, timeliness and flexibility.<br />Proficient computer skills, use of electronic mail and electronic medical records systems.<br />Excellent communication (written and verbal), listening and interpersonal skills.<br />Demonstrates human relation skills with the ability to develop rapport and maintain positive, professional relationships with a variety of patients, team members and physicians. Ability to take initiative and work collaboratively with others.<br />Demonstrated ability to effectively make critical, independent decisions.<br />Excellent organization, prioritization and problem-solving skills.<br />Demonstrates time management skills with an ability to multi-task and prioritize in an environment with frequent interruptions.<br />Demonstrates coordination, collaboration, delegation and team building skills.<br />Certification Addendum:<br />Team members will maintain annual educational requirements for hospital based certifications (e.g. DNV, CARF or others)</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, reach above shoulders, and twist frequently throughout the workday.<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 50 lbs. from floor to waist.<br />lift up to 20 lbs. over the head.<br />carry up to 40 lbs. a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 30 lbs. of force.<br />perform a sliding transfer of 150 lbs. with a second person present.<br />Position requires use of foot pedals on carts or machines.<br />May be exposed to chemical and hazardous waste as well as blood and body fluids and communicable disease. Therefore, protective clothing and equipment must be worn as necessary.<br />Must have functional speech, vision, hearing, and touch with ability to use fine hand manipulation skills for IV insertion and other procedures/functions.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />#AuroraGMKERN<br />Military friendly organization</p><p>Pay Range<br />$37.50 - $56.25<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora St Lukes Medical Center - 2900 W Oklahoma Ave]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) - Emergency Department - Southshore]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-St-Lukes-South-Shore---5900-S-Lake-Dr/Registered-Nurse---RN----Emergency-Department---Southshore_R167451?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora St Lukes South Shore - 5900 S Lake Dr<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R167451<br />Department:<br />Status: <br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />36<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Full time, 2nd shift, 1500-0330, Every 3rd weekend rotation, 50% holiday requirement<br />The amazing team at Southshore’s Community Hospital is an experienced group of caregivers who treat patients with various emergent and critical care needs. This Level IV trauma unit welcomes experienced and strong communicators who are skilled and engaged to provide a compassionate level of patient centered care with collaboration and a commitment to delivery high quality, exceptional care. This high volume, fast-paced unit is needing dynamic teammates like you! <br />What we offer: <br />·Up to $10,000 sign on bonus for eligible RN's <br />·Student Loan Forgiveness up to $20,000 <br />·Tuition Reimbursement up to $7,200 <br />·Referral Bonus up to $5,000 <br />·Career Advancement <br />Why choose Advocate Aurora Health: <br />Primary Stroke Center <br />Accredited Geriatric Emergency Department <br />Modern Healthcare - Top Organization for Diversity <br />Seramount - Best organization for Multicultural Women <br />AORN Go Clear Award - Gold Level - Surgical Smoke-Free Recognition Program <br />Active Professional Governance <br />Primary Stroke Center <br />Accredited Geriatric Emergency Department <br />Modern Healthcare - Top Organization for Diversity <br />Seramount - Best organization for Multicultural Women <br />AORN Go Clear Award - Gold Level - Surgical Smoke-Free Recognition Program <br />Forbes 2024 Best-In-State Employer <br />1+ year acute RN experienced required<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Uses the nursing process to assess the needs of the patient, plan and implement individualized interventions and evaluate the effectiveness of the plan of care. Includes the patient and family in planning and implementing care and develops and maintains a therapeutic relationship throughout the healthcare continuum.<br />Anticipates and recognizes significant changes in the patient’s condition, status, and need for care. Provides ongoing assessment of the patient and takes appropriate actions when changes occur. Anticipates and alters the plan of care as needed, mobilizes appropriate resources, and collaborates with other health care team members to coordinate patient centered care.<br />Implements strategies to reduce patient risk and increase patient safety. Assesses patient and family readiness to learn and individualizes the approach as necessary. Works collaboratively to develop strategies to meet the learning needs of the patient and family.<br />Actively coordinates the discharge plan utilizing an interdisciplinary approach. Applies evidence-based practice to deliver patient care. Consistently incorporates nursing and regulatory standards of care into practice.<br />Provides ongoing evaluation of patient, team, and unit outcomes and is empowered to take appropriate action when changes are needed. Supports shared governance activities and initiatives to improve processes and patient outcomes.<br />Demonstrates effective communication, feedback, and conflict resolution skills. Promotes collaboration among healthcare team members. Assumes a leadership role in the care team and delegates appropriately to unlicensed personnel.<br />Promotes a culture of safety through identifying threats to patient safety and intervening to prevent patient harm. Reports patient safety events and near misses in a timely manner. Seeks to identify potential safety issues and assists in the implementation of corrective actions.<br />Applies ethical decision making, demonstrates respect and understanding for peers, and other clinical disciplines. Participates as an effective member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated, unbiased, individualized approach to care.<br />Participates in quality/process improvement initiatives to improve the functions of the department and the patient care experience.<br />Participates in professional activities which contribute to personal professional development and the development of others. Seeks opportunities to be taught, coached, and mentored. Attends required meetings/educational programs and completes annual competencies in a timely manner.<br />Must be able to demonstrate knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patients served. Must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient's status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to his/her age-specific needs, and to provide the care needed as described in the department's policies and procedures. Age-specific information is developed further in the departmental job standards.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Registered Nurse license issued by the state in which the team member practices, and<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Providers certification issued by the American Heart Association (AHA).</p><p>Education Required:<br />Completion of an accredited or approved program in Nursing.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />Minimum 1 year of experience in clinical nursing required - Would consider a newly licensed RN with EMT, Paramedic, ED externship experience</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Demonstrates progression to provide holistic patient care and the ability to view clinical situations from a patient and family focus.<br />Demonstrates progression to recognize situational changes that require unplanned or unanticipated interventions, and responds to situations with confidence, timeliness and flexibility.<br />Proficient computer skills, use of electronic mail and electronic medical records systems.<br />Excellent communication (written and verbal), listening and interpersonal skills.<br />Demonstrates human relation skills with the ability to develop rapport and maintain positive, professional relationships with a variety of patients, team members and physicians. Ability to take initiative and work collaboratively with others.<br />Demonstrated ability to effectively make critical, independent decisions.<br />Excellent organization, prioritization and problem-solving skills.<br />Demonstrates time management skills with an ability to multi-task and prioritize in an environment with frequent interruptions.<br />Demonstrates coordination, collaboration, delegation and team building skills.<br />Certification Addendum:<br />Team members will maintain annual educational requirements for hospital based certifications (e.g. DNV, CARF or others)</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, reach above shoulders, and twist frequently throughout the workday.<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 50 lbs. from floor to waist.<br />lift up to 20 lbs. over the head.<br />carry up to 40 lbs. a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 30 lbs. of force.<br />perform a sliding transfer of 150 lbs. with a second person present.<br />Position requires use of foot pedals on carts or machines.<br />May be exposed to chemical and hazardous waste as well as blood and body fluids and communicable disease. Therefore, protective clothing and equipment must be worn as necessary.<br />Must have functional speech, vision, hearing, and touch with ability to use fine hand manipulation skills for IV insertion and other procedures/functions.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$37.50 - $56.25<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora St Lukes South Shore - 5900 S Lake Dr]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) - Emergency Department - Southshore]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-St-Lukes-South-Shore---5900-S-Lake-Dr/Registered-Nurse---RN----Emergency-Department---Southshore_R167450?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora St Lukes South Shore - 5900 S Lake Dr<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R167450<br />Department:<br />Status: <br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />36<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Full time, Four 8 hr shifts 1900-0330, Every 3rd weekend rotation, 50% holiday requirement<br />The amazing team at Southshore’s Community Hospital is an experienced group of caregivers who treat patients with various emergent and critical care needs. This Level IV trauma unit welcomes experienced and strong communicators who are skilled and engaged to provide a compassionate level of patient centered care with collaboration and a commitment to delivery high quality, exceptional care. This high volume, fast-paced unit is needing dynamic teammates like you! <br />What we offer: <br />·Up to $10,000 sign on bonus for eligible RN's <br />·Student Loan Forgiveness up to $20,000 <br />·Tuition Reimbursement up to $7,200 <br />·Referral Bonus up to $5,000 <br />·Career Advancement <br />Why choose Advocate Aurora Health: <br />Primary Stroke Center <br />Accredited Geriatric Emergency Department <br />Modern Healthcare - Top Organization for Diversity <br />Seramount - Best organization for Multicultural Women <br />AORN Go Clear Award - Gold Level - Surgical Smoke-Free Recognition Program <br />Active Professional Governance <br />Primary Stroke Center <br />Accredited Geriatric Emergency Department <br />Modern Healthcare - Top Organization for Diversity <br />Seramount - Best organization for Multicultural Women <br />AORN Go Clear Award - Gold Level - Surgical Smoke-Free Recognition Program <br />Forbes 2024 Best-In-State Employer <br />1+ year acute RN experienced required<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Uses the nursing process to assess the needs of the patient, plan and implement individualized interventions and evaluate the effectiveness of the plan of care. Includes the patient and family in planning and implementing care and develops and maintains a therapeutic relationship throughout the healthcare continuum.<br />Anticipates and recognizes significant changes in the patient’s condition, status, and need for care. Provides ongoing assessment of the patient and takes appropriate actions when changes occur. Anticipates and alters the plan of care as needed, mobilizes appropriate resources, and collaborates with other health care team members to coordinate patient centered care.<br />Implements strategies to reduce patient risk and increase patient safety. Assesses patient and family readiness to learn and individualizes the approach as necessary. Works collaboratively to develop strategies to meet the learning needs of the patient and family.<br />Actively coordinates the discharge plan utilizing an interdisciplinary approach. Applies evidence-based practice to deliver patient care. Consistently incorporates nursing and regulatory standards of care into practice.<br />Provides ongoing evaluation of patient, team, and unit outcomes and is empowered to take appropriate action when changes are needed. Supports shared governance activities and initiatives to improve processes and patient outcomes.<br />Demonstrates effective communication, feedback, and conflict resolution skills. Promotes collaboration among healthcare team members. Assumes a leadership role in the care team and delegates appropriately to unlicensed personnel.<br />Promotes a culture of safety through identifying threats to patient safety and intervening to prevent patient harm. Reports patient safety events and near misses in a timely manner. Seeks to identify potential safety issues and assists in the implementation of corrective actions.<br />Applies ethical decision making, demonstrates respect and understanding for peers, and other clinical disciplines. Participates as an effective member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated, unbiased, individualized approach to care.<br />Participates in quality/process improvement initiatives to improve the functions of the department and the patient care experience.<br />Participates in professional activities which contribute to personal professional development and the development of others. Seeks opportunities to be taught, coached, and mentored. Attends required meetings/educational programs and completes annual competencies in a timely manner.<br />Must be able to demonstrate knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patients served. Must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient's status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to his/her age-specific needs, and to provide the care needed as described in the department's policies and procedures. Age-specific information is developed further in the departmental job standards.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Registered Nurse license issued by the state in which the team member practices, and<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Providers certification issued by the American Heart Association (AHA).</p><p>Education Required:<br />Completion of an accredited or approved program in Nursing.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />Minimum 1 year of experience in clinical nursing required - Would consider a newly licensed RN with EMT, Paramedic, ED externship experience</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Demonstrates progression to provide holistic patient care and the ability to view clinical situations from a patient and family focus.<br />Demonstrates progression to recognize situational changes that require unplanned or unanticipated interventions, and responds to situations with confidence, timeliness and flexibility.<br />Proficient computer skills, use of electronic mail and electronic medical records systems.<br />Excellent communication (written and verbal), listening and interpersonal skills.<br />Demonstrates human relation skills with the ability to develop rapport and maintain positive, professional relationships with a variety of patients, team members and physicians. Ability to take initiative and work collaboratively with others.<br />Demonstrated ability to effectively make critical, independent decisions.<br />Excellent organization, prioritization and problem-solving skills.<br />Demonstrates time management skills with an ability to multi-task and prioritize in an environment with frequent interruptions.<br />Demonstrates coordination, collaboration, delegation and team building skills.<br />Certification Addendum:<br />Team members will maintain annual educational requirements for hospital based certifications (e.g. DNV, CARF or others)</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, reach above shoulders, and twist frequently throughout the workday.<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 50 lbs. from floor to waist.<br />lift up to 20 lbs. over the head.<br />carry up to 40 lbs. a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 30 lbs. of force.<br />perform a sliding transfer of 150 lbs. with a second person present.<br />Position requires use of foot pedals on carts or machines.<br />May be exposed to chemical and hazardous waste as well as blood and body fluids and communicable disease. Therefore, protective clothing and equipment must be worn as necessary.<br />Must have functional speech, vision, hearing, and touch with ability to use fine hand manipulation skills for IV insertion and other procedures/functions.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$21.45 - $56.25<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora St Lukes South Shore - 5900 S Lake Dr]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>