<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://stableotto.github.io/workdayxml/</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Nvidia: Verification Engineer - New College Grad 2025]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://nvidia.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/NVIDIAExternalCareerSite/job/US-CA-Santa-Clara/Verification-Engineer---New-College-Grad-2025_JR1995559?workerSubType=ab40a98049581037a3ada55b087049b7&locationHierarchy1=2fcb99c455831013ea52fb338f2932d8]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, CA, Santa Clara<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>time left to apply<br>End Date: June 11, 2025 (30+ days left to apply)<br>job requisition id<br>JR1995559<br>We are now looking for a Verification Engineer - New College Grad. As a Verification Engineer at NVIDIA, you will verify the design and implementation of our state of the art memory subsystem for our mobile SoCs and GPUs. This position offers the opportunity to have real impact in a dynamic, technology-focused company impacting product lines ranging from consumer graphics to self-driving cars and the growing field of artificial intelligence. We have crafted a team of extraordinary people stretching around the globe, whose mission is to push the frontiers of what is possible today and define the platform for the future of computing.<br>What you'll be doing:<br>In this position, you will be responsible for verification of memory subsystem or coherent high speed interconnect design, architecture, golden models and micro-architecture using advanced verification methodologies.<br>As a member of our verification team, you'll understand the design & implementation, define the verification scope, develop the verification infrastructure (Testbenches, BFMs, Checkers, Monitors), execute test/coverage plans, and verify the correctness of the design.<br>Collaborate with architects, designers, emulation and silicon verification teams to accomplish your tasks.<br>What we need to see:<br>Completing or recently completed a Bachelors or Masters Degree (or equivalent experience)<br>Minimum 6 months experience in architecting test bench environments for unit level verification.<br>Exposure to verification using random stimulus along with functional coverage and assertion-based verification methodologies.<br>Prior Design or Verification experience of dynamic memory controllers or coherent high speed interconnects.<br>C++ programming language experience, scripting ability and an expertise in System Verilog.<br>Exposure to design and verification tools (VCS or equivalent simulation tools, debug tools like Debussy, GDB).<br>Strong debugging and analytical skills.<br>Strong communication and interpersonal skills are required.<br>NVIDIA is widely considered to be one of the technology world’s most desirable employers. We have some of the most forward-thinking and hardworking people in the world working for us. Are you creative and autonomous? Do you love the challenge of crafting the highest performance & lowest power silicon possible? If so, we want to hear from you! Come, join our Memory Controller team and help build the real-time, cost-effective computing platform driving our success across several exciting and quickly growing fields.<br>The base salary range is 96,000 USD - 212,750 USD. Your base salary will be determined based on your location, experience, and the pay of employees in similar positions.<br>You will also be eligible for equity and benefits. NVIDIA accepts applications on an ongoing basis. <br>NVIDIA is committed to fostering a diverse work environment and proud to be an equal opportunity employer. As we highly value diversity in our current and future employees, we do not discriminate (including in our hiring and promotion practices) on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, gender expression, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, disability status or any other characteristic protected by law.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: Senior Microarchitect - Memory Coherency Fabric Systems]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-California-Santa-Clara/Senior-Microarchitect---Memory-Coherency-Fabric-Systems_JR0269437-1?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>US, Massachusetts, Beaver Brook<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0269437<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Do Something Wonderful!<br>Intel put the Silicon in Silicon Valley. No one else is this obsessed with engineering a brighter future. Every day, we create world changing technology that enriches the lives of every person on earth. So, if you have a big idea, let's do something wonderful together. Join us, because at Intel, we are building a better tomorrow.<br>Who We Are <br>The DCAI and Silicon Eng Team (DASE) deliver leadership Xeon products to cloud and datacenter customers through development of industry leading x86 core and differentiated IPs that enhances product performance and competitiveness in both Xeon and AI platforms. IP design group within DCAI designs Coherent Fabric IP, Memory controller, NOC, PCIE and many fundamental building blocks for the Xeon server SOCs.<br> Who You Are<br>We are seeking an experienced Senior Micro Architect to design, develop, and implement advanced memory coherency fabric systems for next-generation data center and AI chips. This role requires a unique blend of architectural expertise and hands-on RTL coding skills to bring cutting-edge designs to life. The ideal candidate will have a deep understanding of memory subsystem architecture, interconnect protocols, and coherency mechanisms, coupled with a proven ability to implement these designs at the RTL level.<br><br>Your responsibilities include but not limited to:<br>Architect scalable memory coherency protocols and interconnect topologies to achieve high performance and low latency for data center and AI SoCs.<br>Design and implement critical components of the memory fabric microarchitecture, including coherency controllers and interconnect blocks.<br>Develop RTL code for core components of the memory fabric, ensuring optimal performance, area, and power trade-offs.<br>Work closely with verification teams to create test plans and debug issues arising during pre-silicon validation.<br>Collaborate with cross-functional teams (physical design, software, and firmware) to ensure seamless integration of memory fabric systems.<br>Analyze system performance, conduct workload modeling, and optimize the architecture for target use cases.<br>Mentor junior engineers and contribute to technical reviews and design documentation.<br>Stay updated with emerging technologies and trends in memory subsystems, coherency protocols, and AI/ML hardware.<br>Strong problem-solving and debugging skills.<br>Excellent communication and collaboration abilities.<br>Ability to manage and prioritize multiple tasks effectively.<br>Qualifications:<br>Minimum Qualifications<br>Graduate of Bachelor’s Degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, or a related field with at least 4+ years’ experience in SoC design, including significant experience in memory systems, coherency protocols, and RTL coding OR;<br>Graduate of Master’s Degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, or a related field with at least 3+ years’ experience in SoC design, including significant experience in memory systems, coherency protocols, and RTL coding OR;<br>PhD in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, or a related field.<br>Expertise in memory coherency protocols (e.g., MESI, MOESI, CXL, CCIX, CHI).<br>Strong knowledge of interconnect technologies (e.g., AMBA, PCIe, NoC architectures).<br>Proven RTL coding experience in Verilog or SystemVerilog.<br>Proficiency in simulation tools for performance modeling and analysis.<br>Familiarity with physical design implications of memory fabric architectures (timing, power, area).<br>Experience with EDA tools for synthesis, linting, and static timing analysis.<br><br>Preferred Experience<br>Experience with high-bandwidth memory (HBM), DDR, or other advanced memory technologies.<br>Knowledge in AI/ML accelerator or data center SoC design.<br>Knowledge of scripting languages like Python or TCL for workflow automation.<br>Experience with software-hardware co-design for end-to-end system optimization.<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>Additional Locations:<br>US, Massachusetts, Beaver Brook<br>Business group:<br>The Data Center & Artificial Intelligence Group (DCAI) is at the heart of Intel’s transformation from a PC company to a company that runs the cloud and billions of smart, connected computing devices. The data center is the underpinning for every data-driven service, from artificial intelligence to 5G to high-performance computing, and DCG delivers the products and technologies—spanning software, processors, storage, I/O, and networking solutions—that fuel cloud, communications, enterprise, and government data centers around the world.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$161,230.00-$227,620.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will be eligible for our hybrid work model which allows employees to split their time between working on-site at their assigned Intel site and off-site. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Microchip: Sr. Technical Staff Engineer - AI Systems]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://wd5.myworkdaysite.com/en-US/recruiting/microchiphr/External/job/CA---Roseville/Sr-Technical-Staff-Engineer---AI-Systems_R426-25?zz_LRV_Job_Category_Requisition_Extended=57f4a35d19da0140025b77636501bd99&zz_LRV_Job_Category_Requisition_Extended=57f4a35d19da0166f84174636501b499&zz_LRV_Job_Category_Requisition_Extended=57f4a35d19da01e9981873636501b199&locationCountry=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&locationCountry=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&timeType=51c161e7620310f46a28a73d306c1426]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>CA - Roseville<br>CA - San Jose - 3870 N. First St<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R426-25<br>Are you looking for a unique opportunity to be a part of something great? Want to join a 20,000-member team that works on the technology that powers the world around us? Looking for an atmosphere of trust, empowerment, respect, diversity, and communication? How about an opportunity to own a piece of a multi-billion dollar (with a B!) global organization? We offer all that and more at Microchip Technology, Inc.<br>People come to work at Microchip because we help design the technology that runs the world. They stay because our culture supports their growth and stability. They are challenged and driven by an incredible array of products and solutions with unlimited career potential. Microchip’s nationally-recognized Leadership Passage Programs support career growth where we proudly enroll over a thousand people annually. We take pride in our commitment to employee development, values-based decision making, and strong sense of community, driven by our Vision, Mission, and 11 Guiding Values; we affectionately refer to it as the Aggregate System and it’s won us countless awards for diversity and workplace excellence.<br>Our company is built by dedicated team players who love to challenge the status quo; we did not achieve record revenue and over 30 years of quarterly profitability without a great team dedicated to empowering innovation. People like you.<br>Visit our careers page to see what exciting opportunities and company perks await!<br>Job Description:<br>Overview:<br>We are seeking a highly skilled and experienced AI Systems Engineer to join our dynamic team. This candidate will play a pivotal role in driving efficiency across all aspects of operations within our support team and tools. As a Senior Technical Staff AI System Engineer, you will architect, develop, and optimize advanced AI systems across a variety of domains. You will lead initiatives to design, implement, and deploy scalable AI solutions, collaborating with cross-functional teams to drive innovation and operational excellence. The ideal candidate will possess a deep understanding of AI systems, exceptional problem-solving abilities, and a proven track record of implementing AI-driven solutions to enhance operational performance.<br>Key Responsibilities:<br>Develop and implement AI strategies to optimize operational efficiency across engineering teams<br>Lead end-to-end machine learning system design, including model development, evaluation, and deployment.<br>Lead the integration of AI solutions into existing customer support tools, enterprise software and infrastructure, ensuring seamless deployment and scalability<br>Collaborate with cross-functional teams to identify opportunities for AI integration and automation.<br>Design, build, and deploy AI models and algorithms to solve complex business problems.<br>Monitor and evaluate the performance of AI systems, making necessary adjustments to improve accuracy and effectiveness.<br>Provide technical leadership and mentorship to team members on AI-related projects.<br>Stay up to date with the latest advancements in AI technology and industry trends.<br>Provide technical training on AI ML related technologies<br>Ensure compliance with data privacy and security regulations in all AI initiatives.<br>Requirements/Qualifications:<br>Required Skills and Experience:<br>Advanced degree (Master’s or Ph.D.) in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, or a related field.<br>Minimum of 10 years of hands-on experience in AI systems development and implementation.<br>Proficiency in programming languages such as Python, Java, C, and C++.<br>Deep understanding of machine learning algorithms, neural networks, and statistical modeling<br>Strong knowledge of machine learning frameworks (e.g., TensorFlow, PyTorch, Keras).<br>Experience with classical machine learning techniques (e.g., XGBoost, scikit-learn) and time series analysis (e.g., Prophet, LSTMs).<br>Experience with large language models (LLMs), agentic frameworks, and prompt engineering<br>Familiarity with containerization and version control tools like Docker and GitHub.<br>Strong understanding of product lifecycle management and production code release processes.<br>Strong analytical, problem-solving, and communication skills<br>Desired Skills and Experience:<br>Familiarity with RTL, Verilog and ASIC development life cycle<br>Experience working in a fast-paced, high-tech environment<br>Optimize open-source AI frameworks and libraries for high-performance computing on specialized hardware<br>Design, implement, and validate new AI algorithms and models for enterprise-scale applications<br>Understanding of DevOps practices and tools for AI model deployment and monitoring.<br>Experience in benchmarking AI ML designs<br>Expertise in identifying and collecting appropriate metrics to measure the effectiveness of the AI ML tools<br>Expertise in computer vision techniques using OpenCV, TensorFlow, PyTorch, and PyTorch Lightning.<br>Proficiency in cloud infrastructure, specifically Azure AI Foundry, Cosmos DB, VNet, Entra ID auth, Blob storage, App Service, AI Search, Azure Monitor & Alerts.<br>Travel Time:<br>0% - 25%<br>Physical Attributes:<br>Feeling, Handling, Hearing, Seeing, Talking, Works Alone, Works Around Others<br>Physical Requirements:<br>Regular business hours (8:00 AM to 5:00 PM); 70% sitting, 15% standing, 15% walking<br>Pay Range:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive base pay, restricted stock units, and quarterly bonus payments. In addition to these components, our package includes health benefits that begin day one, retirement savings plans, and an industry leading ESPP program with a 2 year look back feature. Find more information about all our benefits at the link below:<br>Benefits of working at Microchip<br>The annual base salary range for this position, which could be performed in California, is $88,000 - $232,000.*<br>*Range is dependent on numerous factors including job location, skills and experience.<br>Microchip Technology Inc is an equal opportunity/affirmative action employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to sex, gender identity, sexual orientation, race, color, religion, national origin, disability, protected Veteran status, age, or any other characteristic protected by law.<br><br>For more information on applicable equal employment regulations, please refer to the EEO is the Law Poster and the EEO is the Law Poster Supplement. Please also refer to the Pay Transparency Policy Statement.<br>To all recruitment agencies: Microchip Technology Inc. does not accept unsolicited agency resumes. Please do not forward resumes to our recruiting team or other Microchip employees. Microchip is not responsible for any fees related to unsolicited resumes.]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>