<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/christopherlam888/workday-scraper</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Medical Director Specialty Care Billings]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Intermountain-Health-St-Vincent-Regional-Hospital/Medical-Director-Specialty-Care-Billings_R137758-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>locations</li><li>Intermountain Health St Vincent Regional Hospital</li><li>time type</li><li>Part time</li><li>posted on</li><li>Posted Today</li><li>time left to apply</li><li>End Date: May 12, 2026 (30+ days left to apply)</li><li>job requisition id</li><li>R137758</li><li>Job Description:</li><li>Medical Group Medical Director of Specialty Care in Montana Market, Billings is a leadership position reporting to and collaborating with the market Medical Group Associate Chief Medical Officer. Together, and in dyad partnership with market operations directors sustain healthy relationships among providers and Intermountain Health. The Medical Director must be a patient centric leader who is an excellent trusted clinician with strong interpersonal and organizational skills. They must have a strong commitment to improving the processes at Intermountain Health working with other departments, clinical programs, service-lines, clinical shared services, markets, and clinics in the organization through development of standard work and process improvement. The Medical Director will collaborate with all team members and all providers to deliver services that are high in measurable quality, value, and service, while also furthering the mission, the Framework for Excellence and strategic initiatives of Intermountain Health.</li><li>Responsibilities:</li><li>Leadership:</li><li>Practice medicine with excellence, as an example to others, exhibiting qualities and behaviors consistent with Employer’s Framework for Excellence</li><li>Provide leadership, management and coaching for providers toward the attainment of the clinical, quality, patient experience, productivity and strategic growth goals of Intermountain Health; assist in becoming a highly functional, integrated Medical Group</li><li>Assist in hiring of Physicians, Nurse Practitioners and Physician Assistants in collaboration with market Associate Chief Medical Officer and Regional VP of Practice Operations</li><li>Collaborate with the Regional VP of Practice Operations, Practice Administrators and other members of the management team in the development of strategic plans, quality programs, practice transformation and initiatives in alignment with Intermountain Health.</li><li>Maintain and enhance open and effective communication among providers, management teams, Care Site, and Intermountain Health</li><li>Ensure that all Physician and Advanced Practice Providers (APP) reviews and check-ins are up to date</li><li>Supervise, collaborate and mentor Medical Directors of reporting specialties/provider groups</li><li>Financial Stewardship</li><li>Review cost, utilization and value data regularly with Practice Administrators and ensure that this data is effectively disseminated among all assigned providers.</li><li>Collaborate with Practice Administrators to assist with local practice management to control costs and provide efficient, effective delivery of care.</li><li>Assist Practice Administrators and Intermountain Health (Coding and Payer Relations, Managed Care Contracting, Finance and Accounting, and Patient Financial Services) to facilitate the education of providers.</li><li>Customer Service:</li><li>Collaborate with team(s) in efforts related to optimize customer service and patient care (patients and employers, as well as physicians, associates, and other internal customers), and assist the Executive Director, Practice Administrators in efforts to develop superior service and quality; and</li><li>May serve as liaison, when appropriate, to internal and external customers.</li><li>Physician Partnership and Support</li><li>Meet regularly with leadership to develop strong relationships with providers and care teams that is essential to the successful performance of the practice and the organization;</li><li>Engage and be responsible for performance of reporting Medical Directors and matrixed providers.</li><li>Coordinate and participate in regular Practice meetings as a forum for dialogue around organizational strategic themes, clinical quality, patient experience, productivity and as a forum for gaining provider trust, input and feedback</li><li>Participate with market Associate Chief Medical Officer in quarterly Leadership rounding to assigned clinics.</li><li>Assist with physician and APP recruitment, retention and interviewing activities.</li><li>Attend PLC monthly meetings and subcommittee meetings as assigned.</li><li>Partner with clinical programs and service line leadership, responsible for implementing clinical best practices, care process models to promote clinical excellence, and high realizability while reducing unnecessary clinical variation.</li><li>Quality Management</li><li>Assist the Associate Chief Medical Officer in developing and deploying tools to measure care outcomes related to the improvement of care processes, in the context of clinical quality, service and access.</li><li>Ensure that the services provided by the employed providers are compliant with all legal and regulatory requirements and will assist with monitoring and auditing when necessary.</li><li>Responsible to provider engagement and performance to clinical quality metrics and at-risk measurements</li><li>Minimum Requirements</li><li>MD or DO with ABMS or equivalent AOA Board Certification in a relevant specialty.</li><li>Active Medical Licensure</li><li>Minimum two years of clinical experience in relevant specialty and experience in leading successful quality improvement projects within the clinical setting.</li><li>Effective verbal, written, and interpersonal communications skills.</li><li>Physical Requirements:</li><li>Interact with others requiring caregiver to verbally communicate as well as hear and understand spoken information.</li><li>Operate computers, telephones, office equipment, and manipulate paper requiring the ability to move fingers and hands.</li><li>See and read computer monitors and documents.</li><li>Remain sitting or standing for long periods of time to perform work on a computer, telephone, or other equipment.</li><li>Location:</li><li>Intermountain Health St Vincent Regional Hospital</li><li>Work City:</li><li>Billings</li><li>Work State:</li><li>Montana</li><li>Scheduled Weekly Hours:</li><li></li><li>The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience.</li><li>$7.25 - $999.99</li><li>We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged.</li><li>Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.</li><li>Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.</li><li>At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.</li><li>All positions subject to close without notice.</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Intermountain Health St Vincent Regional Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Medical Director Surgical and Procedural Care Billings]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Intermountain-Health-St-Vincent-Regional-Hospital/Medical-Director-Surgical-and-Procedural-Care-Billings_R137757-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Intermountain Health St Vincent Regional Hospital<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date: May 12, 2026 (30+ days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R137757<br />Job Description:<br />Medical Group Medical Director of Surgical and Procedural Care in Montana Market, Billings is a leadership position reporting to and collaborating with the market Medical Group Associate Chief Medical Officer. Together, and in dyad partnership with market operations directors sustain healthy relationships among providers and Intermountain Health. The Medical Director must be a patient centric leader who is an excellent trusted clinician with strong interpersonal and organizational skills. They must have a strong commitment to improving the processes at Intermountain Health working with other departments, clinical programs, service-lines, clinical shared services, markets, and clinics in the organization through development of standard work and process improvement. The Medical Director will collaborate with all team members and all providers to deliver services that are high in measurable quality, value, and service, while also furthering the mission, the Framework for Excellence and strategic initiatives of Intermountain Health.<br />Responsibilities:<br />Leadership:<br />Practice medicine with excellence, as an example to others, exhibiting qualities and behaviors consistent with Employer’s Framework for Excellence<br />Provide leadership, management and coaching for providers toward the attainment of the clinical, quality, patient experience, productivity and strategic growth goals of Intermountain Health; assist in becoming a highly functional, integrated Medical Group<br />Assist in hiring of Physicians, Nurse Practitioners and Physician Assistants in collaboration with market Associate Chief Medical Officer and Regional VP of Practice Operations<br />Collaborate with the Regional VP of Practice Operations, Practice Administrators and other members of the management team in the development of strategic plans, quality programs, practice transformation and initiatives in alignment with Intermountain Health.<br />Maintain and enhance open and effective communication among providers, management teams, Care Site, and Intermountain Health<br />Ensure that all Physician and Advanced Practice Providers (APP) reviews and check-ins are up to date<br />Supervise, collaborate and mentor Medical Directors of reporting specialties/provider groups<br />Financial Stewardship<br />Review cost, utilization and value data regularly with Practice Administrators and ensure that this data is effectively<br />disseminated among all assigned providers.<br />Collaborate with Practice Administrators to assist with local practice management to control costs and provide efficient, effective delivery of care.<br />Assist Practice Administrators and Intermountain Health (Coding and Payer Relations, Managed Care Contracting, Finance and Accounting, and Patient Financial Services) to facilitate the education of providers.<br />Customer Service:<br />Collaborate with team(s) in efforts related to optimize customer service and patient care (patients and employers, as well as physicians, associates, and other internal customers), and assist the Executive Director, Practice Administrators in efforts to develop superior service and quality; and<br />May serve as liaison, when appropriate, to internal and external customers.<br />Physician Partnership and Support<br />Meet regularly with leadership to develop strong relationships with providers and care teams that is essential to the successful performance of the practice and the organization;<br />Engage and be responsible for performance of reporting Medical Directors and matrixed providers.<br />Coordinate and participate in regular Practice meetings as a forum for dialogue around organizational strategic themes, clinical quality, patient experience, productivity and as a forum for gaining provider trust, input and feedback<br />Participate with market Associate Chief Medical Officer in quarterly Leadership rounding to assigned clinics.<br />Assist with physician and APP recruitment, retention and interviewing activities.<br />Attend PLC monthly meetings and subcommittee meetings as assigned.<br />Partner with clinical programs and service line leadership, responsible for implementing clinical best practices, care process models to promote clinical excellence, and high realizability while reducing unnecessary clinical variation.<br />Quality Management<br />Assist the Associate Chief Medical Officer in developing and deploying tools to measure care outcomes related to the improvement of care processes, in the context of clinical quality, service and access.<br />Ensure that the services provided by the employed providers are compliant with all legal and regulatory requirements and will assist with monitoring and auditing when necessary.<br />Responsible to provider engagement and performance to clinical quality metrics and at-risk measurements<br />Physical Requirements:<br />Minimum Requirements<br />MD or DO with ABMS or equivalent AOA Board Certification in a relevant specialty.<br />Active Medical Licensure<br />Minimum two years of clinical experience in relevant specialty and experience in leading successful quality improvement projects within the clinical setting.<br />Effective verbal, written, and interpersonal communications skills.<br />Location:<br />Intermountain Health St Vincent Regional Hospital<br />Work City:<br />Billings<br />Work State:<br />Montana<br />Scheduled Weekly Hours:<br />12<br />The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience. <br />$7.25 - $999.99<br />We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged. <br />Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.<br />Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.<br />At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.<br />All positions subject to close without notice.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Intermountain Health St Vincent Regional Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Medical Director Inpatient Services Billings]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Intermountain-Health-St-Vincent-Regional-Hospital/Medical-Director-Inpatient-Services-Billings_R137754-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Intermountain Health St Vincent Regional Hospital<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date: May 12, 2026 (30+ days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R137754<br />Job Description:<br />Medical Group Medical Director of Primary Care, Peaks Region, Montana Market, Billings, Inpatient Services is a leadership position reporting to and collaborating with the market Medical Group Medical Director of Primary Care, Peaks Region, Montana Market, Billings. Together, and in dyad partnership with market operations directors sustain healthy relationships among providers and Intermountain Health. The Medical Director must be a patient centric leader who is an excellent trusted clinician with strong interpersonal and organizational skills. They must have a strong commitment to improving the processes at Intermountain Health working with other departments, clinical programs, service-lines, clinical shared services, markets, and clinics in the organization through development of standard work and process improvement. The Medical Director will collaborate with all team members within their limited scope of services and all providers to deliver services that are high in measurable quality, value and service, while also furthering the mission, the Framework for Excellence and strategic initiatives of Intermountain Health.<br />Responsibilities:<br />Leadership:<br />Practice medicine with excellence, as an example to others, exhibiting qualities and behaviors consistent with Employer’s Framework for Excellence<br />Provide leadership, management and coaching for providers toward the attainment of the clinical, quality, patient experience, productivity, and strategic growth goals of Intermountain Health; assist in becoming a highly functional, integrated Medical Group with a particular focus on their limited focus of practice as outlined.<br />Assist in hiring of Physicians, Nurse Practitioners and Physician Assistants in collaboration with market Medical Group Medical Director.<br />Maintain and enhance open and effective communication among providers, management teams, Care Site, and Intermountain Health<br />Participate in and complete check ins and reviews with Physicians and Advanced<br />Lead and participate in education of providers as requested from supporting services.<br />Customer Service:<br />Collaborate with team(s) in efforts related to optimize customer service and patient care (patients and employers, as well as physicians, associates, and other internal customers), and will assist the Executive Director, Practice Administrators in efforts to develop superior service and quality.<br />4. Physician Partnership and Support<br />Meet regularly with leadership to develop strong relationships with providers and to discuss information that is essential to the successful performance of the practice.<br />Coordinate and participate in regular Practice meetings as a forum for dialogue around organizational strategic themes, clinical quality, patient experience, productivity and as a forum for gaining provider trust, input and feedback.<br />Assist with physician and APP recruitment, retention, and interviewing activities.<br />Attend their clinic’s/groups MOR/practice meetings monthly and as needed.<br />Partner with clinical programs and service line leadership, actively participate in implementation of clinical best practices, care process models to promote clinical excellence, and high reliability while reducing unnecessary clinical variation.<br />5. Quality Management<br />Assist the Medical Group Medical Director in developing and deploying tools to measure care outcomes related to the improvement of care processes within their limited scope of practice, in the context of clinical quality, service and access.<br />Ensure that the services provided by the employed providers are compliant with all legal and regulatory requirements and will assist with monitoring and auditing when necessary.<br />Minimum Requirements<br />MD or DO with ABMS or equivalent AOA Board Certification in a relevant specialty.<br />Active Medical Licensure<br />Minimum two years of clinical experience in relevant specialty and experience in leading successful quality improvement projects within the clinical setting.<br />Effective verbal, written, and interpersonal communications skills.<br />Physical Requirements:<br />Interact with others requiring caregiver to verbally communicate as well as hear and understand spoken information.<br />Operate computers, telephones, office equipment, and manipulate paper requiring the ability to move fingers and hands.<br />See and read computer monitors and documents.<br />Remain sitting or standing for long periods of time to perform work on a computer, telephone, or other equipment.<br />Location:<br />Intermountain Health St Vincent Regional Hospital<br />Work City:<br />Billings<br />Work State:<br />Montana<br />Scheduled Weekly Hours:<br />12<br />The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience. <br />$7.25 - $999.99<br />We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged. <br />Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.<br />Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.<br />At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.<br />All positions subject to close without notice.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Intermountain Health St Vincent Regional Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Pediatric Registered Nurse IV team]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Intermountain-Health-Primary-Childrens-Hospital/Pediatric-Registered-Nurse-IV-team_R124525-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Intermountain Health Primary Childrens Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date: May 19, 2025 (6 days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R124525<br />Job Description:<br />The Registered Nurse (RN) is a professional caregiver who assumes responsibility and accountability for assessing, planning, implementing and evaluating care of patients. The staff RN utilizes the nursing process by use of technology, therapeutic intervention, evidence-based practice and coordination of care with other health team members.<br />RNs at Intermountain Healthcare are committed to providing patient centered care while demonstrating our values and mission.  If you are interested in contributing to our mission of helping people live the healthiest lives possible-<br />Posting Specifics:<br />Benefits Eligible: yes<br />Shift Details: full time, 36 hrs a week, rotating days/nights 50/50<br />Unit/Location: Primary Children’s Hospital<br />Essential Functions<br />Assess: Performs appropriate assessment of physical, social, and psychological status (including cognitive, communicative, and developmental skills as appropriate). Seeks and evaluates information acquired from other members of interdisciplinary team: patient, family, physician, non-nursing disciplines, support staff, others.<br />Plan: Uses assessment information and critical thinking skills to collaboratively develop individualized plan of care. Actively seeks patient, family, team, and physician involvement to develop plan of care including needed education. Collaboratively plans and prepares patients for further support needs once the current episode of care outcomes are met (i.e., teaching, referrals, and follow-up).<br />Implement: Directs the interdisciplinary care team via delegation, coordination, and collaboration as appropriate. Provides or delegates care consistent with plan of care, guidelines of care and professional licensure provisions. Demonstrates the ability to set priorities and to coordinate and organize patient care delivery through effectively managing time, supplies, and resources.<br />Evaluate: Evaluates patient response to interventions through review of achievement of goals, clinical outcomes, patient, and family satisfaction. Revises plan of care as indicated and reassesses changes as appropriate.<br />Professionalism: Promotes nursing profession and participate in development of others.<br />Integrates legal and ethical standards into practice, complies with regulatory standards, practices within scope of licensure, provides accurate & timely documentation, and understands legal implications of care delivery.<br />Skills<br />Patient Care Delivery<br />Nursing Fundamentals<br />Interdisciplinary Teams<br />Documentations<br />Professional Etiquette<br />Accountability<br />Patient Care Coordination<br />Communication<br />Patient Evaluation<br />Critical Thinking</p><p>Minimum Qualifications<br />Current license to practice as a Registered Nurse in state of practice. Valid compact licenses must be transferred to the state of practice within 60 days of the start of employment.<br />RNs with less than 12 months of experience must obtain their Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN) within four (4) years of their hire date.<br />Basic Life Support Certification (BLS) for healthcare providers.</p><ul><li>Preferred Qualifications</li><li>One or more years of RN work experience</li><li>Bachelor's Degree in Nursing (BSN). Education must be obtained from an accredited institution. Degree will be verified.</li><li>Bachelor of Science in Nursing (BSN) is required as of the job description's last update on 4/27/2025. Employees hired or promoted prior to this date will be held to the minimum requirements that were in place at the time of their promotion or hire.</li><li>Physical Requirements:</li><li>Ongoing need for employee to see and read information, labels, assess patient needs, operate monitors, identify equipment and supplies.</li><li>and -</li><li>Frequent interactions with patient care providers, patients, and visitors that require employee to verbally communicate as well as hear and understand spoken information, alarms, needs, and issues quickly and accurately, particularly during emergency situations.</li><li>and -</li><li>Manual dexterity of hands and fingers to manipulate complex and delicate equipment with precision and accuracy. This includes frequent computer use and typing for documenting patient care, accessing needed information, medication preparation, etc.</li><li>and -</li><li>Expected to lift and utilize full range of movement to transfer patients. Will also bend to retrieve, lift, and carry supplies and equipment. Typically includes items of varying weights, up to and including heavy items.</li><li>and -</li><li>Need to walk and assist with transporting/ambulating patients and obtaining and distributing supplies and equipment. This includes pushing/pulling gurneys and portable equipment, including heavy items. Often required to navigate crowded and busy rooms (full of equipment, power cords on the floor, etc).</li><li>and -</li><li>May be expected to stand in a stationary position for an extended period of time.</li><li>Location:</li><li>Intermountain Health Primary Childrens Hospital</li><li>Work City:</li><li>Salt Lake City</li><li>Work State:</li><li>Utah</li><li>Scheduled Weekly Hours:</li><li></li><li>The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience.</li><li>$34.19 - $50.73</li><li>We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged.</li><li>Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.</li><li>Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.</li><li>At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.</li><li>All positions subject to close without notice.</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Intermountain Health Primary Childrens Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Post Acute Care Nurse-RN/Physician Office]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://sih.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/SIH_External/job/Logan-Primary-Care-Herrin/Post-Acute-Care-Nurse-RN-Physician-Office_JR100671-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>locations</li><li>Logan Primary Care-Herrin</li><li>Nursing Homes</li><li>time type</li><li>Full time</li><li>posted on</li><li>Posted Today</li><li>job requisition id</li><li>JR100671</li><li>Current SIH employees need to apply for positions through our internal job portal. Log in to Workday to apply through the Jobs Hub.</li><li>Location: Herrin, IL</li><li>Shift: Days</li><li>Time Type: Full Time</li><li>Facility/Clinic Name: Logan Primary Care - Herrin</li><li>Position Summary</li><li>The Post Acute Care nurse provides office support for all Post-Acute Care Providers as a liaison between providers, facilities, patients, and families.</li><li>This role focuses on managing the care of patients who are in nursing homes following a hospital discharge, ensuring continuity of care during the transition from hospital to post-acute settings.</li><li>The ideal candidate will work closely with healthcare providers, nursing staff, and families to ensure the continuity of care for patients who require specialized attention after their hospital stay.</li></ul><ul><li>Education</li><li>Associates Degree in Nursing</li></ul><ul><li>Licenses and Certification</li><li>Current Illinois Registered Nurse License</li><li>BLS Certification</li></ul><ul><li>Experience and Skills</li><li>EPIC and a working knowledge of Post Acute Care facility EMRs</li><li>Experience in Post Acute Care or working within skilled nursing facilities.</li><li>Strong understanding of the medical needs and treatment plans for patients in nursing homes.</li><li>Excellent communication and team collaboration skills.</li><li>Role Specific Responsibilities</li><li>Assess and plan patient care needs</li><li>Assist provider in Post Acute Care office setting</li><li>Place orders and referrals and provide follow up</li><li>Field and triage incoming patient and family calls</li><li>Answer time-sensitive fax</li><li>Communicate effectively with families, caregivers, and multidisciplinary teams to keep all parties informed on the patient’s condition and progress.</li><li>Be point of contact for distributing lab results and orders to facility nurses</li><li>Some travel required</li><li>Compensation (Commensurate with experience):</li><li>$26.50 - $41.61</li><li>To access our Benefits Guide/Plan Information, please click the link below:</li><li>http://www.sih.net/careers/benefits</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[2 Locations]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Southern Illinois Healthcare (SIH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[ICU registered nurse Part time days]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://methodisthealth.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MLH/job/Methodist-North-Hospital/ICU-registered-nurse-Part-time-days_R-7937-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>remote type<br />On Campus<br />locations<br />Methodist North Hospital<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R-7937<br />If you are looking to make an impact on a meaningful scale, come join us as we embrace the Power of One!<br /> We strive to be an employer of choice and establish a reputation for being a talent rich organization where Associates can grow their career caring for others. For over a century, we’ve served the health care needs of the people of Memphis and the Mid-South.<br /> ICU RN Part time Days 7am-7pm with alternating weekends</p><p>Working at MLH means carrying the mission forward of caring for our community and impacting the lives of patients in every way through compassion, a deliberate focus on service expectations and a consistent thriving for excellence.</p><p>A Brief Overview<br />Responsible for delivering and coordinating nursing care for patients within a multidisciplinary team, utilizing the nursing process to ensure comprehensive, high-quality care. Provides compassionate, patient-centered care while supporting patients and families through emotional challenges and crises. Prioritizes patient safety and strives for optimal care outcomes through evidence-based practice. Educates and advocates for both patients and their families, empowering them with the knowledge and resources needed for treatment and self-care. Demonstrates professionalism and upholds the MLH Mission, Vision, and Values, serving as a role model for excellence in nursing practice.</p><p>What you will do<br />Conducts comprehensive nursing assessments to determine appropriate interventions and develop individualized care plans.<br />Provides patient and family education on care plans, medications, and self-care strategies.<br />Develops, implements, and adjusts personalized patient care plans based on ongoing clinical assessments.<br />Administers medications safely, following best practices in medication management.<br />Collaborates with interdisciplinary teams to ensure coordinated, high-quality patient care.</p><p>Education Qualifications<br />Post-Graduate Certificate or Diploma Nursing - RN<br />Preferred: Bachelor's Degree Nursing - RN<br />Experience Qualifications<br />Minimum of 6 months RN experience<br />Preferred: Greater than 1 year experience in similar clinical setting<br />Skills and Abilities<br />Comprehensive understanding of patient care, including the ability to conduct thorough assessments using the nursing process.<br />Strong knowledge of the Nurse Practice Act and the scope of practice for a Registered Nurse.<br />Ability to process complex clinical information using critical thinking to develop, implement, and support individualized care plans.<br />Ability to effectively delegate tasks to team members, ensuring a collaborative, team-based approach to delivering high-quality patient care.<br />Familiarity with healthcare technology that enhances patient safety and care efficiency (e.g., bar code scanning, electronic health records).<br />Licenses and Certifications<br />BASIC LIFE SUPPORT - American Heart Association<br />Registered Nurse Tennessee - Tennessee Board of Nursing<br />Preferred: Certification in clinical specialty<br />Supervision Provided by this Position<br />The Registered Nurse directs and delegates all patient care activities on nursing units.<br />Physical Demands<br />The physical activities of this position may include climbing, pushing, standing, hearing, walking, reaching, grasping, kneeling, stooping, and repetitive motion.<br />Must have good balance and coordination.<br />The physical requirements of this position are: medium work - exerting up to 50 lbs. of force occasionally and/or up to 25 lbs. of force frequently.<br />The Associate is required to have close visual acuity including color, depth perception, and field of vision to perform an activity, such as assessing patients, preparing and analyzing data and figures; transcribing; viewing a computer terminal; or extensive reading.<br />Frequent invasive and non-invasive patient contact.<br />Exposure to patient body fluids as well as exposure to hazardous or poisonous materials.<br />Ability to react quickly to emergency situations.<br />Our Associates are passionate about what they do, the service they provide and the patients they serve. We value family, team and a Power of One culture that requires commitment to the highest standards of care and unity.</p><p>Boasting one of the South's largest medical centers, Memphis blends a friendly community, a thriving and growing downtown, and a low cost of living. We see each day as a new opportunity to make a difference in the lives of the people in our community.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Methodist North Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Methodist Le Bonheur Healthcare]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) - Le Bonheur Pediatric Inpatient Unit - Nights - Full-Time]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://methodisthealth.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/MLH/job/Le-Bonheur-Childrens-Inpatient-Unit---Jackson-Madison-County-General-Hospital/Registered-Nurse--RN----Le-Bonheur-Pediatric-Inpatient-Unit---Nights---Full-Time_R-9546?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>remote type<br />On Campus<br />locations<br />Le Bonheur Children's Inpatient Unit - Jackson-Madison County General Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R-9546<br />If you are looking to make an impact on a meaningful scale, come join us as we embrace the Power of One!<br /> We strive to be an employer of choice and establish a reputation for being a talent rich organization where Associates can grow their career caring for others. For over a century, we’ve served the health care needs of the people of Memphis and the Mid-South.<br /> Are you a nurse with a passion for pediatrics? The Le Bonheur Pediatric Inpatient Med/Surg Unit is the ideal place for you to thrive! Located within Jackson-Madison County General Hospital, this unit offers a beautiful, bright culture where you can make a meaningful impact on the lives of pediatric patients.  You'll be part of a dedicated team that shares your love for working with children, providing exceptional care in a supportive and vibrant environment. This is a fantastic opportunity to grow your career while making a difference in the lives of young patients and their families.</p><p>Working at MLH means carrying the mission forward of caring for our community and impacting the lives of patients in every way through compassion, a deliberate focus on service expectations and a consistent thriving for excellence.</p><p>A Brief Overview<br />Responsible for delivering and coordinating nursing care for patients within a multidisciplinary team, utilizing the nursing process to ensure comprehensive, high-quality care. Provides compassionate, patient-centered care while supporting patients and families through emotional challenges and crises. Prioritizes patient safety and strives for optimal care outcomes through evidence-based practice. Educates and advocates for both patients and their families, empowering them with the knowledge and resources needed for treatment and self-care. Demonstrates professionalism and upholds the MLH Mission, Vision, and Values, serving as a role model for excellence in nursing practice.</p><p>What you will do<br />Conducts comprehensive nursing assessments to determine appropriate interventions and develop individualized care plans.<br />Provides patient and family education on care plans, medications, and self-care strategies.<br />Develops, implements, and adjusts personalized patient care plans based on ongoing clinical assessments.<br />Administers medications safely, following best practices in medication management.<br />Collaborates with interdisciplinary teams to ensure coordinated, high-quality patient care.</p><p>Education Qualifications<br />Post-Graduate Certificate or Diploma Nursing - RN<br />Preferred: Bachelor's Degree Nursing - RN<br />Experience Qualifications<br />Minimum of 6 months RN experience<br />Preferred: Greater than 1 year experience in similar clinical setting<br />Skills and Abilities<br />Comprehensive understanding of patient care, including the ability to conduct thorough assessments using the nursing process.<br />Strong knowledge of the Nurse Practice Act and the scope of practice for a Registered Nurse.<br />Ability to process complex clinical information using critical thinking to develop, implement, and support individualized care plans.<br />Ability to effectively delegate tasks to team members, ensuring a collaborative, team-based approach to delivering high-quality patient care.<br />Familiarity with healthcare technology that enhances patient safety and care efficiency (e.g., bar code scanning, electronic health records).<br />Licenses and Certifications<br />BASIC LIFE SUPPORT - American Heart Association<br />Registered Nurse Tennessee - Tennessee Board of Nursing<br />Preferred: Certification in clinical specialty<br />Supervision Provided by this Position<br />The Registered Nurse directs and delegates all patient care activities on nursing units.<br />Physical Demands<br />The physical activities of this position may include climbing, pushing, standing, hearing, walking, reaching, grasping, kneeling, stooping, and repetitive motion.<br />Must have good balance and coordination.<br />The physical requirements of this position are: medium work - exerting up to 50 lbs. of force occasionally and/or up to 25 lbs. of force frequently.<br />The Associate is required to have close visual acuity including color, depth perception, and field of vision to perform an activity, such as assessing patients, preparing and analyzing data and figures; transcribing; viewing a computer terminal; or extensive reading.<br />Frequent invasive and non-invasive patient contact.<br />Exposure to patient body fluids as well as exposure to hazardous or poisonous materials.<br />Ability to react quickly to emergency situations.<br />Our Associates are passionate about what they do, the service they provide and the patients they serve. We value family, team and a Power of One culture that requires commitment to the highest standards of care and unity.</p><p>Boasting one of the South's largest medical centers, Memphis blends a friendly community, a thriving and growing downtown, and a low cost of living. We see each day as a new opportunity to make a difference in the lives of the people in our community.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Le Bonheur Children's Inpatient Unit - Jackson-Madison County General Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Methodist Le Bonheur Healthcare]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) Day Shift Med/Surg/Ortho]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-St-Lukes-South-Shore---5900-S-Lake-Dr/Registered-Nurse--RN--Day-Shift--Med-Surg-Ortho_R150229?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora St Lukes South Shore - 5900 S Lake Dr<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R150229<br />Department:<br />35811 Aurora St. Lukes South Shore - Med Surg: IU 3rd Floor<br />Status: <br />Full time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />36<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />07-1930 or 07-1530 dependent on needs. Every third weekend rotation, scheduled as needed, every other holiday<br />3MESG is a true Medical/Surgical Unit.  <br />At South Shore 3MESG cares for the majority of surgical patients.  <br />We see a wide variety of ortho and general surgeries, like total knee replacements, bowel resections, lap choles, and amputations.  <br />We also get a wide variety of medical patients, like alcohol withdrawal, pneumonia, anemia, DKA, you name it!  Will see stable pediatric patients aged 16 and older.<br />You will see a very diverse population with many different diagnoses. <br />Our average daily census is 28 patients, with our unit being 33 beds.  <br />It is fast paced, busy, and diverse, which makes 3MESG a great unit to work on and if you haven’t heard already “it’s cooler at the shore!"<br />Looking for novice and experienced RN, Newly Licensed Nurses and Graduate Nurses passionate about nursing care, service and health equity.<br />NEW - Loan forgiveness up to $20,000<br />$5 Sign on Bonus<br />Up to $7,200 Education Assistance <br />Minutes from Grant Park Beach, South Shore beach , and McKinley Beach great for walking after work or enjoying the outdoors<br />Responsible for providing and coordinating comprehensive patient care through the nursing process to deliver safe, therapeutic care in accordance with established standards, policies and procedures. Using evidence-based practice, clinical decision making, compassion and skilled communication, leads efforts to create the safest patient environment and the best patient experience across the continuum.<br />Uses the nursing process to assess the needs of the patient, plan and implement individualized interventions and evaluate the effectiveness of the plan of care. Includes the patient and family in planning and implementing care and develops and maintains a therapeutic relationship throughout the healthcare continuum.<br />Anticipates and recognizes significant changes in the patient’s condition, status, and need for care. Provides ongoing assessment of the patient and takes appropriate actions when changes occur. Anticipates and alters the plan of care as needed, mobilizes appropriate resources, and collaborates with other health care team members to coordinate patient centered care.<br />Implements strategies to reduce patient risk and increase patient safety. Assesses patient and family readiness to learn and individualizes the approach as necessary. Works collaboratively to develop strategies to meet the learning needs of the patient and family.<br />Actively coordinates the discharge plan utilizing an interdisciplinary approach. Applies evidence-based practice to deliver patient care. Consistently incorporates nursing and regulatory standards of care into practice.<br />Provides ongoing evaluation of patient, team, and unit outcomes and is empowered to take appropriate action when changes are needed. Supports shared governance activities and initiatives to improve processes and patient outcomes.<br />Demonstrates effective communication, feedback, and conflict resolution skills. Promotes collaboration among healthcare team members. Assumes a leadership role in the care team and delegates appropriately to unlicensed personnel.<br />Promotes a culture of safety through identifying threats to patient safety and intervening to prevent patient harm. Reports patient safety events and near misses in a timely manner. Seeks to identify potential safety issues and assists in the implementation of corrective actions.<br />Applies ethical decision making, demonstrates respect and understanding for peers, and other clinical disciplines. Participates as an effective member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated, unbiased, individualized approach to care.<br />Participates in quality/process improvement initiatives to improve the functions of the department and the patient care experience.<br />Participates in professional activities which contribute to personal professional development and the development of others. Seeks opportunities to be taught, coached, and mentored. Attends required meetings/educational programs and completes annual competencies in a timely manner.<br />Must be able to demonstrate knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patients served. Must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient's status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to his/her age-specific needs, and to provide the care needed as described in the department's policies and procedures. Age-specific information is developed further in the departmental job standards.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Registered Nurse license issued by the state in which the team member practices, and<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Providers certification issued by the American Heart Association (AHA).</p><p>Education Required:<br />Completion of an accredited or approved program in Nursing.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />Typically requires 1 year of experience in clinical nursing.</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Demonstrates progression to provide holistic patient care and the ability to view clinical situations from a patient and family focus.<br />Demonstrates progression to recognize situational changes that require unplanned or unanticipated interventions, and responds to situations with confidence, timeliness and flexibility.<br />Proficient computer skills, use of electronic mail and electronic medical records systems.<br />Excellent communication (written and verbal), listening and interpersonal skills.<br />Demonstrates human relation skills with the ability to develop rapport and maintain positive, professional relationships with a variety of patients, team members and physicians. Ability to take initiative and work collaboratively with others.<br />Demonstrated ability to effectively make critical, independent decisions.<br />Excellent organization, prioritization and problem-solving skills.<br />Demonstrates time management skills with an ability to multi-task and prioritize in an environment with frequent interruptions.<br />Demonstrates coordination, collaboration, delegation and team building skills.<br />Certification Addendum<br />Team members will maintain annual educational requirements for hospital based certifications (e.g. DNV, CARF or others).</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, reach above shoulders, and twist frequently throughout the workday.<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 50 lbs. from floor to waist.<br />lift up to 20 lbs. over the head.<br />carry up to 40 lbs. a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 30 lbs. of force.<br />perform a sliding transfer of 150 lbs. with a second person present.<br />Position requires use of foot pedals on carts or machines.<br />May be exposed to chemical and hazardous waste as well as blood and body fluids and communicable disease. Therefore, protective clothing and equipment must be worn as necessary.<br />Must have functional speech, vision, hearing, and touch with ability to use fine hand manipulation skills for IV insertion and other procedures/functions.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$37.50 - $56.25<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora St Lukes South Shore - 5900 S Lake Dr]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Medical Assistant Family Practice Kenosha]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Kenosha-WI---10222-74th-St/Medical-Assistant-Family-Practice-Kenosha_R150419?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Kenosha, WI - 10222 74th St<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R150419<br />Department:<br />01120 AMG 74th Street - Family Medicine<br />Status: <br />Full time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />40<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Monday-Friday, schedule TBD, 40 hours per week, no weekends.<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Prepares and rooms the patient for exam by obtaining vital signs and gathering/documenting/updating pertinent health information (i.e., chief complaint, allergies, and/or medications). Monitors and completes Clinical Integration/ Quality Improvement measures with notification to clinician for opportunities within their scope.<br />Performs laboratory procedures (i.e., strep test, wound culture, specimen collection, etc.) using principles of aseptic technique and standard precautions/infection control guidelines.<br />Assists the Physician/ Advanced Practice Professional (APP) with procedures  such as pelvic exams, allergy scratch testing, EMG, cautery, colposcopy, etc.<br />Administers routine medications, under Physician/ APP orders or medical group approved standing orders/protocols, which may include but are not limited to immunizations, antibiotics, vitamins, and topical agents.<br />Follows through with necessary procedure or test requests, pre-approved care algorithms, new appointment times and referrals to other facilities or services. Refers questions to Registered Nurses and Physician/APC per scope of practice guidelines and relays information back to patient as directed.<br />Communicates with Physician/APP and other members of the health care team to ensure smooth clinic flow and adjusts as necessary.  Effectively communicates accurate and timely information with the patient.<br />May perform basic and advanced clinical support tasks or skills based on the specialty and appropriate   competencies such as but not limited to removal of sutures and staples, laboratory procedures (throat/nose culture, drug screen), phlebotomy - butterfly, venous heel stick, EKG, spirometry, Holter monitor application, prescription refills using approved protocols, etc., under clinical supervision.<br />Must be able to demonstrate knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patients served.  Must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient's status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to his/her age-specific needs, and to provide the care needed as described in the department's policies and procedures.  Age-specific information is developed further in the departmental job standards.<br />Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Providers certification issued by the American Heart Association (AHA) needs to be obtained within 45 days unless department leader has determined it is not required.<br />Education Required:<br />GED or HS Equivalency Diploma.<br />Completion of an accredited or approved program in Medical Assistant, or 2 years of verifiable full-time experience as a Medical Assistant within the last 5 years.<br />Experience Required:<br />No experience required<br />Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Ability to perform routine and complex technical skills, within the Medical Assistant scope of practice after demonstrated competency.<br />Excellent communication and interpersonal skills; ability to develop rapport and maintain positive, professional relationships with a variety of patients, team members and physicians.<br />Proficient computer skills including keyboarding, navigation within a windows operating system, and use of electronic mail with exposure to electronic medical records systems.<br />Demonstrates customer service skills that support a positive patient experience.<br />Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, twist, crawl, kneel, climb, and reach above shoulders throughout the workday.<br />Ability to lift 35 pounds without assistance.  For patient lifts over 35 pounds, or when patient is unable to assist with lift, patient handling equipment is expected to be used, with at least one other team member, when available.<br />Unique patient lifting/movement situations will be assessed on a case- by -case basis.<br />Must have functional speech, vision, hearing, and touch with ability to use fine-hand manipulation skills. <br />Will be exposed to the following hazards on a frequent basis: mechanical, electrical, chemical, blood and body fluids.  Will be required to wear protective clothing and equipment as needed. <br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.<br />This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$21.45 - $32.20<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Kenosha, WI - 10222 74th St]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) - Float Pool]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-Medical-Center-Grafton---975-Port-Washington-Rd/Registered-Nurse--RN----Float-Pool_R138386?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora Medical Center Grafton - 975 Port Washington Rd<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R138386<br />Department:<br />34102 AMC Grafton - Nursing Float Pool<br />Status: <br />Full time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />32<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Flexible scheduling. Weekend and Holiday requirements. 15-23 and 15-03 flexibility.<br />Aurora continues to offer leading benefits, and a competitive wage program to help you live your best life! In addition:<br />ExCEL Nursing Professional Development with financial incentives<br />Sign on Bonuses (based on FTE, for new hire RNs)<br />Student Loan Forgiveness<br />Nursing Education /Tuition Assistance<br />Generous RN Referral program<br />Shift and Float differentials <br />Benefits begin DAY ONE<br />Join our dynamic float pool team at Grafton where you will have the opportunity to support our inpatient units growing your professional career within multiple specialty areas, including but not limited to cardiac/neuro, cardiothoracic, medical, oncology, GI, ortho, surgical, observation, and progressive care.<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Uses the nursing process to assess the needs of the patient, plan and implement individualized interventions and evaluate the effectiveness of the plan of care. Includes the patient and family in planning and implementing care and develops and maintains a therapeutic relationship throughout the healthcare continuum.<br />Anticipates and recognizes significant changes in the patient’s condition, status, and need for care. Provides ongoing assessment of the patient and takes appropriate actions when changes occur. Anticipates and alters the plan of care as needed, mobilizes appropriate resources, and collaborates with other health care team members to coordinate patient centered care.<br />Implements strategies to reduce patient risk and increase patient safety. Assesses patient and family readiness to learn and individualizes the approach as necessary. Works collaboratively to develop strategies to meet the learning needs of the patient and family.<br />Actively coordinates the discharge plan utilizing an interdisciplinary approach. Applies evidence-based practice to deliver patient care. Consistently incorporates nursing and regulatory standards of care into practice.<br />Provides ongoing evaluation of patient, team, and unit outcomes and is empowered to take appropriate action when changes are needed. Supports shared governance activities and initiatives to improve processes and patient outcomes.<br />Demonstrates effective communication, feedback, and conflict resolution skills. Promotes collaboration among healthcare team members. Assumes a leadership role in the care team and delegates appropriately to unlicensed personnel.<br />Promotes a culture of safety through identifying threats to patient safety and intervening to prevent patient harm. Reports patient safety events and near misses in a timely manner. Seeks to identify potential safety issues and assists in the implementation of corrective actions.<br />Applies ethical decision making, demonstrates respect and understanding for peers, and other clinical disciplines. Participates as an effective member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated, unbiased, individualized approach to care.<br />Participates in quality/process improvement initiatives to improve the functions of the department and the patient care experience.<br />Participates in professional activities which contribute to personal professional development and the development of others. Seeks opportunities to be taught, coached, and mentored. Attends required meetings/educational programs and completes annual competencies in a timely manner.<br />Must be able to demonstrate knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patients served. Must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient's status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to his/her age-specific needs, and to provide the care needed as described in the department's policies and procedures. Age-specific information is developed further in the departmental job standards.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Registered Nurse license issued by the state in which the team member practices, and<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Providers certification issued by the American Heart Association (AHA).</p><p>Education Required:<br />Completion of an accredited or approved program in Nursing.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />Typically requires 1 year of experience in clinical nursing.</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Demonstrates progression to provide holistic patient care and the ability to view clinical situations from a patient and family focus.<br />Demonstrates progression to recognize situational changes that require unplanned or unanticipated interventions, and responds to situations with confidence, timeliness and flexibility.<br />Proficient computer skills, use of electronic mail and electronic medical records systems.<br />Excellent communication (written and verbal), listening and interpersonal skills.<br />Demonstrates human relation skills with the ability to develop rapport and maintain positive, professional relationships with a variety of patients, team members and physicians. Ability to take initiative and work collaboratively with others.<br />Demonstrated ability to effectively make critical, independent decisions.<br />Excellent organization, prioritization and problem-solving skills.<br />Demonstrates time management skills with an ability to multi-task and prioritize in an environment with frequent interruptions.<br />Demonstrates coordination, collaboration, delegation and team building skills.<br />Certification Addendum<br />Team members will maintain annual educational requirements for hospital based certifications (e.g. DNV, CARF or others).</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, reach above shoulders, and twist frequently throughout the workday.<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 50 lbs. from floor to waist.<br />lift up to 20 lbs. over the head.<br />carry up to 40 lbs. a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 30 lbs. of force.<br />perform a sliding transfer of 150 lbs. with a second person present.<br />Position requires use of foot pedals on carts or machines.<br />May be exposed to chemical and hazardous waste as well as blood and body fluids and communicable disease. Therefore, protective clothing and equipment must be worn as necessary.<br />Must have functional speech, vision, hearing, and touch with ability to use fine hand manipulation skills for IV insertion and other procedures/functions.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$37.50 - $56.25<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora Medical Center Grafton - 975 Port Washington Rd]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) - Pre/Post Surgery Center]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Green-Bay-WI---2253-W-Mason-St/Registered-Nurse--RN----Pre-Post-Surgery-Center_R152358?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Green Bay, WI - 2253 W Mason St<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R152358<br />Department:<br />70101 BayCare Leased Employees - Surgery Center: West Side<br />Status: <br />Part time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />24<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Monday - Thursday (will be scheduled to work 3 days within Monday - Thursday)<br />Hours of operation are 0600-1700. Scheduled hours are based on the needs of the department; candidate will need to be flexible with hours assigned.<br />Will be required to work one/two days "late' or until the last patient is discharged from the facility.<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Uses the nursing process to assess the needs of the patient, plan and implement individualized interventions and evaluate the effectiveness of the plan of care. Includes the patient and family in planning and implementing care and develops and maintains a therapeutic relationship throughout the healthcare continuum.<br />Anticipates and recognizes significant changes in the patient’s condition, status, and need for care. Provides ongoing assessment of the patient and takes appropriate actions when changes occur. Anticipates and alters the plan of care as needed, mobilizes appropriate resources, and collaborates with other health care team members to coordinate patient centered care.<br />Implements strategies to reduce patient risk and increase patient safety. Assesses patient and family readiness to learn and individualizes the approach as necessary. Works collaboratively to develop strategies to meet the learning needs of the patient and family.<br />Actively coordinates the discharge plan utilizing an interdisciplinary approach. Applies evidence-based practice to deliver patient care. Consistently incorporates nursing and regulatory standards of care into practice.<br />Provides ongoing evaluation of patient, team, and unit outcomes and is empowered to take appropriate action when changes are needed. Supports shared governance activities and initiatives to improve processes and patient outcomes.<br />Demonstrates effective communication, feedback, and conflict resolution skills. Promotes collaboration among healthcare team members. Assumes a leadership role in the care team and delegates appropriately to unlicensed personnel.<br />Promotes a culture of safety through identifying threats to patient safety and intervening to prevent patient harm. Reports patient safety events and near misses in a timely manner. Seeks to identify potential safety issues and assists in the implementation of corrective actions.<br />Applies ethical decision making, demonstrates respect and understanding for peers, and other clinical disciplines. Participates as an effective member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated, unbiased, individualized approach to care.<br />Participates in quality/process improvement initiatives to improve the functions of the department and the patient care experience.<br />Participates in professional activities which contribute to personal professional development and the development of others. Seeks opportunities to be taught, coached, and mentored. Attends required meetings/educational programs and completes annual competencies in a timely manner.<br />Must be able to demonstrate knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patients served. Must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient's status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to his/her age-specific needs, and to provide the care needed as described in the department's policies and procedures. Age-specific information is developed further in the departmental job standards.<br />Additional Details: <br />Monday - Thursday (will be scheduled to work 3 days within Monday - Thursday)<br />Hours of operation are 0600-1700. Scheduled hours are based on the needs of the department; candidate will need to be flexible with hours assigned.<br />Will be required to work one/two days "late' or until the last patient is discharged from the facility.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Registered Nurse license issued by the state in which the team member practices, and<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Providers certification issued by the American Heart Association (AHA).<br />Education Required:<br />Completion of an accredited or approved program in Nursing.<br />Experience Required:<br />Typically requires 1 year of experience in clinical nursing.<br />Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Demonstrates progression to recognize situational changes that require unplanned or unanticipated interventions, and responds to situations with confidence, timeliness and flexibility.<br />Proficient computer skills, use of electronic mail and electronic medical records systems.<br />Excellent communication (written and verbal), listening and interpersonal skills.<br />Demonstrates human relation skills with the ability to develop rapport and maintain positive, professional relationships with a variety of patients, team members and physicians. Ability to take initiative and work collaboratively with others.<br />Demonstrated ability to effectively make critical, independent decisions.<br />Excellent organization, prioritization and problem-solving skills.<br />Demonstrates time management skills with an ability to multi-task and prioritize in an environment with frequent interruptions.<br />Demonstrates coordination, collaboration, delegation and team building skills.<br />Certification Addendum<br />Team members will maintain annual educational requirements for hospital based certifications (e.g. DNV, CARF or others).<br />Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, reach above shoulders, and twist frequently throughout the workday.<br />lift up to 50 lbs. from floor to waist.<br />lift up to 20 lbs. over the head.<br />carry up to 40 lbs. a reasonable distance.<br />push/pull with 30 lbs. of force.<br />perform a sliding transfer of 150 lbs. with a second person present.<br />Position requires use of foot pedals on carts or machines.<br />May be exposed to chemical and hazardous waste as well as blood and body fluids and communicable disease. Therefore, protective clothing and equipment must be worn as necessary.<br />Must have functional speech, vision, hearing, and touch with ability to use fine hand manipulation skills for IV insertion and other procedures/functions.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.<br />This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$34.90 - $52.35<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Green Bay, WI - 2253 W Mason St]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse (RN) OR Neuro at St. Lukes]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-St-Lukes-Medical-Center---2900-W-Oklahoma-Ave/Registered-Nurse--RN--OR-Neuro-at-St-Lukes_R143915?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>locations</li><li>Aurora St Lukes Medical Center - 2900 W Oklahoma Ave</li><li>time type</li><li>Full time</li><li>posted on</li><li>Posted Today</li><li>job requisition id</li><li>R143915</li><li>Department:</li><li>Aurora St. Lukes Medical Center - Surgery Room</li><li>Status:</li><li>Full time</li><li>Benefits Eligible:</li><li>Yes</li><li>Hours Per Week:</li><li></li><li>Schedule Details/Additional Information:</li><li>Neuro Specialty</li><li>Monday through Friday 8 hour day shift with variable start times between 530am and 7am</li><li>On-Call requirements Holidays, weekends and week night rotation</li><li>Must Live within 30 minutes of SLMC for call requirement</li><li>Responsible for providing and coordinating comprehensive patient care through the nursing process to deliver safe, therapeutic care in accordance with established standards, policies and procedures. Using evidence-based practice, clinical decision making, compassion and skilled communication, leads efforts to create the safest patient environment and the best patient experience across the continuum.</li></ul><p>Uses the nursing process to assess the needs of the patient, plan and implement individualized interventions and evaluate the effectiveness of the plan of care. Includes the patient and family in planning and implementing care and develops and maintains a therapeutic relationship throughout the healthcare continuum.<br />Anticipates and recognizes significant changes in the patient’s condition, status, and need for care. Provides ongoing assessment of the patient and takes appropriate actions when changes occur. Anticipates and alters the plan of care as needed, mobilizes appropriate resources, and collaborates with other health care team members to coordinate patient centered care.<br />Implements strategies to reduce patient risk and increase patient safety. Assesses patient and family readiness to learn and individualizes the approach as necessary. Works collaboratively to develop strategies to meet the learning needs of the patient and family.<br />Actively coordinates the discharge plan utilizing an interdisciplinary approach. Applies evidence-based practice to deliver patient care. Consistently incorporates nursing and regulatory standards of care into practice.<br />Provides ongoing evaluation of patient, team, and unit outcomes and is empowered to take appropriate action when changes are needed. Supports shared governance activities and initiatives to improve processes and patient outcomes.<br />Demonstrates effective communication, feedback, and conflict resolution skills. Promotes collaboration among healthcare team members. Assumes a leadership role in the care team and delegates appropriately to unlicensed personnel.<br />Promotes a culture of safety through identifying threats to patient safety and intervening to prevent patient harm. Reports patient safety events and near misses in a timely manner. Seeks to identify potential safety issues and assists in the implementation of corrective actions.<br />Applies ethical decision making, demonstrates respect and understanding for peers, and other clinical disciplines. Participates as an effective member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated, unbiased, individualized approach to care.<br />Participates in quality/process improvement initiatives to improve the functions of the department and the patient care experience.<br />Participates in professional activities which contribute to personal professional development and the development of others. Seeks opportunities to be taught, coached, and mentored. Attends required meetings/educational programs and completes annual competencies in a timely manner.<br />Scheduled Hours <br />Neuro Specialty, Monday through Friday 8 hour day shift with variable start times between 530am and 7am<br />Holiday,weekend and week night On-Call requirements <br />Must Live within 30 minutes of call <br />Licenses & Certifications<br />Registered Nurse license issued by the state in which the team member practices, and<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Providers certification issued by the American Heart Association (AHA). <br />Degrees<br />Completion of an accredited or approved program in Nursing. <br />Required Functional Experience<br />Typically requires 1 year of experience in clinical nursing.<br />Knowledge, Skills & Abilities<br />Demonstrates progression to provide holistic patient care and the ability to view clinical situations from a patient and family focus.Demonstrates progression to recognize situational changes that require unplanned or unanticipated interventions, and responds to situations with confidence, timeliness and flexibility.Proficient computer skills, use of electronic mail and electronic medical records systems.Excellent communication (written and verbal), listening and interpersonal skills.Demonstrates human relation skills with the ability to develop rapport and maintain positive, professional relationships with a variety of patients, team members and physicians. Ability to take initiative and work collaboratively with others.Demonstrated ability to effectively make critical, independent decisions.Excellent organization, prioritization and problem-solving skills.Demonstrates time management skills with an ability to multi-task and prioritize in an environment with frequent interruptions.Demonstrates coordination, collaboration, delegation and team building skills.Certification AddendumTeam members will maintain annual educational requirements for hospital based certifications (e.g. DNV, CARF or others).<br />Pay Range<br />$37.50 - $56.25<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora St Lukes Medical Center - 2900 W Oklahoma Ave]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Licensed Practical Nurse (LPN) - Home Health - Chicago North City]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Advocate-Illinois-Masonic-Medical-Center---836-W-Wellington-Ave/Licensed-Practical-Nurse--LPN----Home-Health---Chicago-North-City_R135639-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Advocate Illinois Masonic Medical Center - 836 W Wellington Ave<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R135639<br />Department:<br />34100 Central Metro C - Nursing<br />Status: <br />Full time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />40<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Position services City of Chicago. Areas include 60641, 50534, Norridge, 60656, Norridge,Northlake, Elmwood Park, Schiller Park and surrounding areas.<br />LPN - Home Health<br />Location:  Position services City of Chicago. Areas include 60641, 50534, Norridge, 60656, Norridge, Northlake, Elmwood Park, Schiller Park and surrounding areas.<br />Hours: Days with wkd rotation<br />This position is eligible for up to a $5000.00 sign on bonus.  You must be employed in the exact position at time of payout.  Internal team members are not eligible for this sign on bonus at this time.<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Assuring/Improving Quality of Care: Facilitates the patient and family's right to receive quality cost-effective care following Advocates MVP of Stewardship. Working under the direction and supervision of the RN.<br />    1)Utilizes appropriate resources in response to situations that have the potential to negatively impact patient and family outcomes.<br />    2)Adapts practice to the latest standards according to evidence-based literature.<br />    3)Participates in efforts to reduce risk and improve patient safety.<br />    4)Consistently demonstrates the ability to thoroughly and decisively document to support reimbursement and regulatory requirements.<br />Care and Service Coordination: Practices as an effective team member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated approach to care following Advocates MVP of Partnership.<br />    1)Recognizes changes in clinical situations. Consults with RN as to action based on observation.<br />    2)Consistently makes sound clinical decisions, demonstrating the ability to care for all patients including those with complex problems.<br />    3)Prioritizes and organizes patient care based on established plan of care, ensures clear hand-off communication to achieve optimal health outcomes for patients, utilizing excellent communication techniques like SBAR and 5P's.<br />    4)Actively participates in interdisciplinary case conferences. (As appropriate based on employment status).<br />Leadership/Collaboration/Professional Development: Demonstrates respect and understanding for peers and other clinical disciplines and participates as an effective team member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated approach to care following the Advocate MVP of Excellence.<br />    2)Utilizes available resources to maintain current knowledge base relevant to practice.<br />    3)Demonstrates effective communication, feedback, and conflict resolution skills, promoting collaboration among team members.<br />    4)Seeks out opportunities to enhance knowledge, skill and competency of self and other department members. (As appropriate based on employment status).<br />    1)Participates in staff meetings, agency in-services, and educational activities to ehance development and support organizational initiatives.<br />Patient Relationship: Develops and maintains a therapeutic relationship throughout the healthcare continuum following Advocates MVP of Compassion<br />    1)Demonstrates adaptive communication styles based on individual patient needs by utilizing motivational interviewing and problem solving techniques.<br />    2)Promotes patient/family knowledge and confidence to safely manage self care, disease process, medications, procedures and infection control prevention.<br />    3)Participates in implementing an individualized approach to the plan of care, which includes assessment of physical, psychosocial, comfort, and wellness needs utilizing SMART goals, under the supervision of the RN.<br />    4)Once plan of care is established by the RN, participates in the ongoing assessment of patient and family readiness and involves them in goal setting, planning, and implementation of care, under the supervision of the RN.<br />    5)Provides care that routinely exceeds patient and family expectations, as measured by survey instruments.<br />    6)Incorporates AHHS Standards of Behavior into interactions with patients, other associates, and physicians.<br />Business Development and Growth: Demonstrates behaviors that enhance productivity and an understanding of financial and economic conditions in the health care environment.<br />    1)Demonstrates adherance to personnel and operational policies.<br />    2)Collaborates with RN and implements plans for patient care to maximize efficiencies and conserve resources.<br />    3)Makes suggestions to RN regarding utilization of resources to achieve excellent health outcomes for patients. (As appropriate based one employment status).<br />Patient Education: Demonstrates a commitment to meet the learning needs of patients and their families. Application of a systematic process involving optimal level of self-care for patient and optimal quality of life of patient family and significant other under the supervision of the RN following Advocates MVP of Equality.<br />    1)Assess patient and family readiness to learn and modify approach as needed.<br />    2)Provides and adapts appropriate resource material to achieve educational outcomes, employing health literacy assessments and principles</p><p>Licensure:<br />Nurse, Licensed Practical (LPN)<br />A valid driver’s license issued by the Division of Motor Vehicles.</p><p>Education/Experience Required:<br />Licensed in the State of Illinois (or eligible for licensure) Able to demonstrate compliance with state continuing education requirements. 2 years of Med/Surgical clinical experience, CPR certified</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Basic knowledge of computer use (i.e. Microsoft Word, email access and use). Ability to learn and use computer based scheduling, and documentation system. Ability to communication professionally both verbally and through written reports, with strong documentation skills. Good interpersonal skills. Good time management and self organization skills Proficiency in the ability to obtain lab draws and report results to primary nurse or clinical manager.<br />Current LPN licensure in State of Illinois.</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Extensive travel within geographical boundaries in all extremes of weather and on all types of roads including expressways. Must be able to provide/arrange own transportation to and from patients home and branch offices. Ability to work rotating weekends and holidays. Requires adherence to scheduled days and hours of work based on commitment to patient/client and work load assigned. Ability to attend mandatory informational/education/branch meetings. Work environment includes patient or family homes, or assisted living facilities. Requires full range of body motion including: a. Bending, sitting and standing b. Climbing stairs while carrying objects c. Pulling, pushing, reaching, carrying and lifting: (must be able to lift/carry at minimum 25 pounds) d. Assisting and maintaining patient's safety with ambulation on flat surfaces and stairs; and transferring patients using standard pivot transfers or with use of transfer board or Hoyer lift e. Providing treatment on standard beds in the home environment<br />If position has direct patient care or direct patient contact the following lifting requirement supersedes any previous lifting requirement effective 06/01/2015. Ability to lift up to 35 pounds without assistance. For patient lifts of over 35 pounds, or when patient is unable to assist with the lift, patient handling equipment is expected to be used, with at least one other associate, when available. Unique patient lifting/movement situations will be assessed on a case-by-case basis.<br />COMPENSATION: $24.35-$36.55 per hour<br />We want our teammates and their families to Live Well. Actual compensation offered in the Pay Range will be based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience and/or training and internal equity. To accompany base pay, we offer a comprehensive benefits package including<br />Sign on Bonus eligible (external candidates)<br />Competitive Pay<br />Referral Bonus Programs<br />Tuition Assistance Available<br />Mileage reimbursement</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$24.85 - $37.30<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Advocate Illinois Masonic Medical Center - 836 W Wellington Ave]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Nurse - Pre Surgical Testing Full Time]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Advocate-Condell-Medical-Center---801-S-Milwaukee-Ave/Registered-Nurse---Pre-Surgical-Testing-Full-Time_R150853?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Advocate Condell Medical Center - 801 S Milwaukee Ave<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R150853<br />Department:<br />37717 Advocate Condell Medical Center - Presurgical Testing<br />Status: <br />Full time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />40<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Shift will be Monday - Friday from 8:00AM to 4:30PM<br />Condell Medical Center<br />Libertyville, IL<br />Registered Nurse (RN)<br />Registered Nurse (RN) – Pre Surgical Testing<br />Scheduled Hours - 8am to 4:00pm or 9am to 5pm<br />Monday through Friday<br />Hybrid, Work from home and Onsite at Condell<br />Full time<br />40 Hours a week<br />Will eventually service the full Surgical Services Line.<br />Competitive Benefit Package<br />Medical, Dental, Vision, PTO, Tuition Reimbursement<br />Benefits effective on Day 1 of employment!<br />Responsible for providing and coordinating comprehensive patient care through the nursing process to deliver safe, therapeutic care in accordance with established standards, policies and procedures. Using evidence-based practice, clinical decision making, compassion and skilled communication, leads efforts to create the safest patient environment and the best patient experience across the continuum.<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Uses the nursing process to assess the needs of the patient, plan and implement individualized interventions and evaluate the effectiveness of the plan of care. Includes the patient and family in planning and implementing care and develops and maintains a therapeutic relationship throughout the healthcare continuum.<br />Anticipates and recognizes significant changes in the patient’s condition, status, and need for care. Provides ongoing assessment of the patient and takes appropriate actions when changes occur. Anticipates and alters the plan of care as needed, mobilizes appropriate resources, and collaborates with other health care team members to coordinate patient centered care.<br />Implements strategies to reduce patient risk and increase patient safety. Assesses patient and family readiness to learn and individualizes the approach as necessary. Works collaboratively to develop strategies to meet the learning needs of the patient and family.<br />Actively coordinates the discharge plan utilizing an interdisciplinary approach. Applies evidence-based practice to deliver patient care. Consistently incorporates nursing and regulatory standards of care into practice.<br />Provides ongoing evaluation of patient, team, and unit outcomes and is empowered to take appropriate action when changes are needed. Supports shared governance activities and initiatives to improve processes and patient outcomes.<br />Demonstrates effective communication, feedback, and conflict resolution skills. Promotes collaboration among healthcare team members. Assumes a leadership role in the care team and delegates appropriately to unlicensed personnel.<br />Promotes a culture of safety through identifying threats to patient safety and intervening to prevent patient harm. Reports patient safety events and near misses in a timely manner. Seeks to identify potential safety issues and assists in the implementation of corrective actions.<br />Applies ethical decision making, demonstrates respect and understanding for peers, and other clinical disciplines. Participates as an effective member of the patient care team to formulate an integrated, unbiased, individualized approach to care.<br />Participates in quality/process improvement initiatives to improve the functions of the department and the patient care experience.<br />Participates in professional activities which contribute to personal professional development and the development of others. Seeks opportunities to be taught, coached, and mentored. Attends required meetings/educational programs and completes annual competencies in a timely manner.<br />Must be able to demonstrate knowledge and skills necessary to provide care appropriate to the age of the patients served. Must demonstrate knowledge of the principles of growth and development over the life span and possess the ability to assess data reflective of the patient's status and interpret the appropriate information needed to identify each patient's requirements relative to his/her age-specific needs, and to provide the care needed as described in the department's policies and procedures. Age-specific information is developed further in the departmental job standards.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Registered Nurse license issued by the state in which the team member practices, and<br />Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Providers certification issued by the American Heart Association (AHA).</p><p>Education Required:<br />Completion of an accredited or approved program in Nursing.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />Typically requires 1 year of experience in clinical nursing.</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Demonstrates progression to provide holistic patient care and the ability to view clinical situations from a patient and family focus.<br />Demonstrates progression to recognize situational changes that require unplanned or unanticipated interventions, and responds to situations with confidence, timeliness and flexibility.<br />Proficient computer skills, use of electronic mail and electronic medical records systems.<br />Excellent communication (written and verbal), listening and interpersonal skills.<br />Demonstrates human relation skills with the ability to develop rapport and maintain positive, professional relationships with a variety of patients, team members and physicians. Ability to take initiative and work collaboratively with others.<br />Demonstrated ability to effectively make critical, independent decisions.<br />Excellent organization, prioritization and problem-solving skills.<br />Demonstrates time management skills with an ability to multi-task and prioritize in an environment with frequent interruptions.<br />Demonstrates coordination, collaboration, delegation and team building skills.<br />Certification Addendum:<br />Team members will maintain annual educational requirements for hospital based certifications (e.g. DNV, CARF or others)</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, reach above shoulders, and twist frequently throughout the workday.<br />Must be able to:<br />lift up to 50 lbs. from floor to waist.<br />lift up to 20 lbs. over the head.<br />carry up to 40 lbs. a reasonable distance.<br />Must be able to:<br />push/pull with 30 lbs. of force.<br />perform a sliding transfer of 150 lbs. with a second person present.<br />Position requires use of foot pedals on carts or machines.<br />May be exposed to chemical and hazardous waste as well as blood and body fluids and communicable disease. Therefore, protective clothing and equipment must be worn as necessary.<br />Must have functional speech, vision, hearing, and touch with ability to use fine hand manipulation skills for IV insertion and other procedures/functions.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$37.50 - $56.25<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Advocate Condell Medical Center - 801 S Milwaukee Ave]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Director Surgical Services AMCWC]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Aurora-Medical-Center-Washington-County---1032-E-Sumner-St/Director-Surgical-Services-AMCWC_R152097?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>locations<br />Aurora Medical Center Washington County - 1032 E Sumner St<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R152097<br />Department:<br />37703 AMC Washington County - Surgery Room<br />Status: <br />Full time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />Yes<br />Hours Per Week:<br />40<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />N/A<br />Major Responsibilities:<br />Provides safe staffing needs using workload measurement data to clinical judgment. Accountable 24 hours/day for unit operation decisions.<br />Responsible for service assignments for staff based on knowledge, skill and ability.<br />Develops unit budget and ensures cost effective and cost efficient use of resources. Provides input regarding equipment/supply needs, renovations, and environmental issues in preparation of operating and capital equipment budgets.<br />Participates in departmental strategic planning and policy-making. Engages in decision-making through membership on hospital and departmental committees.<br />Promotes communication among patients, families, hospital departments, and medical staff to optimize the interdependence of all team members. Coordinates the needs of physicians and acts as liaison between the medical staff and the nursing staff by serving as a problem solver and mediator.<br />Supports Shared Governance and its functions related to Nursing Evaluation, Peer Review, Policy/Procedures, and Standards of Nursing Practice.<br />Serves as a clinical resource contact for patients, families, nursing staff, other health care members and external agencies.<br />Ensures unit orientation programs meet learning needs of new employees and prepare staff to fulfill requirements of position. Provides for, and coordinates, unit-based educational programs. Assesses staff needs for supervision, resources, and direction.<br />Identifies clinical and professional educational needs to promote staff development. Assists staff to identify personal learning needs.<br />Evaluates the quality of patient care provided in the specialty area through collaboration with unit and organization resource people. Assures policies and procedures are in compliance with those of the Medical Center, the Nursing Department, and regulatory agencies.<br />Performs human resources responsibilities for staff which include interviewing and selection of new employees, promotions, staff development, performance evaluations, compensation changes, resolution of employee concerns, corrective actions, terminations, and overall employee morale.<br />Develops and recommends operating and capital budgets and controls expenditures within approved budget objectives.<br />Responsible for understanding and adhering to the organization's Code of Ethical Conduct and for ensuring that personal actions, and the actions of employees supervised, comply with the policies, regulations and laws applicable to the organization's business.</p><p>Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required:<br />Registered Nurse license issued by the state in which the team member practices.</p><p>Education Required:<br />Bachelor's Degree in Nursing.</p><p>Experience Required:<br />Typically requires 7 years of experience in nursing. Includes 3 years of management experience in patient care services.</p><p>Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Advanced clinical and technical knowledge of the Operating Room.<br />Excellent interpersonal, communication, and problem solving skills. <br />Ability to handle multiple demands simultaneously.</p><p>Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, reach above shoulders and twist frequently during work shift.<br />Will be exposed to the following hazards on a continuous basis: mechanical, electrical, chemical, radiation, blood and body fluids.<br />Will be required to wear gloves, goggles and gowns on an as-needed basis.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.</p><p>This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbent may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$66.85 - $100.30<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Aurora Medical Center Washington County - 1032 E Sumner St]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Advanced Practice Provider - Sleep Medicine Clinic]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://seattlechildrens.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Bellevue-WA/Advanced-Practice-Provider---Sleep-Medicine-Clinic_R2511330?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<ul><li>locations</li><li>Bellevue, WA</li><li>time type</li><li>Part time</li><li>posted on</li><li>Posted Today</li><li>job requisition id</li><li>R2511330</li><li>We are searching for a Nurse Practitioner or Physician Assistant to join our team of 7 physicians and 5 APPs. In this position, you will assume primary responsibility for management of infants, children, and adolescents in outpatient clinic with a variety of sleep concerns including obstructive sleep apnea, insomnia, sleep movement disorders, and hypersomnia's such as Narcolepsy. You will be independently responsible for assessment, diagnosis, evaluation (including ordering procedures such as sleep studies and IV iron), and treatment (including management of PAP, sleep medications, and behavioral sleep interventions). This position is primarily weekdays during daytime hours.</li><li>Required Education and Experience:</li><li>Master's degree in nursing with a concentration in a pediatric or family nurse practitioner program OR graduate of a nationally accredited physician assistant program.</li><li>One year work experience in a pediatric or family focused clinical area.</li><li>Required Credentials:</li><li>For Nurse Practitioners:</li><li>Active, unencumbered registered nurse and advanced registered nurse practitioner licensure in the State of Washington.</li><li>Current national certification as a pediatric or family nurse practitioner</li><li>For Physician Assistants:</li><li>Active, unencumbered physician assistant licensure in the State of Washington</li><li>Initial certification by the National Commission on Certification of Physician Assistants</li><li>For All Providers:</li><li>Active Drug Enforcement Authority registration</li><li>Current American Heart Association Basic Life Support (BLS) for Healthcare Professionals is required at time of hire and to be maintained continuously throughout employment. American Heart Association Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS) will also be accepted in lieu of BLS for Healthcare Professionals.</li><li>Some clinical locations may require American Heart Association Pediatric Life Support training and continuous maintenance of certification.</li><li>Active clinical privileges as an Allied Health Provider at Seattle Children's Hospital must be secured prior to time of hire and must be maintained in good standing and in compliance with all medical staff bylaws, continuously throughout employment.</li><li>Any and all medical or allied health professional staff privileges at Children's will terminate automatically upon the termination of the individual's employment at Children's. Termination of employment does not prohibit the individual from seeking medical or allied health professional staff privileges at Children's as a non-employee in any category for which the individual qualifies. Questions regarding medical or allied health professional staff privileges may be directed to Medical Staff Services.</li><li>Preferred:</li><li>Two years experience in advanced practice provider role</li><li>Two years experience in pediatric health care</li><li>Compensation Range</li><li>$105,456.80 - $155,097.60 per year</li><li>This position is eligible for relocation for qualified candidates.*</li><li>Salary Information</li><li>This compensation range was calculated based on full-time employment (2080 hours worked per calendar year). Offers are determined by multiple factors including equity, skills, experience, and expertise, and may vary within the range provided.</li><li>Disclaimer for Out of State Applicants</li><li>This compensation range is specific to Seattle, positions located outside of Seattle may be compensated differently depending on various factors.</li><li>Benefits Information</li><li>Seattle Children’s offers a generous benefit package, including medical, dental, and vision plans, 403(b), life insurance, paid time off, tuition reimbursement, and more.  Additional details on our benefits can be found on our website www.seattlechildrens.org/careers/benefits.</li><li>About Us</li><li>Hope. Care. Cure. These three simple words capture what we do at Seattle Children’s – to help every child live the healthiest and most fulfilling life possible.  Are you ready to engage with a mission-driven organization that is life-changing to many, and touches the hearts of all? #HOPECARECURE</li><li>Our founding promise to the community is as valid today as it was over a century ago: we will care for all children in our region, regardless of the families’ ability to pay. Together, we deliver superior patient care, advance new discoveries and treatments through pediatric research, and serve as the pediatric and adolescent, academic medical center for Washington, Alaska, Montana and Idaho – the largest region of any children’s hospital in the country.</li><li>U.S. News & World Report consistently ranks Seattle Children’s among the nation’s best children’s hospitals. For more than a decade, Seattle Children’s has been nationally recognized in key specialty areas. We are honored to be one of the nation’s very best places to care for children and the top-ranked pediatric hospital in Washington and the Pacific Northwest.</li><li>As a Magnet designated institution, we recognize the importance of hiring and developing great talent to provide best-in-class care to the patients and families we serve. Our organizational DNA takes form in our core values: Compassion, Excellence, Integrity, Collaboration, Equity and Innovation. Whether it’s delivering frontline care to our patients in a kind and caring manner, practicing the highest standards of quality and safety, or being relentlessly curious as we work towards eradicating childhood diseases, these values are the fabric of our culture and community. The future starts here.</li><li>Our Commitment</li><li>Seattle Children’s welcomes people of all experiences, backgrounds, and thoughts as this is what drives our spirit of inquiry and allows us to better connect with our patients and families. Our organization recruits, employs, trains, compensates, and promotes based on merit without regard to race, religion, color, national origin, gender (including pregnancy, childbirth, or related medical conditions), sexual orientation, gender identity, gender expression, age, status as a protected veteran, status as an individual with a disability, or other applicable legally protected characteristics.</li><li>The people who work at Seattle Children’s are members of a community that seeks to respect and celebrate all the qualities that make each of us unique. Each of us is empowered to be ourselves.</li><li>Seattle Children’s is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Workplace and Affirmative Action Employer.</li></ul>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Bellevue, WA]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Seattle Children’s Hospital]]></company>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>