<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://github.com/christopherlam888/workday-scraper</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Advanced Practice Provider-Transplant Services]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Intermountain-Health-Intermountain-Medical-Center/Advanced-Practice-Provider-Transplant-Services_R139335?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<h3>locations
Intermountain Health Intermountain Medical Center
time type
Full time
posted on
Posted Today
time left to apply
End Date: May 10, 2026 (30+ days left to apply)
job requisition id
R139335
Job Description:
This position is accountable for the provision of patient care and other activities as permitted by licensure and defined within Credentialing and Privileging documentation (hospital), Credentialing and Scope of Practice (Medical Group), Consultation and Referral Plan (DOPL) or other similar documentation as appropriate. As part of that patient care, this position is accountable to: deliver optimal patient care through effective clinical practice; education of the patient, patient's family, clinical staff, and others; consultation with other healthcare providers; and maintain current knowledge regarding options for optimal patient care and outcomes.
Transplant Services Advanced Practice Provider
 
When you join us, you’ll become a part of a nationally recognized health system dedicated to our mission of “helping people live the healthiest lives possible.” 
About this role:</h3><p>As a Nurse Practitioner or Physician Assistant in Transplant Services you will work with a team of healthcare professionals committed to providing quality care and excellent patient experience.  In this role you will support Intermountain Medical Center’s inpatient Liver & Kidney Transplant services, providing inpatient management of post nephrology and hepatobiliary surgery patients.</p><p>This position includes relocation assistance up to $7,500 based upon distance</p><p>You will practice at Intermountain Medical Center in Murray, Utah</p><p>Your hours will be (4) 10-hour shifts per week upon the completion of orientation</p><p>This position will come with the transition to (3) 12.0 hour shifts with call after full on year orientation period</p><p><strong>How we'll support you</strong>:</p><p>We care about your well-being which is why we provide our caregivers with a generous benefits package. In addition, we offer paid time off, license reimbursement, malpractice insurance coverage, and an annual CME allowance to support your continuous growth and development.  Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package.</p><p><strong>What you’ll bring</strong>:</p><p>APRN or PA-C degree from an accredited program</p><p>AANP or AAPA certification</p><p>years of APP experience and OR experience strongly preferred, no new grads please</p><p>Active, unobstructed Utah license, or the ability to obtain one</p><p>BLS certification and DEA</p><p>Ability to successfully complete Intermountain Health’s credentialing process</p><p><strong>About us</strong>:</p><p>Intermountain Health is a model health system providing extraordinary care and superior service at an affordable cost. We are an integrated not-for-profit system of 33 hospitals, 400 clinics, and a medical group with more than 5,000 employed physicians and advanced practice providers across six states in the mountain west.</p><p><strong>Our value statements are core to our culture. They reflect the behavior and attitudes that are important to us, are an agreement for how we treat each other, help us make decisions on how to act, and are a promise of what people can expect from us. Learn more about our Mission, Vision, and Values at</strong>: About Intermountain!</p><p>What does it mean to be a part of Intermountain Health?</p><p>It means joining the Power of We, building an environment where providers and caregivers can deliver the best in healthcare. Realizing each caregiver and volunteer is vital to providing care to our patients, because WE can only achieve the extraordinary together. Committed to the best in research and most advanced technology, the results are better clinical patient outcomes</p><p>Life in Murray, UT</p><p>Murray City is centrally located in the Salt Lake Valley about 8 miles south of Salt Lake City. Murray has a population of about 50,000, its own school district with excellent, schools known for safe high-quality education. Its location, low crime and friendly residents make it an enjoyable and convenient place to live, work and play. With the main Highway I-15 running straight through it, you can get almost anywhere in a matter of minutes. The Wasatch mountains, ski resorts, hiking trails, cultural activities, and sporting events are only moments away. There are performances by the Utah Symphony, Ballet West and Pioneer Theater Company as well as a renovated theater that offers Broadway plays. The Sundance Film Festival and the Park City Art Festival are nationally recognized events held in nearby communities.  The NBA’s Jazz, ECHL Utah Grizzlies hockey, the Salt Lake Bees, a triple-A baseball team, and Real Salt Lake City, a major league soccer team, all represent Salt Lake Valley.</p><p><strong>Physical Requirements</strong>:</p><p>Ongoing need for employee to see and read information, labels, assess patient needs, operate monitors, identify equipment and supplies.</p><p>and -</p><p>Frequent interactions with patient care providers, patients, and visitors that require employee to verbally communicate as well as hear and understand spoken information, alarms, needs, and issues quickly and accurately, particularly during emergency situations.</p><p>and -</p><p>Manual dexterity of hands and fingers to manipulate complex and delicate equipment with precision and accuracy.  This includes frequent computer use and typing for documenting patient care, accessing needed information, medication preparation, etc.</p><p>and -</p><p>Expected to lift and utilize full range of movement to transfer patients.  Will also bend to retrieve, lift, and carry supplies and equipment.  Typically includes items of varying weights, up to and including heavy items.</p><p>and -</p><p>Need to walk and assist with transporting/ambulating patients and obtaining and distributing supplies and equipment.  This includes pushing/pulling gurneys and portable equipment, including heavy items.  Often required to navigate crowded and busy rooms (full of equipment, power cords on the floor, etc).</p><p>and -</p><p>May be expected to stand in a stationary position for an extended period of time.</p><p><strong>Location</strong>:</p><p>Intermountain Health Intermountain Medical Center</p><p><strong>Work City</strong>:</p><p>Murray</p><p><strong>Work State</strong>:</p><p>Utah</p><p><strong>Scheduled Weekly Hours</strong>:</p><p></p><p>The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience.</p><p>$54.84 - $84.63</p><p>We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged.</p><p>Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.</p><p>Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.</p><p>At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.</p><p>All positions subject to close without notice.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Intermountain Health Intermountain Medical Center]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gastroenterologist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Intermountain-Health-American-Fork-Hospital/Gastroenterologist_R115429-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>locations<br />Intermountain Health American Fork Hospital<br />Intermountain Health Utah Valley Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date</strong>: May 10, 2026 (30+ days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R115429<br />Job Description:<br />Gastroenterologist<br />When you join us, you’ll become a part of a nationally recognized health system dedicated to our mission of “helping people live the healthiest lives possible.”<br /> About this role:<br />As a Physician in Gastroenterology, you will work with a team of healthcare professionals committed to providing quality care and excellent patient experience.  In this role you will be a part of an employed Medical Group Gastroenterology practice serving Utah County. We have a strong community need for increased access to GI and Endoscopy care in Utah County, and we have a team-based GI practice model with physician, APP, and nurse teamwork across our clinic and endoscopy locations.  We will help support you in building your GI practice.  <br />This position includes a starting base salary of $600,000/annually with production incentives, a $50,000 sign-on bonus, up to $20,000 relocation assistance based on distance; student loan repayment and a $1,500 monthly training stipend and future ASC opportunities are also available.<br />You will practice at our American Fork and Utah Valley Hospital locations.<br />Call schedule is shared with group and expected at minimum of 1:5 w/ additional call pay for extra call shifts and opportunity for a (4) day work week<br />You will have the opportunity to teach medical students, resident, will lead in developing new academic programs. Leadership opportunities will be available.<br />How we'll support you:<br />We care about your well-being, which is why we provide our caregivers with a generous benefits package. In addition, we offer paid time off, license reimbursement, malpractice insurance coverage, and an annual CME allowance to support your continuous growth and development.  Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package <br /> What you’ll bring:<br />MD or DO degree from a fully accredited medical or osteopathic school of medicine<br />Residency training in Internal Medicine<br />Board certification or eligibility in Internal Medicine with a subspecialty in Gastroenterology<br />ERCP is welcomed but not required for this position <br />Active, unobstructed Utah medical license, or the ability to obtain one<br />Ability to successfully complete Intermountain Health’s credentialing process<br />Candidates requiring Visa sponsorship will be reviewed on an individual basis<br /> About us:<br />Intermountain Health is a model health system by providing extraordinary care and superior service at an affordable cost. We are an integrated not-for-profit system of 33 hospitals, over 400 clinics, and a medical group with more than 5,000 employed physicians and advanced practice providers across six states in the mountain west. <br />Our value statements are core to our culture. They reflect the behavior and attitudes that are important to us, are an agreement for how we treat each other, help us make decisions on how to act, and are a promise of what people can expect from us.  Learn more about our Mission, Vision, and Values at: About Intermountain!<br /> What does it mean to be a part of Intermountain Health?<br />It means joining the Power of We, building an environment where providers and caregivers can deliver the best in healthcare. Realizing each caregiver and volunteer is vital to providing care to our patients, because WE can only achieve the extraordinary together. Committed to the best in research and most advanced technology, the results are better clinical patient outcomes<br /> Life in American Fork, UT<br />American Fork is a beautiful growing community of more than 32,500. It is located at the base of the majestic Mt. Timpanogos which is between American Fork Canyon and Provo Canyon. Recreational opportunities abound in the area, Utah lake lies minutes away where you can pack a lunch and bask in the sun on the sandy beach, launch your boat or rent some toys from the harbor for the day. Other activities include swimming, golfing, water skiing, snow skiing, fishing, hiking, camping, tennis, etc. There are numerous cultural events throughout the year. The short drives to Salt Lake City (35 miles away) and Provo (11 miles away) offer close proximity to two major cities and universities.  American Fork Hospital is a 90-bed acute care facility with over 200 physicians representing 30 specialties.  <br />Physical Requirements:<br />Physical Requirements<br />Interact with others requiring employee to verbally communicate as well as hear and understand spoken information.<br />Operate computers, telephones, office equipment, and manipulate paper requiring the ability to move fingers and hands.<br />See and read computer monitors and documents.<br />Remain sitting or standing for long periods of time to perform work on a computer, telephone, or other equipment.<br />Location:<br />Intermountain Health American Fork Hospital, Intermountain Health Utah Valley Hospital<br />Work City:<br />American Fork<br />Work State:<br />Utah<br />Scheduled Weekly Hours:<br />40<br />The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience. <br />$7.25 - $999.99<br />We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged. <br />Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.<br />Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.<br />At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.<br />All positions subject to close without notice.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Intermountain Health Utah Valley Hospital; Intermountain Health American Fork Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gastroenterologist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Southridge-Clinic-at-Riverton/Gastroenterologist_R109884?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>locations<br />Southridge Clinic at Riverton<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date</strong>: May 10, 2026 (30+ days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R109884<br />Job Description:<br />Gastroenterology (Gastroenterology)<br />Intermountain Medical Group                             <br />When you join us, you’ll become a part of a nationally recognized health system dedicated to our mission of “helping people live the healthiest lives possible.” <br />About this role: <br />A s a Physician in Gastroenterology, you will work with a team of healthcare professionals committed to providing quality care and excellent patient experience. In this role you will be an employed Medical Group Gastroenterologist within a large non-for-profit health system. We have a strong community need for increased access to GI and Endoscopy care and have a team-based GI practice model with physicians, APP support, and nurse teamwork across our clinic and endoscopy locations.  You will benefit from a strong referral base and we will help support you in building your GI practice.      <br />This position includes a starting base salary of $600,000/annually with production incentives, a $50,000 sign-on bonus, up to $20,000 relocation assistance based on distance;  student loan repayment and a $1,500 monthly training stipend and future ASC opportunities are also available<br />You will practice at our Southridge Clinic in Riverton, Utah, which is supported by a network of primary care physicians in the community who are partners within the Intermountain Medical Group<br />Anticipated call is 1:4<br />How we'll support you: <br />We care about your well-being which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package. In addition, we offer paid time off, license reimbursement, malpractice insurance coverage, and an annual CME allowance to support your continuous growth and development.  Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package . <br />What you’ll bring: <br />MD or DO degree from a fully accredited medical or osteopathic school of medicine <br />U.S. ACGME accredited residency training<br />ABMS board certification or eligibility in Gastroenterology <br />Active, unobstructed Utah medical license, or the ability to obtain one <br />BLS certification and DEA<br />ERCP is welcomed but not required for this position <br />Ability to successfully complete Intermountain Health’s credentialing process <br />Candidates requiring Visa sponsorship will be reviewed on an individual basis <br />About us: <br />Intermountain Health is a model health system providing extraordinary care and superior service at an affordable cost. We are an integrated not-for-profit system of 33 hospitals, over 400 clinics, and a medical group with more than 5,000 employed physicians and advanced practice providers across seven states in the mountain west. <br />Our value statements are core to our culture. They reflect the behavior and attitudes that are important to us, are an agreement for how we treat each other, help us make decisions on how to act, and are a promise of what people can expect from us. Learn more about our Mission, Vision, and Values at: About Intermountain! <br />What does it mean to be a part of Intermountain Health? <br />It means joining the Power of We, building an environment where providers and caregivers can deliver the best in healthcare. Realizing each caregiver and volunteer is vital to providing care to our patients, because WE can only achieve the extraordinary together. Committed to the best in research and most advanced technology, the results are better clinical patient outcomes. <br />Life in the Riverton, UT<br />Riverton is located 20 miles southwest of the Salt Lake Valley. It is a quiet community that basks with views of the Wasatch and Oquirrh Mountains. Once a rural farming community - has now flourished into one of the most rapidly growing communities in Salt Lake County. Population is 44,000.  <br />Riverton is within an hour’s drive of nine world-renowned ski resorts and within a day’s drive of five national parks.  Along with these recreational attractions, there are many cultural and sporting events within a short distance. There are performances by the Utah Symphony, Ballet West and Pioneer Theater Company as well as a renovated theater that offers Broadway plays. The NBA’s Jazz, ECHL Utah Grizzlies hockey, the Salt Lake Bees, a triple-A baseball team, and Real Salt Lake City, a major league soccer team, all represent Salt Lake City. Three universities are within a 1-hour drive.  <br />Physical Requirements:<br />Location:<br />Southridge Clinic at Riverton<br />Work City:<br />Riverton<br />Work State:<br />Utah<br />Scheduled Weekly Hours:<br />40<br />The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience. <br />$7.25 - $999.99<br />We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged. <br />Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.<br />Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.<br />At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.<br />All positions subject to close without notice.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Southridge Clinic at Riverton]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gastroenterologist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Alta-View-Specialty-Clinic/Gastroenterologist_R109889?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>locations<br />Alta View Specialty Clinic<br />Intermountain Health Alta View Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date</strong>: May 10, 2026 (30+ days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R109889<br />Job Description:<br />Gastroenterologist<br />When you join us, you’ll become a part of a nationally recognized health system dedicated to our mission of “helping people live the healthiest lives possible.” <br />About this role: <br />As a Physician in Gastroenterology, you will work with a team of healthcare professionals committed to providing quality care and excellent patient experience. In this role you will be an employed Medical Group Gastroenterologist within a large non-for-profit health system. We have a strong community need for increased access to GI and Endoscopy care and have a team-based GI practice model with physicians, APP support, and nurse teamwork across our clinic and endoscopy locations.  You will benefit from a strong referral base and we will help support you in building your GI practice.      <br />This position includes a starting base salary of $600,000/annually with production incentives, a $50,000 sign-on bonus, up to $20,000 relocation assistance based on distance;  student loan repayment and a $1,500 monthly training stipend and future ASC opportunities are also available<br />You will practice at Alta View Gastroenterology Group in Sandy, UT with privileges at Alta View Hospital w/ opportunity for a (4) day work week<br />Call schedule is shared with group and expected at minimum of 1:5 w/ additional call pay for extra call shifts<br />You will see on average 16 – 22 patients per day in clinic, with a blend of endoscopy and hospital service<br />How we'll support you: <br />We care about your well-being which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package. In addition, we offer paid time off, license reimbursement, malpractice insurance coverage, and an annual CME allowance to support your continuous growth and development.  Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package . <br />What you’ll bring: <br />MD or DO degree from a fully accredited medical or osteopathic school of medicine<br />Residency training in Internal Medicine<br />Board certification or eligibility in Internal Medicine with a subspecialty in Gastroenterology<br />ERCP is welcomed but not required for this position <br />Active, unobstructed Utah medical license, or the ability to obtain one<br />Ability to successfully complete Intermountain Health’s credentialing process<br />Candidates requiring Visa sponsorship will be reviewed on an individual basis<br />About us: <br />Intermountain Health is a model health system by providing extraordinary care and superior service at an affordable cost. We are an integrated not-for-profit system of 33 hospitals, over 400 clinics, and a medical group with more than 5,000 employed physicians and advanced practice providers across six states in the mountain west.  <br />Our value statements are core to our culture. They reflect the behavior and attitudes that are important to us, are an agreement for how we treat each other, help us make decisions on how to act, and are a promise of what people can expect from us.  Learn more about our Mission, Vision, and Values at: About Intermountain! <br />What does it mean to be a part of Intermountain Health?  <br />It means joining the power of “WE”, building an environment where providers and caregivers can deliver the best in healthcare. Realizing each caregiver and volunteer is vital to providing care to our patients, because WE can only achieve the extraordinary together. Committed to the best in research and most advanced technology, the results are better clinical patient outcomes.<br />Community Information:<br />The Salt Lake Valley is the heart of the state of Utah, which is one of the fastest growing states in the country. Salt Lake is located at the base of the Wasatch Mountains and is within an hour’s drive of nine world-renowned ski resorts and within a day’s drive of five national parks.  Along with these recreational attractions, there are many cultural and sporting events.  There are performances by the Utah Symphony, Ballet West and Pioneer Theater Company as well as a renovated theater that offers Broadway plays. The Sundance Film Festival and the Park City Art Festival are nationally recognized events held in nearby communities.  The NBA’s Jazz, ECHL Utah Grizzlies hockey, the Salt Lake Bees, a triple-A baseball team, and Real Salt Lake City, a major league soccer team, all represent Salt Lake City. The University of Utah is also in Salt Lake City.<br />Physical Requirements:<br />No Additional Description Available<br />Location:<br />Alta View Specialty Clinic, Intermountain Health Riverton Hospital<br />Work City:<br />Sandy<br />Work State:<br />Utah<br />Scheduled Weekly Hours:<br />40<br />The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience. <br />$7.25 - $999.99<br />We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged. <br />Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.<br />Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.<br />At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.<br />All positions subject to close without notice.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Intermountain Health Alta View Hospital; Alta View Specialty Clinic]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gastroenterologist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/Avenues-Physician-Tower/Gastroenterologist_R105086?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>locations<br />Avenues Physician Tower<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date</strong>: May 10, 2026 (30+ days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R105086<br />Job Description:<br />Gastroenterologist</p><p>When you join us, you’ll become a part of a nationally recognized health system dedicated to our mission of “helping people live the healthiest lives possible.”</p><h3>About this role:</h3><p><strong>As a Physician in Gastroenterology, you will work with a team of healthcare professionals committed to providing quality care and excellent patient experience.  In this role you will be an employed Medical Group Gastroenterologist within a large non-for-profit health system. We have a strong community need for increased access to GI and Endoscopy care and have a team-based GI practice model with physicians, APP support, and nurse teamwork across our clinic and endoscopy locations.   You will benefit from a strong referral base and we will help support you in building your GI practice.  <br />This position includes a starting base salary of $600,000/annually with production incentives, a $50,000 sign-on bonus, up to $20,000 relocation assistance based on distance; student loan repayment and a $1,500 monthly training stipend and future ASC opportunities are also available<br />You will practice at our Avenues Specialty Clinic in Salt Lake City, UT with privileges at LDS Hospital. A brand new state-of-the-art LDS Hospital, with a comprehensive Digestive Diseases Institute, is projected to open in 2028 in downtown Salt Lake City<br />Call schedule is shared with group and expected at minimum of 1</strong>:5 w/ additional call pay for extra call shifts and opportunity for a (4) day work week<br />You will see on average 16 – 22 patients per day in clinic, with a blend of endoscopy and hospital service</p><h3>How we'll support you:</h3><p>We care about your well-being, which is why we provide our caregivers with a generous benefits package. In addition, we offer paid time off, license reimbursement, malpractice insurance coverage, and an annual CME allowance to support your continuous growth and development.  Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package .</p><h3>What you’ll bring:</h3><p>MD or DO degree from a fully accredited medical or osteopathic school of medicine</p><p>Residency training in Internal Medicine</p><p>Board certification or eligibility in Internal Medicine with a subspecialty in Gastroenterology</p><p>ERCP is welcomed but not required for this position</p><p>Active, unobstructed Utah medical license, or the ability to obtain one</p><p>Ability to successfully complete Intermountain Health’s credentialing process</p><p>Candidates requiring Visa sponsorship will be reviewed on an individual basis</p><h3>About us:</h3><p>Intermountain Health is a model health system by providing extraordinary care and superior service at an affordable cost. We are an integrated not-for-profit system of 33 hospitals, over 400 clinics, and a medical group with more than 5,000 employed physicians and advanced practice providers across six states in the mountain west.</p><p><strong>Our value statements are core to our culture. They reflect the behavior and attitudes that are important to us, are an agreement for how we treat each other, help us make decisions on how to act, and are a promise of what people can expect from us.  Learn more about our Mission, Vision, and Values at</strong>: About Intermountain!</p><p>What does it mean to be a part of Intermountain Health?</p><h3>It means joining the power of “WE”, building an environment where providers and caregivers can deliver the best in healthcare. Realizing each caregiver and volunteer is vital to providing care to our patients, because WE can only achieve the extraordinary together. Committed to the best in research and the most advanced technology, the results are better clinical patient outcomes.
 Community Information:</h3><p><strong>The Salt Lake Valley is the heart of the state of Utah, which is one of the fastest growing states in the country. Salt Lake is located at the base of the Wasatch Mountains and is within an hour’s drive of nine world-renowned ski resorts and within a day’s drive of five national parks.  Along with these recreational attractions, there are many cultural and sporting events.  There are performances by the Utah Symphony, Ballet West and Pioneer Theater Company as well as a renovated theater that offers Broadway plays. The Sundance Film Festival and the Park City Art Festival are nationally recognized events held in nearby communities.  The NBA’s Jazz, ECHL Utah Grizzlies hockey, the Salt Lake Bees, a triple-A baseball team, and Real Salt Lake City, a major league soccer team, all represent Salt Lake City. The University of Utah is also in Salt Lake City.<br /> Physical Requirements</strong>:<br />No Additional Description Available<br />Location:<br />Avenues Physician Tower, Intermountain Health LDS Hospital<br />Work City:<br />Salt Lake City<br />Work State:<br />Utah<br />Scheduled Weekly Hours:<br />40<br />The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience. <br />$7.25 - $999.99<br />We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged. <br />Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.<br />Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.<br />At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.<br />All positions subject to close without notice.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Avenues Physician Tower]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Gastroenterologist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://imh.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/IntermountainCareers/job/McKay-Dee-Medical-Building/Gastroenterologist_R124885-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>locations<br />McKay-Dee Medical Building<br />Intermountain Health McKay-Dee Hospital<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />time left to apply<br />End Date</strong>: May 5, 2026 (30+ days left to apply)<br />job requisition id<br />R124885<br />Job Description:<br />Gastroenterologist<br />When you join us, you’ll become a part of a nationally recognized health system dedicated to our mission of “helping people live the healthiest lives possible.” <br />About this role: <br />As a Physician in Gastroenterology, you will work with a team of healthcare professionals committed to providing quality care and excellent patient experience.  In this role you will be a part of an employed Medical Group Gastroenterology. We have a strong community need for increased access to GI and Endoscopy care and we have a team-based GI clinic/hospital practice model with physician, APP, and nurse teamwork across our clinic and endoscopy locations.  We will help support you in building your GI practice.  <br />This position includes a starting base salary of $600,000/annually with production incentives, a $50,000 sign-on bonus, up to $20,000 relocation assistance based on distance; student loan repayment and a $1,500 monthly training stipend and future ASC opportunities are also available<br />You will practice at McKay Dee Gastroenterology Group in Ogden, UT and Layton Gastroenterology with privileges at McKay Dee Hospital & Layton Hospital<br />The call requirement is 1:5 and will be taken at our McKay Dee Hospital and Layton Hospital<br />You will see on average 16 – 22 patients per day in clinic<br />How we'll support you: <br />We care about your well-being which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package. In addition, we offer paid time off, license reimbursement, malpractice insurance coverage, and an annual CME allowance to support your continuous growth and development.  Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package<br />What you’ll bring: <br />MD or DO degree from a fully accredited medical or osteopathic school of medicine<br />Residency training in Internal Medicine<br />Board certification or eligibility in Internal Medicine with a subspecialty in Gastroenterology<br />ERCP is welcomed but not required for this position <br />Active, unobstructed Utah medical license, or the ability to obtain one<br />Ability to successfully complete Intermountain Health’s credentialing process<br />Candidates requiring Visa sponsorship will be reviewed on an individual basis<br />About us: <br />Intermountain Health is a model health system by providing extraordinary care and superior service at an affordable cost. We are an integrated not-for-profit system of 33 hospitals, over 400 clinics, and a medical group with more than 5,000 employed physicians and advanced practice providers across six states in the mountain west.  <br />Our value statements are core to our culture. They reflect the behavior and attitudes that are important to us, are an agreement for how we treat each other, help us make decisions on how to act, and are a promise of what people can expect from us.  Learn more about our Mission, Vision, and Values at: About Intermountain! <br />What does it mean to be a part of Intermountain Health?  <br />It means joining the power of “WE”, building an environment where providers and caregivers can deliver the best in healthcare. Realizing each caregiver and volunteer is vital to providing care to our patients, because WE can only achieve the extraordinary together. Committed to the best in research and most advanced technology, the results are better clinical patient outcomes.<br />Community Information:<br />Ogden is a city in Weber County, 40 miles north of Salt Lake City, that is the perfect place to work and live if you like easy access to outdoor activities. Ogden is located at the base of the Wasatch Mountains and is within a day’s drive of five national parks. Ogden boasts of its breathtaking mountain views and access to skiing/snowboarding (9 resorts within 60-75 min drive, including Snowbasin - site of the 2002 Olympic Downhill). There is no lack of summer activities either with several water recreational locations close by, Pineview Reservoir, Willard Bay, Ogden River Parkway, and only 10 miles from the Great Salt Lake. Within minutes of leaving McKay Dee Hospital, you can find yourself mountain biking, hiking, fishing, kayaking, and rock climbing. There are outdoor activities for all ages, affordable real estate, and our family-oriented community supports diverse interests for all cultures. Ogden is home to Weber State University.  <br />Physical Requirements:<br />No Additional Description Available<br />Location:<br />Intermountain Health McKay-Dee Hospital, McKay-Dee Medical Building<br />Work City:<br />Ogden<br />Work State:<br />Utah<br />Scheduled Weekly Hours:<br />40<br />The hourly range for this position is listed below. Actual hourly rate dependent upon experience. <br />$7.25 - $999.99<br />We care about your well-being – mind, body, and spirit – which is why we provide our caregivers a generous benefits package that covers a wide range of programs to foster a sustainable culture of wellness that encompasses living healthy, happy, secure, connected, and engaged. <br />Learn more about our comprehensive benefits package here.<br />Intermountain Health is an equal opportunity employer. Qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, age, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability or protected veteran status.<br />At Intermountain Health, we use the artificial intelligence ("AI") platform, HiredScore to improve your job application experience. HiredScore helps match your skills and experiences to the best jobs for you. While HiredScore assists in reviewing applications, all final decisions are made by Intermountain personnel to ensure fairness. We protect your privacy and follow strict data protection rules. Your information is safe and used only for recruitment. Thank you for considering a career with us and experiencing our AI-enhanced recruitment process.<br />All positions subject to close without notice.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Intermountain Health McKay-Dee Hospital; McKay-Dee Medical Building]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intermountain Healthcare (IMH)]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Medical Oncology, Clinical Instructor- Hospitalist-Thomas Jeferson Health]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://jeffersonhealth.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/ThomasJeffersonExternal/job/Philadelphia-PA/Medical-Oncology--Clinical-Instructor--Hospitalist-Thomas-Jeferson-Health_REQ-0002424-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>locations<br />Philadelphia, PA<br />time type<br />Full time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />REQ-0002424<br />Job Details<br />The Honickman Center is seeking a compassionate and academically driven Clinical Instructor to join our growing team in the Division of Medical Oncology and Hospital Medicine. This unique dual-role position offers the opportunity to care for oncology inpatients and provide teaching to residents and fellows in a world-class academic environment.<br />Job Description<br />Serve as a hospitalist providing inpatient care to oncology patients at the Honickman Center.<br />Collaborate with oncologists, nurses, and multidisciplinary teams to manage complex cancer cases.<br />Participate in teaching rounds, supervising medical students and residents.<br />Contribute to quality improvement initiatives within oncology and internal medicine.<br />Attend and present at departmental conferences and tumor boards.<br />Engage in academic and scholarly activities as appropriate.<br />Qualifications</strong>:<br />MD or DO degree from an accredited institution.<br />Board Certification or Eligibility in Internal Medicine.<br />Eligible for medical licensure in the state of Pennsylvania.<br />Demonstrated interest or experience in medical oncology or inpatient oncology care.<br />Excellent communication, collaboration, and leadership skills.<br />Academic or teaching experience strongly preferred.<br />We Offer:<br />Competitive salary with comprehensive benefits package.<br />Supportive and collegial working environment.<br />Access to cutting-edge resources and continuing medical education.<br />Opportunities for academic growth and advancement within [Health System/University.<br />About the Honickman Center:<br />Located in the heart of Philadelphia, the Honickman Center is a state-of-the-art facility dedicated to delivering exceptional cancer care and medical education. Our mission integrates patient-centered care, innovation, and teaching excellence in a collaborative environment.<br />Work Shift<br />Rotating (United States of America)<br />Worker Sub Type<br />Regular<br />Primary Location Address<br />100 S 9th Street, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, United States of America<br />Nationally ranked, Jefferson, which is principally located in the greater Philadelphia region, Lehigh Valley and Northeastern Pennsylvania and southern New Jersey, is reimagining health care and higher education to create unparalleled value. Jefferson is more than 65,000 people strong, dedicated to providing the highest-quality, compassionate clinical care for patients; making our communities healthier and stronger; preparing tomorrow's professional leaders for 21st-century careers; and creating new knowledge through basic/programmatic, clinical and applied research. Thomas Jefferson University, home of Sidney Kimmel Medical College, Jefferson College of Nursing, and the Kanbar College of Design, Engineering and Commerce, dates back to 1824 and today comprises 10 colleges and three schools offering 200+ undergraduate and graduate programs to more than 8,300 students. Jefferson Health, nationally ranked as one of the top 15 not-for-profit health care systems in the country and the largest provider in the Philadelphia and Lehigh Valley areas, serves patients through millions of encounters each year at 32 hospitals campuses and more than 700 outpatient and urgent care locations throughout the region. Jefferson Health Plans is a not-for-profit managed health care organization providing a broad range of health coverage options in Pennsylvania and New Jersey for more than 35 years.    <br />Jefferson is committed to providing equal educa­tional and employment opportunities for all persons without regard to age, race, color, religion, creed, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, marital status, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, military status, veteran status, handicap or disability or any other protected group or status.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Philadelphia, PA]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Jefferson Health]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Patient Care Technician - Float Pool / Surge - Phlebotomy Skill Required - Part Time Nights - Jefferson Einstein Montgomery]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://jeffersonhealth.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/ThomasJeffersonExternal/job/Montgomery-County-PA/Patient-Care-Technician---Float-Pool---Surge---Phlebotomy-Skill-Required---Part-Time-Nights---Jefferson-Einstein-Montgomery_REQ-0005916-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>locations<br />Montgomery County, PA<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />REQ-0005916<br />Job Details<br />Patient Care Technician - Float Pool / Surge - Phlebotomy Skill Required - Part Time Nights - Jefferson Einstein Montgomery<br />Job Description<br />Patient Care Technician - Float Pool / Surge - Phlebotomy Skill Required - Part Time Nights - Jefferson Einstein Montgomery<br />Join the mission of Improving Lives as a Patient Care Tech at Jefferson Health. With more than 42,000 employees, we’re the second largest employer in Philadelphia and the largest health system in the Philadelphia region. And our work to improve lives is never done. <br />Patient Care Tech are responsible for the following</strong>: <br />Performs assigned nursing procedures for the comfort and well-being of the patient. <br />Maintains appropriate documentation on all assigned patients, including flow sheets. <br />Assists physicians with examinations and tests as needed. <br />Reporting to the Nurse Manager, Patient Care Tech will provide direct bedside care to patients. Other tasks include respiratory services, rehabilitation services, and phlebotomy.<br />Qualifications:<br />High School Diploma <br />CPR-BLS through the American Heart Association <br />One (1) year experience in an acute care inpatient environment preferred <br />Patient Care Tech/Nursing Assistant certification preferred</p><p>Work Shift<br />Workday Night (United States of America)<br />Worker Sub Type<br />Regular<br />Primary Location Address<br />609 West Germantown Pike, East Norriton, Pennsylvania, United States of America<br />Nationally ranked, Jefferson, which is principally located in the greater Philadelphia region, Lehigh Valley and Northeastern Pennsylvania and southern New Jersey, is reimagining health care and higher education to create unparalleled value. Jefferson is more than 65,000 people strong, dedicated to providing the highest-quality, compassionate clinical care for patients; making our communities healthier and stronger; preparing tomorrow's professional leaders for 21st-century careers; and creating new knowledge through basic/programmatic, clinical and applied research. Thomas Jefferson University, home of Sidney Kimmel Medical College, Jefferson College of Nursing, and the Kanbar College of Design, Engineering and Commerce, dates back to 1824 and today comprises 10 colleges and three schools offering 200+ undergraduate and graduate programs to more than 8,300 students. Jefferson Health, nationally ranked as one of the top 15 not-for-profit health care systems in the country and the largest provider in the Philadelphia and Lehigh Valley areas, serves patients through millions of encounters each year at 32 hospitals campuses and more than 700 outpatient and urgent care locations throughout the region. Jefferson Health Plans is a not-for-profit managed health care organization providing a broad range of health coverage options in Pennsylvania and New Jersey for more than 35 years.    <br />Jefferson is committed to providing equal educa­tional and employment opportunities for all persons without regard to age, race, color, religion, creed, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, marital status, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, military status, veteran status, handicap or disability or any other protected group or status.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Montgomery County, PA]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Jefferson Health]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Mental Health Registered Nurse Job Share (Butterfly 2)]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://oregon.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/SOR_External_Career_Site/job/Salem--OHA--Oregon-State-Hospital/Mental-Health-Registered-Nurse-Job-Share--Butterfly-2-_REQ-180401?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>locations<br />Salem | OHA | Oregon State Hospital<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />REQ-180401<br />Initial Posting Date</strong>: <br />05/10/2025<br />Application Deadline:<br />05/17/2025<br />Agency:<br />Oregon Health Authority<br />Salary Range:<br />8,237 -  10,877<br />Position Type:<br />Employee<br />Position Title:<br />Mental Health Registered Nurse Job Share (Butterfly 2)<br />Job Description:<br />Opportunity Awaits, Apply Today!  - Mental Health Registered Nurse (Job Share)</p><p><strong>The Oregon State Hospital, a division of the Oregon Health Authority, has a fantastic opportunity for REGISTERED NURSES  to join an excellent team working to help people recover from their illness and return to their lives in the community.<br /> What you will do!<br />You will provide nursing care to individuals currently residing in the Oregon State Hospital, which is a forensic psychiatric facility. You will administer medications as ordered by the provider, develop nursing plans of care, complete assessments, and respond to emergent psychiatric situations that could potentially be dangerous.  Additionally, you will monitor staff work assignments, and supervise staff to provide therapeutic, safe, and secure milieu.<br />For a full review of the position description, please click here<br />This is a job share on Butterfly 2, working day shift on Saturday-Sunday.<br />Working Days</strong>: Saturday-Sunday 6:30am-5:00pm<br />This position is represented by AFSCME<br />Employees sharing the 1.0 FTE (full time equivalent) split the benefits, with contributions that are equal.<br />If one Job Share partner is removed, resigns or is otherwise separated from state service, pending this action, the Appointing Authority has the right to determine if job sharing is still appropriate for the position<br />If you are an internal candidate (OHA) coming from a limited duration position, you would return to a limited duration position in the event the job shares ends.<br />If this opportunity aligns with your strengths, background, and commitment to fostering inclusivity, we encourage you to apply! At the Oregon Health Authority (OHA), we value diversity and encourage applicants from all backgrounds and experiences to help us build a stronger, more equitable future for all.<br />What We Are Looking For<br />Minimum Qualifications:<br />Must possess and maintain a valid and unencumbered Oregon Professional Registered Nurse license during the entire length of their employment.<br />Desired Attributes: <br />Experience working in mental health<br />Experience in conflict and crisis management<br />Strong leadership skills<br />Experience in milieu management<br />Ability to manage multiple job responsibilities at one time<br />Special Qualifications:<br />If you are offered employment, the offer will be contingent upon the outcome of an abuse check, criminal records check and driving records check, and the information shall be shared with the Oregon Health Authority (OHA), Office of Human Resources (OHR). Any criminal or founded abuse history will be reviewed and could result in the withdrawal of the offer or termination of employment.<br />Candidates who are offered employment at the Oregon State Hospital must satisfactorily pass a pre-employment drug test.<br />Pay incentives for our Registered Nurses <br />Educational incentives:<br />Bachelor’s degree +4.75% base rate<br />Master’s degree + 9.5% base rate<br />Doctorate degree +12% base rate<br />Shift incentives for Weekends, Evenings, Nights as well as specialty differentials for additional continuing education<br />Application Guidance<br />How to Apply: Submission Requirements - At the time of application, ensure the work history in your applicant profile is up to date and answer all supplemental questions. <br />External Candidates: Visit the State of Oregon job opportunities webpage to submit your application. Be sure to follow all application submission requirements.<br />Internal Candidates: Current State of Oregon employees must apply through their employee Workday login. Be sure to follow all application submission requirements.<br />After You Apply:<br />Before the job announcement closes, log in to your Workday account to check for pending tasks under “My Applications” and complete them.<br />Remember to check your email (including your junk folder) and Workday inbox for updates on your application.<br />We value our veterans! To ensure the security of your information, kindly follow the instructions for how to submit your Veteran documents for preference found here. Please do not attach your Veterans’ preference documentation in the Resume/CV field of your application.<br />Reminders:<br />Your candidate profile and application materials are great opportunities to showcase your interest in the position and highlight your skills and experience. Submissions will be screened for consistency and communication skills, including attention to detail, spelling, and grammar. For more tips and guidance, check out What you need to know to get the job!<br />This announcement is for one  permanent, half-time, Mental Health Registered Nurse position located in Salem, Oregon ( 2600 Center St. NE). <br />This position is 100% onsite. Please check SECTION 4. WORKING CONDITIONS, of the position description linked above to review more details regarding the details surrounding the working conditions.<br />Please download and save a copy of this job announcement and linked position description, as it is not available after the application deadline. For questions about the announcement, or if you require an alternate format to apply, please contact Jenny Templin at 971-372-8147 or Jenny.Templin@oha.oregon.gov.<br />Benefits of Joining Our Team<br />We offer a workplace that balances productivity with enjoyment; promote an atmosphere of mutual respect, dedication, and enthusiasm. You will collaborate with a team of bright individuals to work with and learn from. If you're driven by the passion to do something meaningful that changes lives, the Oregon Health Authority is the place for you. We also offer a competitive benefits package including:<br />Excellent medical, vision, and dental benefits package for the employee and qualified family members with a very low monthly out-of-pocket cost.<br />Optional life insurance, short-term disability, long-term disability, deferred compensation savings program, and flexible spending accounts for health care and childcare expenses.<br />Employee benefits include 11 paid holidays, 3 personal business days, 8 hours of monthly sick leave, and vacation accrual starting at 8 hours per month.<br />Possible eligibility for the Public Service Loan Forgiveness Program.<br />Membership in the Public Employees Retirement System (PERS)/Oregon Public Service Retirement Plan (OPSRP).<br />Training opportunities that will help grow your career with the State of Oregon.<br />Additional Details<br />The information in your application will be used to complete an Equal Pay Analysis to determine salary placement upon hire. Visit the Department of Administrative Services Equal Pay Analysis Webpage for more information.<br />The salary listed is the non-PERS qualifying salary range. If the successful candidate is PERS qualifying, the salary range will reflect the additional 6.95%. Review the Classification and Compensation page for more details on the classification.<br />Agency does not offer visa sponsorship. Within three days of hire, applicants will be required to complete I-9 documentation and confirm authorization to work in the United States. If your employment authorization and documentation is contingent on sponsorship now or in the future, you will not meet Agency employment eligibility standards.<br />Helpful Links & Resources<br />How to Set Job Alerts | Workday Applicant FAQ | Oregon Health Authority | Facebook | Instagram | LinkedIn | Veterans Resources<br />The Oregon Health Authority is an equal opportunity, affirmative action employer, committed to diversity and pay equity.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Salem | OHA | Oregon State Hospital]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Oregon State Government]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Registered Dietitian- Registry]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://aah.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/Advocate-Christ-Hospital--Medical-Center---4440-W-95th-St/Registered-Dietitian--Registry_R152547-1?q=nurse]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>locations<br />Advocate Christ Hospital & Medical Center - 4440 W 95th St<br />time type<br />Part time<br />posted on<br />Posted Today<br />job requisition id<br />R152547<br />Department</strong>:<br />11903 Advocate Christ Medical Center - Food and Nutrition<br />Status: <br />Part time<br />Benefits Eligible:<br />No<br />Hours Per Week:<br />0<br />Schedule Details/Additional Information:<br />Primarily weekend assistance, approximately one weekend per month. Possible assistance during the week to assist with time off coverage.<br />Major Responsibilities<br />Daily, provides ongoing Medical Nutrition Therapy (MNT) care for entire hospital inpatient census, through screening, prioritizing, assessing, and recommending interventions. Adapts daily workflow to accommodate fluctuations in patient load due to daily census variations, consults, acuity, staffing challenges. Develops and implements a plan of care for patients based on an expert assessment of life cycle- and diagnosis-specific nutritional needs. Assessment includes reviews of medical history and laboratory data, patient interviews, and physical examinations to determine the current nutritional status of inpatients and/or outpatients. Based on the assessment, the Clinical Dietitian develops and implements individualized nutrition plan of care interventions. Documents medical nutrition therapy plan of care in the electronic medical record supporting system clinical documentation and coding standards to maximize reimbursement rates.<br />Prescribes enteral and parenteral nutrition support orders by assessing the patient and calculating macronutrients and/or micronutrients, fluid, and electrolytes. Evaluates patient tolerance and effectiveness of formulas and manages initiation or modifications to enteral/parenteral regimen orders. The Clinical Dietitian demonstrates extensive knowledge of specialized nutrition support (parenteral and enteral) and triages issues and concerns through collaboration with physicians and pharmacy. Constant, secure communication with system level Pharmacy Integrated Clinical Services (PICS) team to manage and order Total Parental Nutrition (TPN) infusions for critically ill patients in the hospital.<br />The Clinical Dietitian prescribes orders for therapeutic diets, oral nutrition supplements, and nutrition support regimens, including vitamins/minerals, fluid management, and lab work as indicated within the scope of the Medical Nutrition Therapy (MNT) protocol. Utilizes order-writing privileges to implement nutrition related orders. Collaborates with Food and Nutrition patient services team to ensure patient intake aligns with nutrition prescription and interdisciplinary plan of care. Partners with site patient services team to identify and recommend appropriate clinical nutrition formula and supplement substitutions during supply chain disruptions to reduce and eliminate significant disruptions to patient care. Partners with physicians, nursing, and nutrition patient services to ensure diet restrictions, allergy restrictions, supplement preferences and tube feedings are consistent with patient needs and personal, religious, and cultural preferences. Develops patient-specific menus for patients admitted with complex dietary needs (e.g., multiple food allergies, numerous diet restrictions, and/or low-use, high risk diet orders).<br />Leads efforts to identify, treat and prevent malnutrition. Performs Nutrition Focused Physical Examinations of high-risk patients to evaluate the loss of specific muscles and subcutaneous body fat to determine the presence of and degree of malnutrition. Communicates findings to the medical team through medical record documentation to ensure maximized reimbursement. Provides medical nutrition therapy education to patients identified with moderate or severe malnutrition to improve patient outcomes and to positively impact inpatient readmission rates.<br />Routinely documents elements of the Global Malnutrition Composite Score (GMCS) for Medicare and Medicaid Services’ (CMS) Nutrition Electronic Quality Indicators. Participates in Quality Assessment Performance Improvement (QAPI) efforts to ensure nutrition care is safe and effective for patients.   Maintains regulatory readiness. Supports department clinical initiatives to ensure compliance with safety initiatives, policies, and procedures, DNV regulations, and department standards.<br />Identifies and documents billable nutrition diagnosis with supporting documentation. May provide clinical support to various hospital-based outpatient medical destination programs (e.g., cancer center, transplant clinic, digestive health programs, bariatric, cardiac rehab, heart failure, etc.) Enters charges for outpatient nutrition charge capture in electronic medical record.<br />Supports partnerships with local didactic programs by precepting dietetic graduate students in clinical nutrition and/or foodservice management. Directs and monitors interns’ progress both daily and at designated touchpoints and provides feedback for growth and development. Communicates regularly with didactic program coordinator. Also, precepts medical residents and provides nutrition orientation as applicable. Provides nutrition lectures to medical residents for internal medicine, trauma, NICU/Peds, and family practice, as applicable.<br />Collaborates routinely with discharge planners, home health, physicians, pharmacy, and other interdisciplinary teams to address the full scope of the system-established priority points protocol for inpatient care. Participates in interdisciplinary team rounds, meetings, and care conferences to coordinate and collaborate on nutrition goals. Assists with transition to home or outside facilities by partnering with Care Management and/or Home Health to coordinate home enteral and/or parenteral nutrition needs.<br />Provides medical nutrition therapy education to patients on prescribed diet, per established priority system, to improve patient knowledge/understanding of nutrition, diet therapy and compliance on prescribed diet. Education is provided to inpatients, outpatients and family members through individual counseling and classes. May provide nutrition in-services to teammates, as applicable.<br />Provides clinical input into system clinical nutrition initiatives and practice changes. Participates in system subgroups/projects, as assigned, to develop and implement evidence-based nutrition practices, clinical initiatives and/or practice changes. Partners with system patient services and clinical teams to deploy system changes and updates regarding CBORD, EPIC, menus, emergency preparedness, downtime processes, formulary, clinical procedures, and policies. Liaisons between clinical nutrition and inpatient nursing and physicians to champion system clinical nutrition initiatives (e.g., new dysphagia standards, malnutrition coding practice changes, enteral nutrition equipment changes, malnutrition nurse screening changes, safety protocol changes, etc.) Assists (via in-person or remote coverage) other sites throughout the State, as needed, to provide clinical nutrition coverage to assure equitable patient care.<br /> Licensure, Registration, and/or Certification Required<br />Dietitian certification issued by the Commission of Dietetic Registration (CDR)<br />Dietitian (RD) registration with the Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics<br />Licensure by the Department of Financial and Professional Regulation (IL only)<br />Certification by the Department of Safety and Professional Services (WI only)<br /> Education Required<br />Minimum of Bachelor's Degree (if CDR registration eligibility is obtained prior to January 1, 2024) or Minimum of Graduate Degree (master’s, practice doctorate, or doctoral) (if initial CDR registration is obtained on or after January 1, 2024)<br />Successful completion of Accreditation Council for Education in Nutrition and Dietetics (ACEND) accredited supervised practice program.<br /> Experience Required:<br />Didactic experience in clinical nutrition from an ACEND approved program.<br /> Knowledge, Skills & Abilities Required:<br />Advanced knowledge in clinical nutrition and Nutrition Focused Physical Exams<br />Ability to respond to the needs of a diverse patient population.<br />Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.<br />Excellent organization, decision-making, time management, and problem-solving skills<br /> Physical Requirements and Working Conditions:<br />Must be able to sit, stand, walk, lift, squat, bend, reach above shoulders and twist frequently during the work shift.<br />Will occasionally be required to lift 25 pounds.<br />Must have functional vision, hearing, speech, and touch.<br />May need to travel between work sites; therefore, may have exposure to weather-related hazards.<br />May need to work remotely and assist other sites as needed.<br />Operates all equipment necessary to perform the job.<br />Exposed to a normal office environment.<br /> This job description indicates the general nature and level of work expected of the incumbent. It is not designed to cover or contain a comprehensive listing of activities, duties or responsibilities required of the incumbent. Incumbents may be required to perform other related duties.<br />Pay Range<br />$28.05 - $45.25<br />Our Commitment to You:<br />Advocate Health offers a comprehensive suite of Total Rewards: benefits and well-being programs, competitive compensation, generous retirement offerings, programs that invest in your career development and so much more – so you can live fully at and away from work, including:<br />Compensation<br />Base compensation listed within the listed pay range based on factors such as qualifications, skills, relevant experience, and/or training<br />Premium pay such as shift, on call, and more based on a teammate's job<br />Incentive pay for select positions<br />Opportunity for annual increases based on performance<br />Benefits and more<br />Paid Time Off programs<br />Health and welfare benefits such as medical, dental, vision, life, and Short- and Long-Term Disability<br />Flexible Spending Accounts for eligible health care and dependent care expenses<br />Family benefits such as adoption assistance and paid parental leave<br />Defined contribution retirement plans with employer match and other financial wellness programs<br />Educational Assistance Program<br />About Advocate Health <br />Advocate Health is the third-largest nonprofit, integrated health system in the United States, created from the combination of Advocate Aurora Health and Atrium Health. Providing care under the names Advocate Health Care in Illinois; Atrium Health in the Carolinas, Georgia and Alabama; and Aurora Health Care in Wisconsin, Advocate Health is a national leader in clinical innovation, health outcomes, consumer experience and value-based care. Headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina, Advocate Health services nearly 6 million patients and is engaged in hundreds of clinical trials and research studies, with Wake Forest University School of Medicine serving as the academic core of the enterprise. It is nationally recognized for its expertise in cardiology, neurosciences, oncology, pediatrics and rehabilitation, as well as organ transplants, burn treatments and specialized musculoskeletal programs. Advocate Health employs 155,000 teammates across 69 hospitals and over 1,000 care locations, and offers one of the nation’s largest graduate medical education programs with over 2,000 residents and fellows across more than 200 programs. Committed to providing equitable care for all, Advocate Health provides more than $6 billion in annual community benefits.</p>]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[Advocate Christ Hospital & Medical Center - 4440 W 95th St]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Advocate Aurora Health (AAH)]]></company>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>