<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Workday Scraper - RSS Feed</title>
<link>https://stableotto.github.io/workdayxml/</link>
<description>An RSS feed for new Workday postings.</description>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Intel: EDA Design Flow Development Engineer]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-Oregon-Hillsboro/EDA-Design-Flow-Development-Engineer_JR0274704-1?timeType=dc193d6170de10860883d9bf7c0e01a9&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10174f0548376bf811bcf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1016541777876bf8111cf&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1011246675c76bf81f8ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101d4e5a61779bf8159d1&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10118b1dfe877bf8162d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf10129d05fe377bf815dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1013ddb7bd877bf8153d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1018c4bf78f77bf8112d0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101b8aec18a77bf810dd0&locations=1e4a4eb3adf101630310dd75bf81a9ce&locations=1e4a4eb3adf1019f4237e975bf81b3ce&workerSubType=dc8bf79476611087dfde9c6b065bae76]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>US, California, Folsom<br>US, California, Santa Clara<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>JR0274704<br>Job Details:<br>Job Description: <br>Technology Development (TD) is the heart and soul of Moore's Law at Intel, enabling Intel to create world-changing technology that enriches the lives of every person on earth. TD drives breakthrough research and develops next generation process/packaging technologies, while also running high volume manufacturing operations in its state-of-the-art facilities in Oregon and Arizona. The Design Technology Platform (DTP) team in TD works closely with the technology team to maximize the value proposition of the technology for our customers thru Design Technology Co-Optimization (DTCO), delivers the Process Design Kits (PDKs), foundational IPs (FIPs), and the Intel Foundry reference flows. These same deliverables carry out technology lead vehicle execution for Si validation. Enablement and optimization of reference flows and design flows on Intel technology play a crucial role in accomplishing DTP's charter. Design flow development engineer will work in a team responsible for architecting, executing, and delivery of the EDA design flow for all DTCO activities, technology lead vehicle design, IP design, and product design in TD. The design flow will be built on top of a reference flow enabled on Intel technology and released from external EDA vendors. The design flow covers all aspects of front-end and back-end design from RTL to GDS, digital and analog, design creation, verification, and signoff. The candidate must be result-oriented and capable of disciplined flow execution to meet delivery milestones in a fast-paced environment on advanced technology nodes. Prior experience in EDA tool/flow and design environment development is highly desirable. Familiarity with automated SoC design methodology and/or analog/mixed-signal design methodology is a big plus.<br>Qualifications:<br>Minimum qualifications are required to be initially considered for this position. Preferred qualifications are in addition to the minimum requirements and are considered a plus factor in identifying top candidates.<br>Minimum Qualification:<br>Candidate must have a BS, MS, or PhD degree in electrical engineering, computer engineering or similar field.<br>BS + 7 years or M.S./Ph.D. + 5 years of experience in the development of EDA tools, flows and/or design env for digital or analog designs with demonstrated strong programing skills.<br>Working knowledge in digital and/or analog Si design and methodology.<br>Preferred Qualifications:<br>Working knowledge with major (EDA) software platforms (Synopsys, Cadence, Siemens).<br>Working knowledge of all aspects of digital SoC in a product setting - floorplanning, RTL design, logic synthesis, place and route, clock tree construction, extraction and timing signoff, signal integrity analysis, layout and reliability verification, and full chip integration.<br>Working knowledge of key aspects of Analog tools - schematic entry, custom layout editing, extraction, simulation, reliability, and signoff.<br>Demonstrated experience in establishing and qualifying digital or analog design flow from an EDA reference flow and addressing product specific design/methodology requirements and design database management.<br>Demonstrated ability to understand and interpret industry EDA trend in response to advanced node requirements, drive design flow initiatives to align.<br>          Job Type:<br>Experienced Hire<br>Shift:<br>Shift 1 (United States of America)<br>Primary Location: <br>US, Oregon, Hillsboro<br>Additional Locations:<br>US, Arizona, Phoenix, US, California, Folsom, US, California, Santa Clara<br>Business group:<br>As the world's largest chip manufacturer, Intel strives to make every facet of semiconductor manufacturing state-of-the-art -- from semiconductor process development and manufacturing, through yield improvement to packaging, final test and optimization, and world class Supply Chain and facilities support.  Employees in the Technology Development and Manufacturing Group are part of a worldwide network of design, development, manufacturing, and assembly/test facilities, all focused on utilizing the power of Moore’s Law to bring smart, connected devices to every person on Earth.<br>Posting Statement:<br>All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, religious creed, sex, national origin, ancestry, age, physical or mental disability, medical condition, genetic information, military and veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, gender, gender expression, gender identity, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by local law, regulation, or ordinance.<br>Position of Trust<br>N/A<br>Benefits:<br>We offer a total compensation package that ranks among the best in the industry. It consists of competitive pay, stock, bonuses, as well as, benefit programs which include health, retirement, and vacation.  Find more information about all of our Amazing Benefits here:<br>https://intel.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/page/1025c144664a100150b4b1665c750003<br>Annual Salary Range for jobs which could be performed in the US:<br>$161,230.00-$227,620.00<br>Salary range dependent on a number of factors including location and experience.<br>Work Model for this Role<br>This role will be eligible for our hybrid work model which allows employees to split their time between working on-site at their assigned Intel site and off-site. * Job posting details (such as work model, location or time type) are subject to change.]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[4 Locations]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Intel]]></company>
</item>
<item>
    <title><![CDATA[Analog: Principal Regulatory Affairs Specialist]]></title>
    <link><![CDATA[https://analogdevices.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/External/job/US-MA-Wilmington/Principal-Regulatory-Affairs-Specialist_R251983?locationCountry=bc33aa3152ec42d4995f4791a106ed09&locationCountry=a30a87ed25634629aa6c3958aa2b91ea&timeType=1a15e0fbb61110090028388769cb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec24734fbbbb0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec247e24e03b0000&jobFamilyGroup=633b03df4f5d1000ec243f6e4cb40001&workerSubType=633b03df4f5d1000ec10abdfb8db0000]]></link>
    <description><![CDATA[locations<br>US, MA, Wilmington<br>time type<br>Full time<br>posted on<br>Posted Today<br>job requisition id<br>R251983<br>About Analog Devices<br>Analog Devices, Inc. (NASDAQ: ADI ) is a global semiconductor leader that bridges the physical and digital worlds to enable breakthroughs at the Intelligent Edge. ADI combines analog, digital, and software technologies into solutions that help drive advancements in digitized factories, mobility, and digital healthcare, combat climate change, and reliably connect humans and the world. With revenue of more than $9 billion in FY24 and approximately 24,000 people globally, ADI ensures today's innovators stay Ahead of What's Possible™. Learn more at www.analog.com and on LinkedIn and Twitter (X).<br>          Principal Regulatory Affairs Specialist<br>Summary of the Role/About the Team & Org <br>ADI’s Digital Healthcare Group is developing novel remote monitoring solutions that improve patient care and quality of life, while keeping costs low.  The Digital Healthcare Group is looking for an energetic, Principal Regulatory Affairs Specialist for the development of novel solutions.   <br> Specific Responsibilities / Duties <br>Provide strategic input and technical guidance on regulatory requirements for new technologies and product modifications, considering FDA regulations   <br>Prepare Pre-Sub and 510(k) submissions and technical documents to support CE mark and other international submissions   <br>Participate in negotiations and interactions with regulatory authorities during the development and review process   <br>Support international product registrations as needed  <br>Manage multiple projects and prioritize tasks on day-by-day basis to meet project schedules  <br>Interface with engineering, quality, clinical, marketing, and other functions as needed to fulfill responsibilities  <br>Review promotional and advertising material  <br>Maintain current regulatory knowledge of domestic and international regulations, guidelines, and standards  <br>Create or revise departmental procedures to improve operations or to reflect changing regulatory requirements  <br>Participate in internal and external audits as needed  <br>Maintain Regulatory affairs documentation to support compliance with applicable regulatory requirements  <br>Ensure compliance with design controls in accordance with ISO 13485 standard and 21 CFR 820 regulation.  <br>Manage Internal Audit program in accordance with ISO 13485 and MDSAP and host all 3rd party audits including FDA. <br>Provide training of QMS processes   <br>Perform other duties as assigned or required  <br>  Previous Experience/Skills Needed & Education Requirements <br>MS Regulatory Affairs <br>Experience with ISO 13485, MDSAP and FDA QSR <br>Should be willing to learn & shouldn’t be afraid of getting their hands dirty! <br>For positions requiring access to technical data, Analog Devices, Inc. may have to obtain export  licensing approval from the U.S. Department of Commerce - Bureau of Industry and Security and/or the U.S. Department of State - Directorate of Defense Trade Controls.  As such, applicants for this position – except US Citizens, US Permanent Residents, and protected individuals as defined by 8 U.S.C. 1324b(a)(3) – may have to go through an export licensing review process.<br>Analog Devices is an equal opportunity employer. We foster a culture where everyone has an opportunity to succeed regardless of their race, color, religion, age, ancestry, national origin, social or ethnic origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, gender expression, marital status, pregnancy, parental status, disability, medical condition, genetic information, military or veteran status, union membership, and political affiliation, or any other legally protected group.<br>EEO is the Law: Notice of Applicant Rights Under the Law.<br>Job Req Type: Experienced<br>          Required Travel: Yes, 10% of the time<br>          Shift Type: 1st Shift/Days<br>          ]]></description>
    <location><![CDATA[US, MA, Wilmington]]></location>
    <company><![CDATA[Analog]]></company>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>